Toyotomi Hideyoshi, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba Prefecture.
Oda Shintaro. A one-hit wonder who is ignorant of theory. From Chiba Prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasube. An absolute ignoramus who doesn't know when to stop calling. From Chiba.
Akechi Koichi. The expert in by-the-book calculative and rational playstyle. From Chiba.
Hayami Akina.
Technically Toyotomi's love interest.
Born with incredible luck.
From Chiba Prefecture.
It's from Mom!
My dear Hideyuki,
are you doing fine?
I keep worrying about you every day,
as I look up at the autumn sky.
It's getting colder day by day,
so be careful not to catch a cold.
Because of his age, your Dad's gotten a bit weaker than before.
You should call us to let Dad hear your cheerful voice again once in a while!
With that, I wish you all the luck in your university studies. Yours truly, Mom.
Mom...
P.S. The student lifestyle seems to use up a lot of money.
Together with my homemade dried plums,
I've sent you 50,000 yen extra this month.
Treat yourself to some nice warm meals with it, okay?
Mooom!
Episode 4 Part 1
Rake Zugan
Don't walk on the lawn!
What do I do now? I wasted all my textbook money on horse races...
What was that?
You got off lightly, you know!
It's autumn and I don't even have anything to wear!
Look! What is this?!
So we're all still in summer clothes, huh...
The autumn wind really stings.
Anyway!
There are only two ways to break out of this
stock market recession brought about by the collapse of the bubble economy!
What are those?
The first would be to further reduce the official bank discount rate.
And the other one is...
Taking out a massive loan from Toyotomi Bank.
It's the only way!
Yeah!
Fiscal restructuring without raising taxes!
A sound compensation for our losses!
Student Cooperative Textbook Store
If I hadn't gotten that money from Mom,
I wouldn't have been able to buy my textbooks!
Um, could I please have some materials on the finance theory, accounting and marketing theory?
We've been waiting!
You sure took your sweet time with it!
Not again!
Toyotomi Hideyuki! We already know everything about where you go out and about!
Thou shalt give up and submit to arrest!
I beg your forgiveness, High Prosecutor!
I haven't done anything...
Enough! No arguing!
Take him away at once!
Yessir!
Oh?
University-wide
Mahjong
Tournament
Zugaan...
Mahjong parlor
Spider's
Web
No luck!
What's your problem? Complaining about your luck the moment you sit down to play...
That's why ya can't ever win, bro!
Put some fight in it! Fight!
No luck...
Thickheads!
I'm actually iishanten for tanyao dora 3! I'm just pretending to be dejected so as not to alert them.
Dora
2m!
Pon!
My kanchan filled up.
This's got to be riichi!
No luck...
C'mon, give me a good draw!
I'm luckless for real...
Still...
I shan't fold!
Oh? You're cutting that?
That's ron from me.
Just riichi ippatsu.
Oh?
This one's uradora!
It got expensive: mangan!
What?! That was like the last tile!
Look!
Getting the last 7s to come out on ippatsu...
Well, it's got to be that!
N-No way it's that time...
Don't tell me it's what they call the Hell Summoning Beacon...
Oh no! It really is the Raking Warning!
Rake: a term used in mahjong to refer to stacking point sticks in an impressive manner.
Among expert mahjong players,
it is considered good etiquette to warn opponents in advance
when they believe they have entered "Raking" mode, regardless of how small the amount is.
Mahjong: indeed, only the truest of gentlemen will be accepted into this game!
Oh! This is a pretty good hand!
Double riichi!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Rake tsumo!
Double riichi ippatsu tsumo chiitoi, 6000 all!
Big Rake-in!
Only this much after a hanchan, huh?
I'm not in my best shape today...
Look, I hope you know a good way to off yourself.
REMATCH
No luck...
Tenpai!
I can win a tanpin sanshoku!
Come out!
Riichi!
What's wrong?
I called riichi!
Dealer's riichi, you know.
I-I see now...
Whenever I'm in tenpai with a good hand...
It's a trap!
It's an elaborate trap!
Making such a good hand, and drawing that riichi's winning tile on the ippatsu turn?
Who'd have thought!
Hey mister, start moving, won't you?
Oh, there's no need to rush so much.
Wut?
Once I draw that tile, my fate of destroying my hand is sealed...
It's all right now...
I shan't panic in the face of death.
But, at least... At least...
Even if for just a minute more...
Allow me to live in this pleasant dream!
Hey you! Stop crying
and draw already! C'mon!
Got it.
See?
It's his winning tile just like I thought.
The gods of mahjong seem to be fond of unfairness.
Good grief!
Well then, let's just fold with genbutsu.
Wait!
How can you allow yourself to talk this way?
Akina-chan...
You're still young, aren't you?!
Why aren't you going all-in with this hand?!
Well, going from previous experience, this is usually the dealer's winning tile...
Leave weakness to the old and frail!
Whoa!
Young players must have the determination to make a comeback even after they dealt in once!
That's no good, Akina-chan!
If it passes, it passes!
It passed.
We did it, Toyotomi-kun!
Ugh, I mean riichi!
That was a riichi!
Ugh, poor me...
Ron! Mentanpin ippatsu sanshoku!
Hooray!
What?!
Now it's your turn to Rake In!
All right...
Rake warning!
This is bad! Even if it's just Toyotomi, once he gets the ball rolling, we'll be in trouble!
Gotta get him off the dealer fast!
Ooh!
Dora
Should I tsumo...
As dealer, tsumo dora 1 is 1000 all...
No, wait!
I'm in the Rake mode right now!
Discarding this one and going furiten riichi on 369p 47p is the only choice!
Riichi!
Attaway!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Rake tsumo!
Bring it on! Big Rake!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo tanyao sanshoku dora dora! Bang bang!
No! I don't wanna hear a call that's that long!
All Last
Wow! So many point sticks!
Not sure I can lift it all!
I hope you fall and break your neck.
You should be all right now, Toyotomi-kun.
I have a seminar now, so I've gotta run.
Sure thing! Leave it to me!
Dora
I did it! 369m three sided tenpai!
The dora is 7m.
I should just push straightaway!
Rake-In riichi!
Oh? Huh? It stopped!
Toyotomi screwed up.
No matter how hard you are Raking, when you are first place in all last and can win with dama,
no matter if you have a 3 sided wait or a 100 sided wait, you must not riichi!
It feels like you'll win even if you riichi.
However, it's a trap!
Not just that,
it's a textbook example of a trap!
Fodl.
Same.
Shan't fodl as dealer!
Pass, wontcha?
Haitei
C'mon, tsumo with haitei!
It's a bust!
Wut?! It came out?!
Ron!
Menhon haitei chiitoi dora dora!
Super Zugaaan...
It's my turn now!
Check it out! Suuankou tsumo!
Mahjong parlor
Spider's
Web
Zugaan!
Secretly, Toyotomi took a part-time job as an office cleaner to learn how to use the rake better.
Come on! Put your back into it!
Well, you're not exactly a pro with that rake, are you?
Maybe you'd be better off working as a delivery boy.
Dear Mom, I got your package.
Your dried plums were really tasty.
I bought textbooks with the money you sent me.
Take care of your health too, Mom.
And give my earnest regards to Dad.
Toyotomi Noe, Anegasaki City, Chiba Prefecture
However, this letter was never destined to be mailed.
East 3, West seat, turn 9, 27600 points Tsumo: 5p Dora: 4s
Read RB1
Mahjong Parlor
No country for suckers
Episode 4 Part 2
Akina Once More
Wait, which round are we in again?
Toyotomi, how much points you got?
Exactly 10,000, huh...
So next round is East 4.
I'm telling you, having Toyotomi around really is useful.
True that.
Whadja mean?
You can look at Toyotomi's point sticks to know which round it is.
Oh?
After East 1, he ends up with 20,000 points.
East 1
South 1
20,000 points or less
10,000 points or more
A single stick
Box
20,000
or less
10,000
or more
A single
stick
Empty
box
After East 2, he usually still has over 10,000.
Then, he gets shadowrealmed in East 4.
Up to minus 25,000 in all last, you can tell pretty precisely.
Got it.
A real convenient fella...
Dora
I did it!
Pinfu dora 1 with possible tanyao and a three sided wait!
That's a riichi!
Chii!
Look.
White!
Pon!
Look!
Pon.
3m.
Chii!
2m!
Pon. Look!
Chii!
6m!
Zugan.
Ron!
Give it a rest!!
Zugandhi.
Oh? Toyotomi got shadowrealmed! Time for South!
Riichi!
Embrace the nonresistance.
Ippatsu!
He's coming!
Long live Zugandhi!
Toyotomi-kun! Toyotomi-kun!
Huh?
Akina-chan!
I knew I'd find you here!
What's the matter today?
Look, there's a Yoneyone Club concert today.
Wanna go?
Ya should ask me out!
Actually, I'm also a huge fan
of that Yoyo Circle!
Man, what are the odds?
"In the name of the Father, the Son, the Yo-yo Spirit..."
What are you talking about?!
Akina-san...
I'm sorry, but Toyotomi can't go with you.
How come?
Right now, Toyotomi's this much in the red.
As long as he keeps losing,
there's no way we'll let him out of here.
The law is harsh but it is the law.
Ya don't say! And how much in the red is he? Wut dis?
The Chiba dialect really spread to her too?
Minus 12,000?
Aight! Imma take all that back for ya!
Ya clear off to yonder, bro!
Dumb girl.
She got a bit lucky the other day
so she's getting cocky.
She really thinks she can win against us twice in a row!?
By the way, if Akina-san loses, she can pay off her losses with something other than money...
Really?
I wonder what's that!
She gonna pay with 'er body or something, huh?
Yasu, she can hear you!
Right, right...
Whatcha all goin' about?!
Let's get to it, chop chop!
East 1
Wow! That's a pretty good hand!
Ah, that's a chii!
Huh? Ryanmen chii with a good hand?!
Honitsu, perhaps?
4p!
No... She wouldn't have discarded 7s that early with honitsu.
Dora
I've got a triplet of the dora...
It's got to be just a tanyao sanshoku!
Hayami's wait is obviously 3p kanchan!
This one!
Oh, should I ron it?
A real cheap wait.
Well, let's win this, howzat?
Just shousangen, dealer's mangan.
Wha? If ya'd waited a turn, ya'd've tsumo'd the hatsu!
Wha? No way!
If I cut 3p instead,
I'd get tsumo'd for 16000 all...!?
Aaa! Should've skipped ron!
Toyotomi, you're such an idiot!
Her luck is terrifying...
Guess the girls ain't got the competitive spirit in them.
This is not the time for jokes... If we hesitate now, it'll be the last time all over again.
Get her off the dealer quick!
Ah! Wait a second!
What?!
Impossible!
And here...
Sorting her tiles like that...
Closed chinitsu! Haneman!
Super cheap wait!
I knew it!
Good! Here comes chiitoi dora dora tenpai!
Dora
To aim for Akina, 8p will come out real easy from her!
Wut?!
It was the 2s after all!
The nan's gonna come out for sure!
Wut?!
Pei? Go for this one? W-Wait...
I shan't change anymore!
Not this!
Why is this happening?!
I drew a triplet of dora!
Rooon!
Super expensive wait!
Pinfu ryanpeikou dora dora!
That's it! My life is over!
Nothing but suffering!
A traveler... Why cometh you here?
Rejected by fortune and luck,
I have lost all dreams and hope.
Gaze upon the sea.
When men fix their eyes at the sea
at times like these,
they can lay themselves bare before the sea.
From now on,
I shall live in my memories...
What is this power?
She's cornering us hand by hand!
She's slowly driving us into desperation then methodically deals the final blow.
Moreover, she has no idea she's doing that.
What a blissfully ignorant girl!
Toyotomi  Tokugawa  Akechi
Akina
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
And we ended up 60,000 in the green too!
Really, you guys should've just let me go!
You're still no match for my Akina-chan!
Oh, you, Toyotomi-kun!
Super Zugan.
All right, gentlemen, since you lost, please hurry up to admit it! Don't be shy!
Hey, Toyotomi-kun!
Since we made such a great comeback,
why don't we go eat something nice to celebrate?
It's a deal, then! Sushi and steaks!
And Spanish food!
Oh no! There's no way we can eat all of that!
I guess you're right!
But before that—concert!
Sure!
Damn it all!
I'll remember this...
I'll never forgive them for this humiliation!
Having overcame the long age of darkness Toyotomi finally achieved his wordly happiness.
His heart was as clear as the autumn sky.
However, as far as the happiness goes,
this one was not meant to last either.
Haiku:
Players' deal-in tiles; Gathering them, before long double shadowrealm.
Thank you for listening.
The autumn is almost over,
so maybe it's time for
For you, who had no luck this past year,
Next on Super Zugan:
You are Perfection
Part 1 and Part 2.
Make sure to catch it!
Don't sleep!