Toyotomi Hideyoshi, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba Prefecture.
Oda Shintaro. A one-hit wonder who is ignorant of theory. From Chiba Prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasube. An absolute ignoramus who doesn't know when to stop calling. From Chiba.
Akechi Koichi. The expert in by-the-book calculative and rational playstyle. From Chiba.
Hayami Akina.
Technically Toyotomi's love interest.
Born with incredible luck.
From Chiba Prefecture.
Zenith
Listen up. Hayami's already beat us twice,
but she's also only played us twice.
In the long run, we're certain to win.
Still, I think that girl's luck is the real deal.
The real deal?
Just like how Toyotomi
has a natural Super Zugan,
I feel like that girl's incredible luck is something she was born with.
Hm, I 'spose!
You two are too feeble-minded.
We can lure her to a hotel with the promise of tennis for a mahjong all-nighter.
I call it: Operation Seductive Anglerfish!
You are Perfection      Episode 5
There! I'm starting!
There... Unlucky.
Really, you can't hit back for toffee!
Why do we need to invite Toyotomi too?
There's no helping it. Didn't ya hear that wherever Toyotomi goes, Hayami goes?
He still haven't got a clue!
Okamoto Fuyuki's clueless like always!
Right! Takada Kaiko's pretty dumb too!
Let's take a peek...
Gulp...
Shh!
Well, but it's still pretty hard!
These grade schoolers
are getting smart lately!
Yes, as expected the class representative is doing his best!
Sorry for the wait!
Oh, that was so fast!
A-All right, let’s dive into the action, then!
Hey, me too, me too!
Who ever said we were gonna play with you?
We came here today
to play mahjong with Akina-chan.
Just because Hayami dragged you along doesn't mean you get to act all cocky!
H-How come...?
It's fine! Let's all just play together, okay?
So be it. Want to draw for who skips?
Whoever draws the 1m sits out first, and then in order, all right?
4m.
2m.
3m.
1m!
One thing that never changes is your crappy draws!
Unlucky...
Riichi!
A fast hand like always...
Chii!
Genbutsu!
Aww, I didn't tsumo.
Good wall shift!
4p?
She might have tsumo'd...
Aight! Tsumo only. 400/700.
Aww! I had such a good wait too...
Dora
If Shintaro had drawn 8p or 9p, the 7p'd have come out.
He's right! If I didn't call, she'd get 4p for ippatsu tsumo!
She'd win a haneman!
East 2
Riichi!
Dora
Wh-What's with this girl?!
Out of nowhere on the third turn...
It's tanpin sanshoku if I stay closed...
No, I have to.
7p chii!
Dammit. I called a completed group...
No ippatsu? Fine, then.
7m.
If I didn't go for it, it'd be Hayami's draw...
I made it!
C'mon, tsumo!
Tsumo! 500/1000!
Aww... I had such an expensive hand...
The hell's that?!
Getting ippatsu tsumo on a fucking 7m penchan?!
Just how strong is her luck, really?
No... Need to calm down now.
I already stopped her short of haneman twice.
Even her luck is not perfect.
Riichi!
Just as I assume that her luck ebbed,
she riichis on turn 2?!?
What's worse, I can't call it...
Call it, Shintaro!
Uh-oh, I drew already!
Let him call! Otherwise she's definitely gonna tsumo!
All right! Yasu, call it!
Wut? How the hell am I supposed to call with this kokushi?!
Ah!
Riichi hatsu ippatsu tsumo!
Worst ever!
All right, my dealer turn now!
You two! Get her off the dealer even if it kills ya!
Got it!
Hm?
Double riichi!
S-Somebody call this! Call!
How can you say dumb shit like that
when I can't even call your tile?!
Call this!
What about this!?
Call it, whatever the cost!
We're screwed.
It's over.
Let's start preparing the point sticks...
6000 should be enough, right?
All— Huh?
No ippatsu?
That's right! There's no way she can tsumo ippatsu every time!
She had me worried for a sec there!
Look at these guys! You can feel a fresh surge of hope in the air!
Whoa! Second draw tsumo!
Ah! The uradora is 3m!
Double riichi tsumo menhon chun sanankou ura ura!
6000 all wasn't enough...
What's this? Ya'd've gotten ippatsu tsumo with the 7m!
What? No way!
Wait:
She missed an ippatsu tsumo dealer's baiman and got a sanbaiman anyway?!?!
However, this girl started
by calling riichi on turn 4...
Turn 3, turn 2, double riichi, her tenpai got faster every time...
Which means that the next one is...!
Yay! I already won at the start! Bo-ring!
Tenhou...
That means there's no point in going for anything other than the fastest tenpai now!
Riichi! It's cheap, somebody deal in!
It's just a riichi nomi!
Hold up! Arentcha lying to us so ya can get second place?!
Idiot! It's not the time to think about that!
Oh, it came out! That's my winning tile!
A bit of a waste, but 9600.
Well at least we know
who's gonna be last now.
Now you've done it...
Aight, second place, let's go!
Ron!
Wh-Whaaat?!
Pinfu sanshoku dora dora! 8000! Eat this!
Y-Y-Ya were aimin' for me?! For me?!
Until now, these three friends' teamwork had been based
Friendship
on the great assumption that they wouldn't steal points from each other.
Now, this strong bond was broken.
I'll get my renchan whatever it takes!
Ron! Gimme my 1000!
This bastard... Breaking off my last dealer turn with his shitty 1000!
Here, choke on it!
That hurt!
Hey! That wasn’t a very polite way to pass the stick according to mahjong etiquette!
Oh, really?
My bad then!
"Your bad" doesn't change that it hurt!
Hold on! Is now really the right time for you two to start infighting?
Right now, interrupting Hayami's luck is the highest priority.
Tsk. Well, I guess Shintaro's right. Whatever...
It's out! Junchan sanshoku dora dora!
Huh?! You had it?!
What a dumbass!
Should've checked the discards!
Hey! Have your fucking point sticks!
The hell didja just do, you mutt?!
Shut up! I never liked you in the first place, you cigarette-sucking jerk!
Stop it, both of you!
What's your problem?!
Ow! That hurt!
Next game is your turn to sit out, so piss off!
Now you've done it!
If they keep fighting like this,
maybe I can even win!
No! I'm certainly going to win!
I'm going to finish the next hanchan 3rd, no matter the cose!
You can do it, Toyotomi!
Oda's terrifying Operation Seducing Anglerfish
collapsed quickly in the face of Akina's impossible luck.
However, the struggle is far from over.
The unsuspecting Akina remains oblivious
as the sinister clutches of Toyotomi's supreme lucklessness creep ever closer.
South 2, East seat, turn 8, 18900 points Tsumo: 3m Dora: West
>muh sanshoku
ngmi
All right...!
Boring... My turn to sit out, huh?
Oh!
Dora
You Are Perfection     Episode 5
Even Akechi, who's normally so collected,
just spurted noodles out of his nose!
Does that mean Hayami's haipai is really that impressive?
I'll chii that right away!
Dora
Sanshoku dora 1 iishanten.
Hey, nice call!
Chii!
Dora
All right, I'm in tenpai!
Wow, pretty!
36p shousuushii tenpai...
Our style-conscious Akechi is so dumbfounded,
he’s got a shrimp hanging from his nose!
Is she in tenpai?!
I did it! Turn 3 tenpai with possible pinfu! Superb!
3p!
Ah! It came out...
I won't ron it.
Toyotomi looks so happy,
I don't want to throw him so deep into the shadowrealm right away...
Relax. If it's 36p, I can easily tsumo it!
Uh?! She drew it?!
Something's wrong...
There's definitely something...
5p, huh...
Those discards, letting me call 2s and 2p...
5p should pass.
Wh-What is this sudden chill?!
It's gonna be like a pinzu chinitsu or something...
Yes, it has to be that.
What a perceptive bastard!
Phew, tsumogiri.
My shousuushii that was only 48k just became a quadruple yakuman worth 192k...
If I ron him now after skipping earlier, he'd feel even more miserable...
What does it matter to you how that moron feels?!
Just ron him, ron him!
Whatever, I'll just draw!
Impossible!
Tch, the 5p passed, huh?!
Ah...
Ah! Shintaro-kun's still got a white!
Since he cut one earlier, it'll come out next turn for sure!
Let's see! Tsumogiri!
How can he be always that luckless?
But since I can ron Shintaro's white with a yamagoshi trap, I'll skip ron!
C'mon! Drop the white!
It came out!
8m ron!
No!
You can't!
Ron! Ron! Ron-ron! Ron! Ron!
No! No! No-no-no! No! No!
Don't ron me, okay? Please!
Toyotomi-kun...
Guess I have no choice...
Wow, you're so sweet!
I love you, Toyotomi-kun!
Yeah, dream about it!
Ron! Pinfu only!
Mahjong is a cruel game, baby.
To-Toyotomi-kun, you idiot!
Whew, Toyotomi, you're such a cruel guy.
Ya made poor Akina-chan cry.
What's her deal? It's just 1000 points!
Is she making fun of me?
She thinks she can never deal in herself?
How arrogant!
Toyotomi, lemme tell you...
Akechi, ya still got a noodle sticking from your nose.
I'll have ya know that Akina-chan...
It's fine, Akechi-kun.
I'm sorry. Let's continue.
Tsk! Girls are such a bother sometimes! C'mon!
Ron! Tanyao iipeikou dora dora!
Dora
Unlucky!
That was fast!
It's only turn 6!
Serious, if you got a mangan,
at least pretend you're happy!
Ron! Pinfu sanshoku dora 1!
Zugan!
Haitei dora dora!
Zugaaan!
Riichi menhon nan sanankou!
Zugan!
Honroutou shousangen!
She's totally focusing on Toyotomi alone!
It's revenge! This is her revenge!
I didn't win a single hand 'cuz ya kept dealing in, ya gull!
Enough is enough!
Even if it's just a drop in the bucket,
I have to get back some points in all last!
Pon!
Chii!
Naked
tanki!
Naked tanki!
Make sure ya don't catch a cold, bro!
I'mma open riichi!
Riichi!
It's a 25p wait riichi, boys.
What's that?
There are three of each already out!
Still two left. Now check Toyotomi get them!
Well, someone's got to have them in hand...
I feel like I'm gonna draw them...
Super Zugan!
Looks like he drew it for real!
He dropped the dora from his hand!
Whoa, this one's still live!
Pon!
I'mma tsumo! Ah, whatever!
Please... Don't be 5p...
Right on...
Pon!
D-Don't tell me...
ZUGAN
What's wrong?
A-Akina-chan...
What is it?
S-Sorry for ronning you for 1000 earlier...
T-That wasn't very considerate on my part, I regret it now...
Oh, no need to apologize for that!
I have already com—
Completely forgotten about it!
It's fine now, so just discard!
That’s the face of someone
who hasn’t forgotten.
More like of someone determined to take revenge.
Ciao!
Ron!
Daisuushii tsuuiisou!
Zu—
gaan!
Triple yakuman!
If ya cut 2p, it'd be just a single yakuman, what an imbecile!
Zugan!
Thanks to Toyotomi playing,
we still somehow broke even.
It was really fun, guys!
We should all do that again sometime!
Yeah!
What are you so excited about, Toyotomi-kun?
Huh?
Nobody said we'll bring you along.
Without Toyotomi,
we'd be the only chronic losers.
Yes, exactly!
Um, Hayami-kun, could you go back on that
and let Toyotomi-kun in too?
All right! Now then, why don't we get going?
Um, what about me?
Since you're the only one who lost,
you will walk home as a punishment!
No way!
Akina-chan...
At last, even Akina has given Toyotomi the cold shoulder.
This cold rain pouring down
on the autumn day...
Could it actually be the tears flowing from his frozen heart?
Don't try to stop him, mother.
Where will Toyotomi go as a man?
Next time we'll meet that mysterious man Baba-san with thick lips.
And also another mysterious young man from Kansai.
And then we'll go to the hot springs!
Next on Super Zugan:
Object X From Osaka
and Hot Water Zugan.
Don't miss it!
Sleep is for the weak!