Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Episode 19 Part 1
South Pole Zugan
This is Souzu!
Heisei Base, please respond!
What was that?!
Which means the Souzu
can't advance any further?
Understood. Then wait for the weather to improve and dispatch a helicopter.
End of transmission.
You've all heard it, people.
We won't be able to get out of here
any time soon?
Yeah. Until the helicopter arrives,
we'll just have to wait.
There is one problem.
What is it?
There are five of us in this
First Antarctic Wintering Expedition.
However, the helicopter can only seat four.
And in this adverse weather, only God knows if the helicopter can make two round trips.
In other words...
One of us will have to be left behind?
I should be able to beat this guy...
Well, in any case, he's no threat...
All right! I'll say it again!
The game's South Pole rules, south round only!
One dealer turn for each of you and it's done.
I'm the captain, so I'll be the first to get in the chopper. That's the rule.
SOUTH 1
All right. I'm the starting dealer.
Chii!
Ryanmen chii on turn 5? Does he have an anko of the Dora chun?
8s!
Ron! Tanyao, 1,000!
Spending the Antarctic winter
alone gonna be cold!
Asshole! Screwing over my dealer turn
with his fucking 1,000!
SOUTH 2
Pon!
I can't cut this hatsu against toitoi...
This one!
Oops, sorry!
South only, 1,000!
Have fun looking at the aurora by yourself!
Bastard...
SOUTH 3
I've paid him back!
Ron! Pinfu only, 1,000!
Wow! Sanmenchan Dama? Sub-zero!
ALL LAST
Man... What's this haipai...
I'll pon that!
If Yasu tsumos, I get away with 3rd place!
He's clearly still in iishanten!
I'll let him call the tiles he needs!
Call it!
Wut, it came out? Chun only, 1,000!
Zugan!
Tied for last place...
What?! The helicopter can seat six?
Whoa, what a godsend!
So you're saying there was even
a free spot all along?!
Thank god! You were making me all so worried, you...
IN THE MEANTIME...
That's right, I'd forgotten all about you!
Toyotomi will finally come home
the day after tomorrow!
That's right! The day after tomorrow, let's make
Toyotomi-kun's favorite duck hotpot!
Ridiculous. With dogs as opponents, the outcome should be obvious.
You blowhard!
What kind of pon is that?! You!
Actually, the dog brothers Taro and Jiro
were able to telepathically communicate
the tiles they needed.
DORA
Ugh, I can't believe we're letting him call the dora...
I can't stand dealing with dogs...
Taro is clearly going for a Manzu Chinitsu...
But there's no way I'd lose to a dog!
Baba Hirokazu, 24 years old,
born in Ikebukuro
All right! This is great, as long as I don't deal in, Baba will be last!
B-But I don't have any safe tiles!
In this ruleset, it's totally possible that he has a suji trap on 8p...
The 4s matagi is the most dangerous...
So I'll trust the kabe of 4m...
There's no way he has a manzu wait!
Riichi ippatsu honitsu ittsuu, haneman?!
Now I'm tied with Baba!
But, I'm still only tied with him.
I'm still not guaranteed to be 4th.
Ura dora?! Baiman?!
Zugan!
Zugan...
Are you Toyotomi's family?
You're the members
of the Antartic expedition, aren't you?
This time, he...
Why?
Miss...
This guy would make
for a great substitute luckless feeder.
Oh, is that so?
Ron! Riichi tanyao pinfu ippatsu iipeikou dora dora!
Zugan!
It's true! He gets bad draws and he deals in a lot, he's great to play against!
I know, right?
Then, let's play another hanchan!
Zugan!
A year later,
Oda and the others sailed to Antarctica again for the second wintering expedition.
Shin-san, do you think
Toyotomi's still alive?
I don't know...
But, if he still is...
If he still is?
Wh-What the hell happened here?
This is serious...
OBSERVATION JOURNAL
December 21st: I'm cold
December 23rd: I'm starving
December 25th: I'm tired
He's frozen into the Antarctic ice by now!
Probably
I hear something!
Over here, guys!
Sh-Shin-san! Look!
Wut the...
Toyotomi!
That weasel! He's playing mahjong
for fish against goddamn penguins!
That's how he survived!
Toyotomi!
IOU
Ah! The bastard's making a run for it!
Let's get him!
IOU
Asshole, who're you taking us for?!
Zugan!
Stop!
To all those who sleep alone,
please take care of yourselves.
I've caught a cold, damn it...
"Extremely popular mangaka Hatayama Masayuki's luxury villa?"
Ah, that was refreshing!
Hey, wanna go for a swim too, Toyotomi?
I actually prefer watching you swim
than swimming myself, you know.
Anyway, I didn't know you had such talent, Toyotomi!
Turning your own lucklessness into the "Ultra Zugan" manga,
and just like that, you're a millionaire!
Episode 19 Part 2
Nouveau Riche Zugan
Boss!
There are guests to see you.
Hm? Who?
Well, they're three odd blokes
who say they're old friends of yours...
Saying:
"Ultra Zugan is modeled after us!"
"Give us our royalties!"
"Wuh! Wuh!"
And making a fuss about
other such nonsensical things.
So they've come?
I don't care.
Drive them away.
All right, mates, boss's busy.
Why don't you come another time?
Fuck! He's gonna turn us away at the gate?!
That dick, claiming
all the fortunes for himself?!
Give it to me too! Share some of your fortune with me too, yeah!
Toyotomi-kun, are you sure you should send them away?
More importantly,
I've got a present for you.
Wow, it's wonderful!
Thank you so much!
Boss.
I'm so happy, Toyotomi-kun! I love you!
Boss!
What is it?
You've got another guest.
Again? Just send them away already!
But, boss, she's a girl fans of you,
college student it seems.
Pretty busty too.
Akina-chan, it turns out
I've got some business.
See you later. Take it easy.
Hey, thanks for coming!
Ah, nice to meet you.
My name is Satomi.
I'm a big fan of your works!
I'm the Toyotomi Hideyuki!
Ah! He shook my hand!
Actually, since you're here,
why don't I show you where I work?
Wow, I'd be delighted!
Sorry for intruding!
Oh?
But there's no desk for you to work on...
That's because I...
Do my job like this!
Why don't you stop resisting...
Don't touch me!
Come on, come on!
Bank balance 70,000,000 yen?!
Have your way with me...
The old savings book trick always works!
A-Akina, it's not what it—
You animal!
Ah! Akina-chan!
Akina-chan! Wait! Akina-chan!
Hello!
I'm Yukari!
I'm Eriko!
And you are...?
Satomi's friends!
We were planning
to come together, but...
No good, you're late!
Sorry!
Our train was a bit late!
You know, that guy's got 70,000,000 yen in savings...
Wow, no way!
And it's well known he's bad at mahjong!
Uh, Maestro?
Would you have some time?
What for?
Wanna play some mahjong?
Mahjong?!
Sure, but...
But...?
My body can't take
regular mahjong anymore...
Are you okay with that?
Wh-What do you mean?
In my mahjong...
The one who dealt in, even for just 1,000 points, must take off a piece of clothing...
Strip mahjong!
Kyah! Sounds like fun!
I'm first dealer!
Gotta do your best!
Now...
All right, let's go! Chop chop!
They're such naïve and good girls,
and my haipai's good too!
3p.
Chii!
Don't need chun!
Hatsu!
Pon!
Don't even need any shousangen!
Ron! Hatsu only!
All right, now strip!
Oh no!
Oh geez...
Success!
Hey, miss...
You really cut that one, huh?
Ron! Chun only! Now strip!
Oh no, not again!
Oh my...
9s!
Ron!
No way!
Cheapest out, pinfu only missing tanyao and sanshoku, now strip!
C'mon, with that you'd skip the 9s...
Ron, iipeikou only! Now strip!
Ron, ton only! Now strip!
Ron, riichi nomi, now strip!
Ron, chun only! Ron, nan only! Ron, riichi only!
Ron, pinfu only! Ron, just ron!
Oh no, we've been tricked!
This guy is actually good!
So weird!
Now, I've got you cornered!
SOUTH 1 EAST SEAT TURN 8
Got it!
Superb!
In this hand, you would normally cut 6m and go for 234 sanshoku using the 4m...
But right now, I don't need a high score.
DORA
C'mon, I've got a 2369m wait, cut it already!
My wish is merely ron.
Just tanyao, waiting on 36p!
Ah! How can he be so lucky?
Well, who'll be the first to bare
her cute boob for me?
Yukari-chan?
Or Eriko-chan?
Or Satomi-chan after all?
Maestro? it's your turn!
Zugan!
I tsumo'd...
That's no fun at all!
I've got to cut my 6m head and change my wait!
It came out! Ron! Chun honitsu dora 1, mangan!
Zugan!
You rock, Satomi!
You're a genius!
Yay!
Zugan!
My luck's run out!
K-Kokushi musou tenpai!
Dama...
Dammit, it won't come...
Ugh?!
I-I tsumo'd...
Shit, why are my draws so good tonight?
Should I just tsumo?
No.
With just a little more effort...
I can taste those sweet, enticing fruits!
And for kokushi,
furiten applies only to genbutsu.
All I seek here is a wonderful man's romance...
Cut 1m!
Ron! Pinfu only!
Ron! Pinfu iipeikou!
Ron! Chanta chiitoitsu!
Zugan!
Now, because it's triple ron,
take off everything—your pants and underpants!
That's right!
N-No... No!
Strip him!
Ah! Anything but that!
Satomi-chan,
next hanchan, let's bet this house!
Z-Zuga—AAAA!
Thus, Toyotomi died.
Wh-What's that, you guys?!
Hey, Toyotomi! Just woke up?
We were just deciding seats.
Get on with it, come on!
Phew... It was just a dream...
Tsumogiri...
Ron! Pinfu dora 3!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu iipeikou!
Chanta chiitoitsu!
Zugan...
Toyotomi-kun?
Isn't it you, Toyotomi-kun?
Toyotomi-kun!
A-Akina-chan...
Won't you buy some matches, Akina-chan?
In the end, you were defeated by those girls and lost even your mansion, didn't you?
Akina-san.
Kenjin-san?
I can't let ya be
that poor bugger's missus.
Ya'll catch the poors from him.
Kenjin...
Is this how you treat your boss...
Buy yourself a pasty, mate.
Let's go. We'll be late to the party.
O-Okay.
"Is the dream truth,
or is truth but a dream?"
"Life is truly but a butterfly's dream."
"The proud do not endure [...] reveals the truth that the prosperous must decline."
"In nothing but idleness, I have spent my days before this inkstone [...]"
"In spring, dawn [is best]."
Zugan...!
Have you seen him?
The mahjong demon undefeated for 20 years: Sakurada Mongai!
Why do three pros have to enter the local parlor's tourney again?!
Next time on Super Zugan:
"Undefeated! The Legendary Mahjong Demon"
and "Whose Will Be the Glory...?"
Don't miss it!
Don't want to you to sleep on it!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Raw provider
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa