Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
It's finally here!
The day when maidens bashfully confess their true love to their sweetheart!
The yearly ultra big event!
Valentine's Day!
Episode 17 Part 1
My Zugan Valentine
I hope I'll get heaps of chockie this year!
Hey!
So, how many did you get last year?
Last year's last year, righto?
So, zero.
S-Stop making fun of me!
And besides, how many chockies
did you get, mate?
Ron!
Chiitoi. And yes, I did get chocolate from 7 girls.
I only got some from my Megumi.
Ron! Sanankou Dora 1, Hatsu Hell Wait!
I got chocolate from Tomomi, Junko, Rie, Masako...
About 13 girls!
N-No way!
Ron! Kokushi! 13-sided wait!
Toyotomi! How many did you get?
Zero.
Right-oh!
As expected of me boss!
Let's both do our best this year!
Happy Valentine's Day!
Hey, Akina-chan!
Here, Toyotomi, my homemade chocolate!
Ah! Thanks!
B-Boss...
And storebought one for the rest!
Here.
Oh, thanks.
Thank you!
I can feel Hayami's love!
Dem lollies're for ladies 'n' ankle biters...
So did ya bring one for me too?
Oh?
Sorry, I bought one too few!
You have too little screentime.
As if, you broad!
Just ya watch!
I'll get a ladyfriend and chockie today!
Damned if I don't!
I'll show them all why they nicknamed me the number one pickup artist!
Oi, babe! How 'bout some tea 'n' bickies over there?!
No!
Oi, sheila! How 'bout—
Are you kidding me?!
Oi, sheila, tea...
Get lost!
Crikey!
These Tokyo sheilas don't know what a true blue bloke I am!
Hurrying, hurrying.
Hey lady, let's talk!
Shan't let ya escape! I was my middle school's sprint champion!
And I was known as the best runner of Kamakura High School!
She's from Kamakura?!
Good onya, sheila.
Yes, you too...
I think we'll make a ripper couple.
I suppose...
This is my boss's house.
No worries, you can come in.
What, that sponger again?
And we thought ya wouldn't be comin' back...
Oh? Who is that?
My mate.
Nice to meet you! I'm Asami.
Please, help yourselves!
Oh, what a nice girl!
She's too good for ya!
Can I brew some tea?
Ah... Don't worry, I'll do it.
You can sit down
with Kenjin-kun, Asami-chan.
Hold it! I shan't let me boss's ladyfriend do such a thing!
Hey! Make mine real thick and steamy!
Thick and steamy my ass!
You barely know her, you sick fuck!
Well, I guess I'll brew it myself.
It's fine, you can sit down, Kenjin-san.
No, I'll do—
No, I'll—
I...
I'll do it!
No, I'll do it!
Asami-chan...
Kenjin-san...
I don't care who does it,
but get on with it!
Right-o!
Can you swap two players out so I can join?
Sure! Come on in.
I like it more when there's two fish rather than one.
Fish?
You mean me?
You're a funny guy!
The tea is ready!
Th-They did it...
Nice combination...
They're a match made in heaven for sure...
Now that I have a ladyfriend,
there's no one here who can beat me!
Sorry, I need you to be here for a sec.
Now, there's really no one in this room who can beat me!
Come on...
You're joking, right?
We'll see about that!
Now watch my playstyle.
Dora
8m or 1p, which should I cut?
Obvious dama, and go for the dama junchan sanshoku dora 1 haneman on 7m.
Dora
Nice! Here comes the skill of a man who got 7 chocolates last year!
Pick one nice and smooth...
Riichi!
Zugan! If I knew it was gonna come out,
I should have called riichi!
I'll pon that dora!
I'll riichi then!
2s!
9s!
3s!
If it won't come out... I'll tsumo it!
Ron!
Riichi tanyao pinfu ura 1!
Toitoi dora 3! Superb!
Zugan! Double ron!
See. That's all skill.
I don't know how to play mahjong!
What's that?
Zugaaan...
Wow, so cute!
What are these flowers?
M'lady, they're called the Luckless Flowers...
They bloom in my heart whenever the frustration becomes unbearable...
They're so pretty! Can I pick them?
Go ahead, they'll bloom plenty more so it's fine!
As if I'll let you!
Chiin!
Pon!
Tsumo
The 8m...
Oh man...
Tsumo
Oi, mate! Discard quick!
The time is not yours to waste.
What?!
Then try ronning this tile, you fake!
Mate, yer back's gonna be
a real flower bed.
Ron! Chinitsu.
Zugan!
Wow, so pretty!
I'll put some on Ken-san too!
Hey, that ain't right!
But why, when they're so pretty?
Riichi!
Dora
I drew the last 3m!
14m are the dora suji, and a great wait!
Dora
Should I cut 4p and go for an iishanten accepting 36p58s14m?
Or cut 8s and accept 1245m2356p?
Dora
No! 4p and 8s are both risky!
I'll fold and...
Discard genbutsu for acceptance of 58s25m25p!
Crikey! I drew the dora!
But no worries mate, I'll cut 5m!
Crikey! I should have made 8s my head and dropped 67s!
Then I'd have won off of that 2p!
The hell ya on about?
It's over...
Dora
Whoa...
This is...
Dora
Ron! Riichi hatsu ura ura!
Crikey! I've been infected
by boss's lucklessness!
Ron! Baiman!
Ron! Dealer's haneman!
I can do better! Tsumo! Suuankou!
Double super zugan!
Well, we're off to go get our own chocolates.
It was tasty!
Have fun with the ladies!
Zugan!
All right, I'll be heading home too!
It was fun!
W-Wait, Asami-san...
Huh?
Are ya...
Are ya gonna leave me behind all buggered like this?
Huh?
Asami-san... Did you really not love me
even for a moment?!
No, I love you. So...
So...
Let's just be good friends forever!
Th-Those words are...
Bye!
Zugan.
She dealt the finishing blow...
"Let's just be friends forever."
That was the end of Kenjin.
First
Building
Episode 17 Part 2
Akina Triangle
I see. Chun pon!
Episode 17 Part 2
Akina Triangle
Now I'm tenpai for
Chun Chanta Sanshoku Dora 1!
Dora
Ron! Dealer's mangan!
I've got good flow today!
Oi, boss!
Ya got heaps good flow today!
But he shouldn't get too carried away...
Welcome!
What's cooking, Mama-san?
That's Sanjouin Kimimaro!
Wow! The crown prince of Sanjouin Group—
the kingpin of the Japanese economy!
Ah... Welcome!
Is there a free seat?
Crown prince coming to the municipal parlor—
talk about being fed from a silver spoon.
Toyotomi-kun!
You're a funny guy.
Well then, can I join your table?
You all right, Mama-san?!
EAST 1   STARTING DEALER: SANJOUIN
I'll show this greenhorn
the rough seas of the real world!
Well then, East 1...
Let's start with a dealer's mangan.
Sanjouin-san is famous for announcing his score beforehand, and then winning with it!
What?! Well, we've got Babe Ruth too!
C'mon!
Pon!
Tch, double ton?
I've got a good hand too!
Cut dora before it's too late!
Dora pon!
Boss, ya shouldn't let him call all that!
Don't whine about things
that can't be helped!
All right, riichi!
Let's go! Riichi Shaa Honitsu Iipeikou! If I Ippatsu Tsumo the Hatsu, it's Baiman!
I won't let anyone stop my ippatsu!
So cold!
Ron! Double east dora 3, that's 12,000.
Zuga-
No, not so fast!
Let's win 5,800 from toimen now, shall we?
Boss!
Ron! Dealer's 60 fu sanankou,
5,800 plus 1 honba.
Zugan!
Senpai!
Cheers!
It's been such a long time
since we've last dined like this.
Indeed.
I was on exchange in London,
so it's been about two years.
You've become a real lady in the meantime.
No way, senpai!
There's something
I'd like to give to you today.
Th-This is...
A memento of our reunion.
Something so fancy...
I can't accept it.
Eh?!
N-No way, you already have someone else?
Yes.
Materia
Right, t here's something
I'd like to give to you today.
Here!
Kya! No way, three months'
worth of your salary?
What's this?
Seriously? That's so unlike you! It's basalt!
Fiddlesticks!
I'll never give up!
Man, it's cold!
Kotatsu's the best when it's cold!
Coming!
Go see who's that.
Wassat you're saying?!
You're the boss, and this is your place,
so you should be dealin' with yer guests!
Look, you...
C'mon, what's going on?
Akina-chan!
Y-You...!
Well, well, we meet again.
I'd never have thought
you were that Toyotomi-kun.
Are you really in love with Hayami-kun?!
Wh-Wha...
I love her!
Wh-What?!
I've graduated from Oxford,
work at Sanjouin Group,
and at age 24 already make over 80 million yen per year!
On top of that, I'm 188 cm tall
and good-looking!
However, Hayami-kun still wants to choose you over me.
Eh? She really does?
Boss! This ain't the time to be laughing like nothing happened!
But I still don't consider you
a match for Hayami-kun!
What?!
You heard me right.
I'll fight you at mahjong once again!
If you can beat me,
I'll be a good sport and step aside!
What do you say?
Hold it, Hayami-san!
Life is always a gamble!
Whatever's the thing—if you win, flowers!
If you lose and fall, the mud!
N-No way...
That's right... The only field where I
have a chance against other men is mahjong!
Riichi!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu chiitoi ura ura!
But I'm also so bad at mahjong!
Toyotomi-kun, it's just started...
Don't give up!
Kan!
Dora
Tanyao dora 3 straight away!
2m is dora, 4p is the dora indicator...
This shanpon won't come out.
If I cut 4p, the 369p is furiten.
All right...
Won't take furiten!
Boss, I'll help ya.
If he can't call anything in pinzu, he's buggered.
Try callin' it, mate!
The 8p you just cut!
Chii!
Crikey, what's that call?!
Wait
Riichi!
Tsumo! Mangan.
Horrible!
My luck is even worse than normal!
Boss! You can't lose your spirits and give up!
All right, surely this riichi will win!
You just don't get it, do you?
C'mon! Please! Dora!
She's trying to deal in!
Hayami-san was really
on boss's side after all!
This is Hayami's answer!
Why won't you ron her
if she loves you this much?!
Wait
You just said why!
Ron! Honitsu haku.
Thank you, Hayami-kun.
I can feel your love!
Cunt! I'll bugger ya up!
Lessgo!
Pon!
Tsumo 3s! Crikey...
Tsumogiri!
Boss! Why did ya call that
and flog my tsumo?
That's a ripper draw! Good on me!
Wait
She'll be right now,
closed chinitsu 259s wait!
Wait
9s!
Crikey! I won't ron ya, boss!
Aight, I'll tsumogiri and riichi!
Fine! This passed last turn!
Boss! A bloody pair drop!
Riichi ippatsu chinitsu, baiman!
Zugan!
Hayami-kun, what's there even to like about this guy?
All people get unlucky sometimes.
He's in a bad spot now.
But Senpai, when you hit a rough patch,
can you make such beautiful and colorful flowers bloom?
Wh-What did you say?
Ron! Best out riichi pinfu ittsuu!
You've been the ace hitter since forever,
senpai, and you're amazing.
But people who've always been sidelined on the bench
and still never gave up
are even more admirable!
They're beautiful...
I-I see...
I never knew flowers growing forgotten by the wayside could be so valiant and beautiful...
Sanjouin-senpai...
I lost.
You've showed me something so beautiful...
But I still won't give up!
If I also can make such flowers bloom, then for sure...
For sure, I can outshine you...
D-Did you just give up?
Ah! Did they know the feelings that dwelt in their hearts, or not?
The Luckless Flowers
said nothing and bloomed in silence.
Working at a mahjong parlor is hard work!
You have to fill in for customers and teach them manners!
I wonder if Toyotomi-kun can do that?
Next time on Super Zugan:
"Welcome to the Mahjungle"
and "Mahjong Rules 101."
Don't miss it!
Don't want to you to sleep on it!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Raw provider
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa