Toyotomi Hideyoshi, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba Prefecture.
Oda Shintaro. A one-hit wonder who is ignorant of theory. From Chiba Prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasube. An absolute ignoramus who doesn't know when to stop calling. From Chiba.
Akechi Koichi. The expert in by-the-book calculative and rational playstyle. From Chiba.
Hayami Akina.
Technically Toyotomi's love interest.
Born with incredible luck.
From Chiba Prefecture.
Yes?
Who is it?
Toyotomi-kun!
Zu... ga... n.
Episode 3 Part 1
The Toyotomi Machine of Terror
You lost against those three at mahjong again, didn't you?
Zugan.
I've made a mistake.
Luckless.
I told you to quit mahjong, but in the end,
that'd just mean running away from the problem.
If you give up on a sour note, you’ll carry the label of a loser for the rest of your days!
Luckless?
So you’ve gotta hit back at them with everything you’ve got, like a real man!
Huh?
A-Are those the famous...
Luckless flowers?
Luckless...
Toyotomi-kun, come with me for a second.
Where are we?
My friend Ide-san is a mahjong pro,
and this is his dojo!
Hey, Hayami-kun!
Long time no see.
Is this Toyotomi-kun who needs the special training
from me, the University of Tokyo graduate?
Yes! Please be nice to him!
Huh? No, wait. Uh...
Got it.
As the University of Tokyo graduate, I’ll do everything in my power
University                                                                   of Tokyo
to turn Toyotomi-kun into the strongest, unbeatable mahjong player.
No! I don't wanna! Akina-chan! What the...
Ide's
Mahjong
Dojo
Do your best, Toyotomi!
What is this room?
I may not mentioned it before, but actually, I've graduated from the University of Tokyo.
I've heard that three times already!
University of Tokyo
As a University of Tokyo programming graduate,
I’ll now teach you the basics of computer mahjong.
Seriously? Isn't it just a mahjong video game?
Indeed, until now, there's been heaps of so-called "mahjong video games."
Perfect Mahjong from the University of Tokyo Genius Ide
Planning: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
Direction: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
Programming: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
Supervision: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
However, none of them are able to recreate mahjong's artistic and theoretical qualities.
Characters: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
Music: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
Choreography: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
Scenario: Ide, University of Tokyo graduate
That's because they're made by a bunch of poorly educated country bumpkins
who just popped out of school!
I like strip mahjong though...
Idiot! That's why you're so bad at mahjong!
And I, a University of Tokyo graduate, am always right!
All right! I'll play it!
Hmm... Like he said,
it seems pretty serious.
All right, let's win this! The dealer is my toimen, Ide-pro, huh...
I have two dora.
That's a decent hand!
Dora
Huh?
Tenhou ryuuiisou!
Zugaaan...
What the hell is this game?
As a University of Tokyo graduate, I must always be perfect, even within the computer!
It's quite a shitty game though!
Tenhou chuuren poutou!
Zugaaan!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo daisangen!
Dammit... He's done it 2627 times straight since last night...
All right. Let's move on to the second stage of training!
Huh?
What is it this time?
This is psyche strengthening machine, invented by me, the University of Tokyo graduate!
Psyche strengthening machine?!
This'll let you experience
the virtual reality mahjong.
You're going to keep watching these images without blinking.
You left me no choice!
As you watch, your psychic state
will be displayed here as a waveform.
Let us begin, then.
Ron! Mentanpin sanshoku iipeikou!
Zugan!
What you're sitting on is an electric chair, through which a million volts of electric current
will flow whenever your mental state becomes disturbed.
H-How much?!
To avoid getting fried, keep your psychic waves under control.
Without a strong psyche,
there is no victory in mahjong!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Ippatsu tsumo!
Yakuman!
Zugaaaaan!
Ron!
Good, it's a success.
One month later
Toyotomi-kun!
You did it, Toyotomi-kun!
You did really well enduring all that at Ide-san's place for a whole month!
Toyotomi-kun?
It's no use talking to him now.
Inside his mind, all that matters is winning at mahjong, and he won't respond to anything else.
Huh!?
He's a machine.
Setting aside trivial emotions, he can steadily advance his hand with composure and logic.
He has been reborn as a mahjong-playing machine.
I didn't ask you
to change his personality!
It's all for the victory.
The one who has made the greatest sacrifices will ultimately emerge as the winner!
That's unreasonable...
I'm from the University of Tokyo!
Mahjong
Parlor
Booby
Trap
Let's roll.
What? That's some nerve you got to challenge us.
Hey, the look in his eyes is different from usual.
Didja catch conjunctivitis or something?
Ah! They're starting!
I'm from the University of Tokyo.
How is he sorting his tiles so fast?!
Dora
This hand...
To aim thoroughly for 567 sanshoku, discard 4s.
However, the disadvantage of ending up with a bad wait is too big.
Discard 5m to lock in 678. This is the widest hand.
Even if I draw 5p, I can discard 5s and expect mangan with riichi on the dora suji.
Finally, there is discarding 5s, but this makes the hand extremely narrow if I draw 58p or 36s.
On the other hand, it leaves both kinds of sanshoku feasible.
However, if I draw 8s and try to go for 678 sanshoku, it's one move slower.
That being said, here discarding from the 5s anko early is the optimal move.
Huh? He discarded 5s?
Relax. He's a machine.
Between drawing a tile and discarding, he calculates through a million possibilities
in just 0.5 seconds.
And then he makes the best possible move.
Toyotomi-kun...
Ron!
Sanshoku doukou sanankou tanyao dora 3!
Baiman!
Zugaan.
He dealt in?
How was that the best possible move?!
This outcome was precalculated too.
Look at him closely!
You're right. Even the way he says "Zugan"
doesn't break his composure.
Ron! Junchan sanshoku pinfu iipeikou!
Zugan.
Lucky! Pinfu ryanpeikou dora dora!
Dora
Zugan.
Riichi!
That's riichi ippatsu chinitsu ittsuu dora 1!
Zugan.
He's a machine!
Huh?
The precision to deal in the takame every time!
The increased durability to keep dealing in without flinching!
A-Are you saying...
Yes, he has become...
Without exaggerating, the world's strongest...
University of Tokyo
Dealing-in machine!
Thus, Toyotomi was remodeled
by the University of Tokyo mahjong pundit Ide
into a perfect dealing-in machine.
Ron!
Daisangen.
Will the day ever come when he can return to the ways of the world? Stay strong, Toyotomi!
Zugan.
WWYD? South 1, East seat, turn 12, 21100 points Draw: 8m Dora: 3s
The first prize ski trip!
Here it is!
Ah, too bad! You win tissue paper.
Tough luck!
Zugan!
Fine! All last!
yakuman!
Oh!
Toyotomi-kun!
Luxury
wares
First prize:
a ski trip!
Akina-chan!
Let's go...
Oh! Congratulations!
Yay! I did it!
Great! That's our Akina-chan! You're amazing!
Episode 3 Part 2
Snowslide Zugan
All right, Toyotomi-kun! Let's slide!
Aye!
There!
Toyotomi-kun! Hurry up!
Will be there now! Let's go!
Let's go?
Well, that's just like you, Toyotomi-kun!
Akina-chan is so cute!
But, when two go skiing together,
the après-ski is a matter of course!
I'm going first, Toyotomi-kun!
It's just the two of us, Toyotomi-kun...
Just the two of us, Akina-chan...
I'm feeling a bit tipsy...
Wanna go to bed, then?
Akina-chan!
Ah, aren't you rushing things, Toyotomi-kun?
Akina-chan...
Whassat?
What?
What's that?
T-These voices!
Hey! Move it, move it, move it!
What the... What the... What the... What the...
Did I really just see...
Yo! If it isn't Toyotomi!
What a coincidence!
Zugan
Really, what are the odds?
To think we'd end up in neighboring rooms at the same inn!
Didn't you three just follow me here?
What are you on about? We won the ski trip from that same lottery.
It makes sense that we stayed
in the same inn!
What?! These guys too?
This will make our après-ski
a lot more exciting!
Yeah! Let's get straight to it!
Do something, Akina-chan...
Hey, don't act like a spoiled kid!
Damn right, men belong in the men's world!
Akina-chan...!
Pon!
That's a pon!
I'm gonna pon that chun too.
Riichi!
Why stop now?
4m!
Whoa! Impressive!
That's what I call ultra-cool mahjong!
I got to tenpai but I can't discard 4s...
It's time for the trustworthy technique: genbutsu of two players!
Weak.
Passing the bump that is Yasu
and dodging Shintaro's frozen tree,
magnificent mawashi-uchi!
My parallel technique!
Ron! Tanyao sanshoku dora 1!
Zugaaan!
Zugan.
Zugan. Zugan. Zugan.
Zugan, Zugan, Zugan!
Toyotomi                  Oda                 Akechi            Tokugawa
Zugaaan...
Really, Toyotomi?
Last place again?
Let's switch, Toyotomi-kun.
Let me play instead of you.
But you're hopeless, Akina-chan...
No more hopeless than you!
Well, if you say so...
Yes, please do! Play with me! Let's play together!
We'll keep playing all night!
Yasu, you're drooling.
Dora
East 1st round
Akina Hayami
Dealer's hand
Hm? That's a pretty good haipai.
You start discarding with the honors, like this, right?
Huh! Oh no, I dropped my pair of pei!
Oh? It's another pei!
Really? That's a win for me!
Oh no! I would have won from the start and you didn't tell me, Toyotomi!
Right, you sure are lucky...
Tsumo dora 1 is 1000 all, you know.
Wow, thanks!
Look at this, Toyotomi-kun!
Huh? He fell over...
That's because he's a snowflake.
Fine, then. I can do it by myself.
Riichi!
Her luck just doesn't end...
Yay! Ippatsu tsumo!
What!?
Huh-uh?!
I wish I had it...
But not this time.
Jeez... How long are we gonna let her keep stringing us along?
Ah, my bad!
The tiles stuck together, ya know!
Dora
So, pinfu ryanpeikou dora dora, or, chiitoitsu dora dora...
Which one should I go for, huh?
4p was the girl's tsumo!
Riichi with this one!
Huh?
Haneman!
Yay!
I got tsumo!
Look!
The hell? 47p shanpon? Unthinkable!
What a stupid wait...
Uhh, with riichi and tsumo,
it's toitoi, right?
Riichi tsumo...
Toitoi?
Oh man, would you look at the time!
Yeah, gotta go to sleep soon.
Right, right, it's bad for my skin.
Not so fast!
Wha... Didn't you faint earlier?
That's right! I saw it!
Huh? Faint? Why would I?
If you wanna go back to your room,
pay up that 16,000 all first!
Way to go, Akina-chan!
You just made up for all my losses!
Go, Akina! Akina!
Oh, I was just getting in the mood...
Dora
Tsumo
Let's go! Double ton dora 3, ni-
Riichi.
Huh?! No way!
Really? This is a top hand!
Got it! My kanchan!
Riichi ippatsu double ton dora 3!
With ura being 6m, that's dealer's baiman!
Well, that rocks, all right...
Ron!
Tsumo!
Ron! Tsumo!
Ron!
Tsumo!
T-That woman is no joke...
Suddenly she's at the top with 300,000.
Well, isn't that amazing, Akina-chan!
Two people dealt in and you got a yakuman!
Toyotomi-kun, I'm sleepy.
Can I go to bed?
Yeah, sure!
I'll handle it from here.
Even you should be okay with 300,000 of advantage, Toyotomi-kun.
Sorry, but I'll leave the rest to you.
Sure thing!
There's no way I can lose to these dolts now!
Easy win, easy money!
Toyotomi...
Easy win... against us?
There's no way I'm gonna lose to you.
You're all so intimidating!
But a 300,000 point lead
is not that easy to close!
Ron! Mentanpin sanshoku!
Just 8,000 for now,
300,000 is still a way off...
I-It is a way off, as you say.
The first place is clearly mine already.
W-Why don't you just accept it already and go for second?
Here.
Ron! Menhon double ton!
Damn it, that's not even haneman...
I really needed a dora...
E-Even 12,000 is still not a big deal...
N-No... It isn't!
Ron! Chiitoi dora dora!
Double ron! Ittsuu dora dora!
Oops, it's this late already?
See ya tomorrow!
I gotta sleep too.
Not so fast!
No quitting without a rematch!
If you wanna go to sleep, you're gonna have to play with us for at least 10 hanchans more!
And so, Toyotomi's hellish après-ski night dragged on.
Ah! That sweet dream of spending the night with Akina, whither is it now?
Good morning, Toyotomi-kun!
Huh?
Zugaaan...
T-There's no way...
Stupid Toyotomi-kun!
Super Zugan!
It seems I'm way luckier than Toyotomi-kun.
I guess I should also try to play mahjong more often now?
Huh? Oh no, I have to move!
Next on Super Zugan:
Rake Zugan
and Akina Once More.
Definitely watch it!
Don't you fall asleep!