Mahjong Parlor BestPlace
Hey! I need to leave!
Can you fill in for me?
Toyotomi-kun!
Table 4 needs to fill in!
Got it!
I'm up by about 10,000,
so you can take it easy.
Got it!
Well, it's just the 3rd day of Toyotomi working here, but he's really doing well!
Oh, nice haipai!
Go easy on us, won't you, Mr. Student?
Aye, go easy, mate.
Riichi!
Double riichi?
Soon enough, all last
Riichi.
Crikey! Not again!
Give us a break, wontcha!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo pei!
Toyotomi-kun, what's the matter
with you today?!
Did you see it, Manager?
I hope nothing bad happens now!
Why would it?
It's all skill, no luck involved!
Episode 6 Part 1
Object X From Osaka
Akina-chan...
Wh-Who the hell are you?
Come on, stop sleeping!
Who are you?!
You're too loud!
Oi s'matter, mate?
You're the customer who I beat
in the mahjong parlor where I work!
That's some bloody good exposition!
Aye! I'm just a wandering uni student without two farthings to rub together.
But on me path, seeking to calm me heart,
once in a while, I chance into a parlor.
That doesn't explain what you're doing here.
In that parlor, me heart...
T'was yer play that brought peace to my heart.
Ya stripped me of all me point sticks
like it was nothing!
And what's more, ya stripped me
of me place to sleep.
Listen, you...
But, happiness is found amid sorrow, mate.
And I shan't let go of that bloody lead once I've found it!
And it's you who let me see it, Master!
Master?!
Of course, mate!
I had a hunch back in that parlor...
"Ah! I'm not match for 'im!
I admire that bloke
from the depths of me heart!
This bloke's best fit to be me master, aye!"
Really?!
Aye, that's about it, mate.
But who let you sleep here?!
Wake the damn up, you jerk!
Tea House Zugan
Oi, Master! Ya look buggered, mate.
'Course I do! I didn't sleep a wink tonight!
Ya got work today, mate?
No.
Then how 'bout we get a group going for some hard round of mahjong?
How about we don't
and you just go home?
How can ya say that?
Ya'r me master now, mate!
Ah! Oi, babe, another cuppa, please.
Who the hell are you, anyway?!
Sorry I'm late!
Did I make you wait, Toyotomi-kun?
Oh hey, no! I just got here.
Crikey!
M-Much obliged for takin' care of me master.
Yes, I'm Hayami, hello.
Who is this?
Akina-chan, just ignore him altogether!
By the way, do ya happen to dabble in mahjong, Akina-san?
Yeah, I can play.
Das wonderful!
Playing mahjong with a hottie like yerself been me dream since ever!
No!
Who else should we invite?
Hey, that's my address book!
Akechi, Oda and Tokugawa're gonna rock up, and maybe even Baba-san!
Tea 'n' bickies: OK!
Pillows: OK!
Point sticks: OK!
Ashtray and matches: OK!
Now, now, ya can just get yerself seated, Master and Akina-san.
Long time no see!
Ya'r right on time, Baba-san!
East 1
Oi, Baba-san,
I've a shedload to ask ya...
Who is this feller, by the way?
Me? In Osaka, I am known as the Calling Dabo Ken!
Oh, really?
Hey... Show some more respect! Baba-san is a pro, yet he agreed to play with us.
I'm just a C League pro.
Aight-o! Mate, this haipai's a pearler!
Oi, let's see!
You don't have to yell it every time.
Haku.
Pon, mate!
Chun.
Let's play safe.
That's suji.
Oi, wait a minute there, mate.
Did I deal in?
Nah, it passed, mate. Made ya bloody spooked though, didn't I?
You bastard!
Wally's the pretty bone, so with the trolley bus I get blood and blanket with two pretties.
That's a bloody mangan, mate!
All right, riichi!
Crikey!
P-Pon, mate!
Pretty bone pon!
She let me pluck the pretty bone too!
Gotta be a shonky reachie!
Here, blimey!
P-Pass.
Righto, let's tie up this haneman!
Aight! Kan!
Wally kan!
Dirty oldies and all pairs with ten pretties! That's a counted yakuman!
Oi, gimme a good draw!
Bloody hell!
Wow, it came out!
Riichi only!
Wh-What the bloody hell's that?!
Hey! I got 7 ura dora!
Mangan?
That's a baiman, girl.
Unbelievable!
Hayami-san, ya came a bloody gutser calling a reachie with the pretty bone!
Oh, why's that? It's a suji trap.
As if I'm gonna bugger off with me bloody huge hand!
But you discarded the 8m anyway!
Das not what I bloody mean!
Hm? Then what do you mean?
It's about time to show Akina-chan what it means to play with a pro.
The ideal discards.
Riichi!
If I win this hanchan...
Baba-san, you're amazing!
I've always wanted a strong man like you to have me!
Sure! I'll "have" all of you!
Just like that!
Ah, I can see your 3p kanchan!
Baba-san, it ain't funny, mate.
If I know his wait, I'm dead set to win this!
6s.
Pon!
5s.
Dinkum colour, all mids and pairs!
Good on me! Coming back for a double baiman right after getting do boned!
5m.
Ron!
Master!
I shan't let ya discard the five rick!
What? It's the riichi's genbutsu!
As if! The reachie's ridgy-didge, but ya gotta fold against the other blokes too!
I reckon ya need to go for the one chance squadron, mate!
What the hell's your problem?!
Iipeikou dora 1!
Blimey!
Holding me squadrons and me gates!
And she's got a pair of Baba's traffic lights!
Blow me!
Master, we can't be careless now!
Doncha agree? There's a few things ya should never let go of in ya life!
I'm not talking about justice or friendship, of course!
It's the Master-Disciple love.
The deep bond that always connected us!
Long story short, if the disciple loses, the master loses, mate!
What?!
And in return, when my master wins, I win!
It's our fate to never be sundered apart, mate!
I never asked for this!
And then, all last...
You ain't have to worry about nothing, mate.
I flogged the pro good and I'm in first place by heaps!
It's not over yet, ya know.
'Course it is, mate!
I got a 10k lead in all last, I can win this with me peepers closed, mate!
You said it, now you gotta win with your eyes actually closed.
And I will! Just watch this!
You'll just hafta say the bones out loud, mate.
6s.
3p.
Chun.
Ton and riichi!
I don't quite get it...
The hell? That's a seven double-ups if I ever saw one!
I'll discard the jimmy rick!
Yay, it came out!
Riichi ippatsu menhon shousangen chanta dora dora!
Dora
How much is that as dealer?
What the...
Master!
It was just for a jiffy, but good on ya for taking care of me.
With this, I take me leave!
See ya again!
This world is cash!
Cash makes the world go round!
That's the Way of Osaka Finance!
The mysterious man from Osaka,
the self-proclaimed Calling Dabo Ken
will return in the second part.
South 1, West seat, turn 9, 19200 points Draw: 5s Dora: 7p
Discard 9s for damaten but 6s for riichi.
TN: ?????
Well, Toyotomi-kun, looks like you're the Scum again!
No luck!
Master! Master! Deal 'em to me too!
C'mon, Master!
All the seats in this limited express Romancecars were reserved,
so if they find out there's five of us,
we're screwed!
Whatever ya reckon, mate,
but I wanna play too!
Who the hell are you?
Actually, I don't know either.
That's a good one, who are you?
Mate, such a bunch of bloody wallies you are!
Master 'n' Akina-san 'n' Baba-san too!
Didja already forget the mahjong session we had yesterday?!
Back home they call me Kenjin.
I come from Osaka.
Without two farthings to rub together,
I was all buggered up!
T'was when I had the luck to meet me master.
And stop calling me your master!
When I say ya'r me master then ya'r me bloody master, mate!
Righto, mate?
I'm your personnel from now on.
If it weren't for me,
yer future'd be all buggered up!
Well them, why don't we return to playing President?
Yes, let's do that!
M-Master!
You again? Man, you're such a nuisance...
We'll let you play, but promise to keep quiet!
Episode 6 Part 2
Hot Water Zugan
Howzat? I'll start.
Ace!
Ace!?
Pass!
Pass.
What a cretin,
starting off with that card!
You don't know the rules, do you?
If they're the same mark,
just stacking them up is enough, right?
Yeah, with at least 3 cards.
Howzat, then?
Pass!
Pass.
Oi! Then I guess I done won this one!
Zugan.
Oi, mate, gimme two of your best cards, wontcha?
I shouldn't have let you come with us...
I'm scared!
It'll be fine!
Relax, girl!
Oi! Oi! Whatcha gon' do if ya can't cross this?!
Ah! Stop it!
Ah...
Baba-san! Come help us!
It rained yesterday,
so the water level is just right.
Yeah, it is.
Welcome to our inn!
Thanks for having us!
There's four of you in all, right?
Yeah, only four of us! Not five!
I ain't lying to you!
Just ask them—people call me "Honest Yasu"!
Make yourselves at home, then.
Just keep your mouth shut!
Ow! That hurt...
Master, ya can come out now.
Ah... That was horrible,
I wanna go to a hot bath right away.
I'll go too!
That's better!
Yeah, that water is right nice!
Master! Master!
What is it again?
I just wanted to tell, that door leads directly to the women's section!
What?!
Everybody dive!
Lucky! There's nobody here!
It feels so good!
Really, some inveterate pervs you are.
But why am I the only one who got slapped?
Master, that's love, mate, love!
All right, let's get down to business!
Right...
Why do I have to win for this freeloader too?
Master, do your best!
All right!
To widen my hand, what should I discard?
Whatever ya reckon, Master!
Dora
Here ya should keep the nan a safe tile and cut the 4m!
And you should just shut up!
These blokes've got quick hands!
If ya greed ya'r gon get outpaced!
Riichi!
Aye, told ya so, mate.
Now hurry up to deal in!
I have no safe tiles! What should I do?
Leave it to me, Master!
We'll use the method of elimination!
The method of elimination?
Aight, listen up! First off, the 25p we have 4 of is no good.
We also shan't discard the 36s we have 3 of.
The 4m and 5s are ura suji, so those are the mainline!
The 6p riichi discard was either from 566 or from 246!
So that means 3p and 4p are the most dangerous!
Ah! That means...
3m!
Of course, we shan't discard that either because it's dora!
We ain't discarding anything it seems!
Oh man! Why does it
have to be so bad for me?
Entertainments
Sukan
and
Zugan
in Kyoto
Well, ain't that why I were telling ya to take South, huh?
There's no point saying that now!
Ya gonna discard something or what?!
When I don't have safe tiles, I'll cut this and advance my hand!
Wut? It passed.
All right...
6s!
That's the same tile!
All right!
Slam! 4m riichi!
Wut... Sanmenchan?
C'mon...
The cheaper out...
Riichi pinfu tsumo dora 1...
Ya what, mate?
Ya forgot to check the ura!
M-Master!
Menpin tsumo dora 3!
That's a haneman!
East 2
Dora
This is where ya just ride the flow and riichi!
I don't know where the dora is...
I'll play it safe and dama!
Ya'r a bloody pussy, Master.
What are you two murmuring about?
Riichi!
It came!
Let's cut 9m and call riichi!
Fine...
Yan!
Ah...!
Let the bygones be bygones! C'mon now!
Wow!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo!
Chiitoi dora dora!
Really? No way!
I was waiting on the white too...
You seen that? Seen that?
I dint expect no less from me master!
What about the ura?
What? It didn't come up?!
It should have come, what is this?
You're getting unlucky, Master.
What are you on about? Riichi!
Next round
Rich people... How does it go?
Don't fight between themselves, Master.
Ron! 3,900.
I guess we should keep an eye on you too, huh?
Oi, do yer best, mate!
Ron! 2,000!
Dama 2000? Are you okay winning that?
It goes to next round so that's even good for us!
Ron! 1,300.
Ha-ha! That's peanuts!
Ron! 1,500.
It's next to nothing!
Ron! 2,900 is 3,200!
Too little!
Tenpai.
Tenpai!
I'm the only one noten, really?
Master, I wouldn't laugh if I were you...
All last
So... 24,000 points!
I got 24,800.
25,000 sharp.
26,200...
A solid first place with 2200 over last place?
Master...
Master!
Wh-What?
Now, the time to repay me Master has come.
The truth is, in Osaka
they call me "Getaway Ken!"
Me profound apologies
for hiding it up until now.
Me technique of running away in all last...
Please drink yer beer there
and observe it carefully!
Yeah. Sure, I'll leave it to you.
Turn 4
A ryanshanten with sanshoku chance. The dora is 9m?
Dora
Shan't need it!
What are you doing?
To take 1st, you need a fast hand more than points!
It's basic theory.
You can't get to the first place
if you keep these!
You can! You totally can!
You missed tenpai for sanshoku dora 3!
Doesn't matter.
This iishanten has a much better shape!
Let's go with that.
Ron!
Pinfu dora 1! 2000!
2200 more than last
deal in for 2000
= last place
Bloody hell! Just no luck today!
La-Last place... Last...
If you're last, it will last...
Gambling is about luck, Master!
We're going back!
Let it flow away...
All of the sad memories...
Let them flow away with the stream.
Master! Am I just a paper lantern to you?!
"The record with my memories of you of yesteryear is still playing..."
Is what Toyotomi was thinking.
"Let the pain fly away."
So Kenjin-kun ended up freeloading at Toyotomi-kun's place and he's here to stay.
Pleasure being here!
Next time on Super Zugan:
Baby Player Ponta
and Jongputer in a Pond.
Make sure to watch it!
Don't you fall asleep!