Toyotomi Hideyoshi, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba Prefecture.
Oda Shintaro. A one-hit wonder who is ignorant of theory. From Chiba Prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasube. An absolute ignoramus who doesn't know when to stop calling. From Chiba.
Akechi Koichi. The expert in by-the-book calculative and rational playstyle. From Chiba.
Hayami Akina.
Technically Toyotomi's love interest.
Born with incredible luck.
From Chiba Prefecture.
Riichi!
Here it comes...
I see...
Episode 2 Part 1
Happy Birthday Zugan
S-Since when do you cut tiles like that?
You're not gonna make it if you're the
sort to discard genbutsu to a riichi...
To make your read yet discard a harsh tile...
Doing that sharpens your innate sensitivity and allows you to see through the opponent's tiles!
That passes.
There!
Pass!
How about this?
Why? What's wrong?
I'll let it pass...
What kind of hand are you even making?
Meanwhile, the one who riichi'd
has to play defensive.
This is the best feeling!
Here!
Y-You're... really gonna discard that on haitei?
Eh?
That was... haitei?
Ah,
Tanyao nomi.
Ron on takame! Riichi Itsuu
Haitei Dora 1 Ura 1!
Zugaaaan...
Just a dream?
Yes? Toyotomi here.
Ah, Toyotomi-kun?
This is Hayami.
Akina-chan?
Truth is, it's my birthday today.
Huh, is that so?
So I wanted to ask
if you'd like to come today.
We'll celebrate, just the two of us.
Yahoo!
I can handle cooking and other menial things myself,
so could you just buy the cake
on your way here?
Welcome!
This birthday cake, please!
Is it someone's birthday?
Yup!
Your girlfriend?
Could you write "Akina" on it for me?
Should I add "from an enviable little guy?"
Thanks for your business!
Is it your girlfriend's birthday?
Oh, come on!
You already asked this—
What a coincidence,
us meeting in a place like this!
Also, is that a cake I'm seeing?
N-No, it's...
Let me see!
Since we're here, we might as well let deliver the cake ourselves.
No! You can't have that cake!
There's nothing to worry about, pal.
You'll be coming along as well, right?
Come on! Chop chop! Let's go!
Zugaaaaan...
Mahjong parlor
Pleasant
That's quite the cake you bought.
But what about repaying your debt to us, I wonder?
Beep, boop...
Don't try to boop-boop us.
You must pay us back
with any extra money you get.
What's the deal with a cake like this anyways?
No! Please, not the cake...
Humph! Only if you win.
Defeat us and you'll have your cake back.
Tsumo.
Chun, Menzen Honitsu.
Tsumo!
Tanyao, Pinfu, Dora 2!
Riichi, Tsumo, Sanankou.
Damn, this is some tanoshii mahjong.
Bet, bet!
Oh come on, why'd you always have
to make a nasty face like that?
You're spoiling the fun.
Ron! Pinfu, Dora 1!
2900 as dealer.
I must win this...!
I win and then it's a very special happy birthday just for the two of us!
Chi!
Pon!
Huh?
What's going on with that call and that pond?
There's been two hatsus discarded
already as well...
It's either an Itsuu made out of souzu
or a 123 shape sanshoku, right?
He just doesn't learn, does he?
Ron!
Sanshoku Doukou Nomi!
That's a 2900 yoroshiku!
What?!
Toyotomi did a renchan...
How could this be?
I-I've never seen anything like that...
Ron! Tanyao Nomi!
Tsumo! Chun!
The three players who saw Toyotomi's renchan for the first time ever could not hide their shock.
Yet Toyotomi continued to stack his wins.
Until finally...
S4
It's All Last with me leading 15000
above the second place.
I'm winning by a landslide!
All right! I got a dora ankou!
Riichi!
Aye, same here.
Dora
Good! I got to tenpai as well.
If I'm to aim for the hidden Sanshoku, then it's best I cut South for the penchan on 7s.
Yasu
Toyotomi
Shintaro
Akechi
But 7s is unlikely to come out of Toyotomi...
Shintaro's riichi looks dangerous after all...
On that note, Toyotomi's more likely to drop 8s as a one-chance... so I'll deliberately...
Tanki on the 9s!
Three riichis on the same turn, huh? Dammit!
Come on!
It came!
A 369 wait mangan! Chun Dora 3!
If it plays out well, sanankou stacks
as well raising it to haneman!
Judging by the discards, a 9s
has 90% chances of passing!
And as long as it doesn't connect to the dealer,
there's no chances of a gyakuten.
I won!
With this, the victory is mine!
Akina-chan, I'll be with you soon!
Congratulations, Akina-chan!
Thank you, Toyotomi-kun.
Whoa! This stew's delicious!
The salad's great too!
What's wrong, Akina-chan?
I just thought it almost looks like it's your own birthday instead!
But I'm really glad you came.
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu South Dora 1, 12000!
Riichi Ippatsu
Pinfu Itsuu! That's 8000!
Oh boy, we both read well didn't we?
Well said!
We're like mahjong brothers!
Huh? Wait, triple ron was allowed, right?
Aye! Anything goes!
Sorry then, that's a ron from me too.
Riichi Ippatsu Honroutou
Chiitoitsu Ura 2, 16000.
Su...
Super Zugaaaaan...
Super Zugaaan!
P-Please... Another round.
But let that cake be!
Mahjong parlor
Pleasant
By the way, Toyotomi,
that jacket seems a little too nice for you.
Hey, Toyotomi, some change fell out.
Thanks for the cake!
Quite a productive day we had, right?
Sure did.
Zugan...
Toyotomi-kun sure is late...
Toyotomi
If only...
If only he had left without hurry after eating that cup ramen...
He might have never even
come across that trio.
But alas, he could not possibly know how much good
this 129 yen cup of ramen could do him after he answered that phone call...
All right, riichi!
The true essence of mahjong
lies not in reading the pond...
It is way more important to be able to pinpoint with precision what your opponent is thinking.
For example, this guy will sip on some
tea in exactly 30 seconds.
It can't be 29 seconds or 31 seconds.
Only 30 seconds sharp.
My calculation must be impeccable!
Yasu will light a cig in 7 seconds...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7..!
Did i deal in?
You really did!
How did you know?
Riichi Sanankou Dora 1!
Come on, give me the sticks already.
"Keep the change."
Really? How generous!
A washbowl...
That's right, a washbowl!
Episode 2 Part 2
Rejected Zugan
And that's another riichi for me!
What...?
What is...
...he doing?
Hm! Genbutsu. He tightened up.
The true essence of mahjong is four people sticking their faces in a washbowl.
The first one to raise his face loses.
Tenpai! Kanchan wait on 5m!
Pon.
Come on, get out of the water!
Just come on already and...
Raise your head!
Tsumo!
Menzen Honitsu Iipeikou!
Zugan...
That's nothing! Tsumo!
Hontoutou Chiitoitsu.
Tsumo! Suuankou!
Zugan, zugaaan...
Akina-chan!
Good morning, Toyotomi-kun!
Sorry I'm late.
It's probably due to that nightmare I had...
I mean... No, nevermind! Let's go!
Please make it so that things would work out
between me and Akina-chan someday.
Please make it so that Toyotomi-kun
stops playing mahjong.
Fortune slips
Hey, let's draw some fortune slips!
Sure!
I got 6!
I got 12.
Yay! I'm going to be in luck!
What have you got, Toyotomi-kun?
You're going to be out of luck
W-Wanna try drawing another one?
Yeah. One more!
You'll be SHIT out of luck
O-One more...
Zugan
One more!
One more! One more! One more!
One more! One more! One more! One more!
Hey mister,
maybe it's best that you stop now?
Give me last chance!
Lesser Luck
I got fed up with your persistence
Did it!
Fortune slips
That'll be 5000 yen for all the slips.
Zugaaaan...
Still, even if it cost 5,000, you managed to draw a Lesser Luck, so it was worth it, wasn't it?
I really admire that resilient part of yours, Toyotomi-kun.
Oh? Look!
They're staging a Noh performance over there.
What's wrong Toyotomi-kun?
Why do you look so scared?
Zugaaan...
Toyotomi-kun!
Mahjong parlor
Long Dive
Just like in my nightmare...
Oh, Toyotomi!
Wow, to think we'd meet here!
Honestly, did you notice us?
W-Weren't the three of you supposed to go to some hot springs this week?
We went there. We really did.
But without seeing you, we were getting homesick, so we returned early.
Allowance
Plus, we can’t buy the souvenirs
without a New Year’s allowance from you.
But maybe the envelop we bought
is a tad too small for this?
Yasu, don't you know how to keep your mouth shut?
But well, now you know what happened.
Well then, let's start the first hanchan
with the steamed buns from hot springs at stake!
Huh?
Kokushi tenpai waiting tanki on South...
There's already one in the ponds...
Fuck it, riichi!
Say, what?
Shintaro's gimmick is ippatsu
tsumo after all, right?
I'll call it.
You little...
Whatever, here comes a spicy one!
Ah... I should've riichi'd that one too...
Dora
I would've won it with that 7s, but since
I'm yakunashi I can't win off of it...
Even though I have dora to boot...
Just tsumo it!
Rats!
Pass it!
Finally! Yakuman, Kokushi Musou!
Ron! 5200!
Unlucky...
Wait a second! That south Toyotomi just tsumogiri'd...
If I hadn't called I'd have tsumo'd then and there!
I didn't think about it in the heat of the moment!
Unlucky...
What a luckless man I am!
Because I was being so inattentive, I'll never,
ever get to eat steamed buns from hot springs!
Easy now. These things happen.
I really like that resilient part of yours, Toyotomi-kun!
T-That's right!
After so many unlucky slips,
I finally got one one with Lesser Luck.
Men of the future need to be more resilient!
Stickier than fermented beans!
I’ll keep fighting with the tenacity of a bull!
Watch me closely Akina-chan!
Did it!
Suuankou Tenpai.
Hmm... I'll wait on it on the chun.
Chun might be a hell wait, but as long as it's
not in the dead wall, it's as good as mine!
As for 1p, as long as nobody has an
ankou of it, it should still get dropped.
But if I cut chun, then it'll be a 13p wait! On top of that...
3p would
make it a simple sanankou!
I cannot possibly win this
hand as a mere sanankou!
Ah, to hell with it! There's no way they'll both
get dropped in the same turn anyway!
I'll wait on my 1p tank!
3p!
Don't drop a 1p on me now!
I guess I don't need this one.
To hell with your iipin!
The essence of mahjong is four people sticking their heads into a washbasin.
The first to raise his face is the loser!
Th-That's it! The dream from this morning!
The first one to raise his head loses!
And I cannot possibly afford to lose here!
Zugaaan!
Phew, man!
That took me by surprise!
For me to get a Kokushi back-to-back... Man, this is some crazy luck!
Super... Zugan!
I'm at 47000.
32000 here.
I'm 80000.
Keep a tab of it, will you?
Zugaaan...
Akina-chan!
You left me all alone at the shrine to play mahjong again, didn't you?!
Forget that I ever knew you!
W-Wait, it was by force of circum—
Zugaaan....
A stray cloud floating in the autumn sky.
The spring quickly changes to summer,
then, before you know it, it's autumn.
Will Toyotomi's spring ever arrive?
Haiku: O crimson dragonfly, whither doth thy path lie in yon boundless azure firmament?
There's always tomorrow.
Don't give up, Toyotomi! Good luck, Toyotomi!
If we turn Toyotomi-kun into an augmented
superhuman mahjong machine,
he might be capable of defeating the trio!
And then he'll go back
to how he used to be!
Next time: Super Zugan!
The Toyotomi Machine of Terror and
Snowslide Zugan.
Watch it, okay?
Don't you fall asleep!