Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Mahjong parlor
First Building
Hey, what's the score?
Aye, Boss. East round's over, and yer on 48,000 points, boss.
Heh, that's not a lot.
Well, time for South!
Episode 16 Part 1
Head-On Zugan
Toyotomi's drive is really something today!
You haven't seen anything,
that's just the East round!
Riichi!
Dora
don't know what to do about the above signs, remind me to typeset them when muzu fills that in
If I draw 6p or 7p,
it's tanyao sanshoku tenpai...
Dora
Dealer riichi? 2s is dangerous...
"Rich men shouldn't pick fights!" Mawashi!
I drew it...
Boss!
If ya hadn't cut the 4s,
ya could've won ya best out!
If the 4m and 2s had passed, that is.
All right! Riichi tsumo!
Oi! The dealer's wait was 58m!
Either one would've passed!
E-Easy to say in hindsight...
Well, it was cheap anyway,
it was the right call.
Dora
All right, with this I'll push everything!
And it's only turn 6!
Dora
Ron! Chun Dora Dora! 9,600!
Boss!
Riichi!
My hand's trash...
All right! Tsumo! 3,000/6,000!
Zugan!
Ron! 7,700.
Tsumo. 500/1,000!
Ron! 6,400!
Tsumo! 8,000!
You spin me right Zugan!
Mama-san, cold water please.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Good night!
Havin' to go for two minute noodles's pretty shoddy.
Why couldn't I take first place...
I always get good draws in East...
Today too!
I had 48,000 points going into South!
I got it, Boss.
The problem's the dealer Riichi in South 1!
Riichi!
Dora
Ya cut your only genbutsu, 4s, and bludged!
This too
Dora
That's the obvious play as first place.
Fair enough, but after that...
All right! Riichi tsumo!
Ron! 9,600!
Tsumo! 3,000/6,000!
Ron! 7,700.
Tsumo! 500/1,000!
Ron! 6,400!
Tsumo! 8,000!
O-Okay, you can stop already.
I shan't! That 4s is the reason for all ya losses, Boss!
Right-o, Boss?
If yer gambling hard and don't play head-on,
that's piss-poor! Got it?
Head-on?
Too right! Like at Sekigahara!
When the victory of the Eastern Army was already assured!
5TH YEAR OF KEICHO (1600), BATTLE OF SEKIGAHARA
Two thousand Satsuma soldiers from the Western Army remained on the battlefield!
Criminy!
It seems our Western Army is defeated!
If we're to retreat anyway, then we'll show them the spirit of Satsuma first!
Against the tens of thousands
of advancing Eastern soldiers...
They went on a never seen before in military history—forward retreat!
In other words, they retreated in the direction of the enemy!
They sped across right before the eyes
of the Eastern commander, Tokugawa Ieyasu...
And in the end were able to escape!
Splendid! They went straight through!
Another example!
Imagine yer a fine arts student who's destined to fail!
Okay...
If yer gonna fail anyway,
which model are ya gonna paint?
Huh?
A frontal nude, or from the back?
From the front!
Too right!
I get it! A man's gotta take things head-on!
It's the same with mahjong!
If yer gonna get last anyway,
it's better to pull it head on than by folding!
Even if ya lose big time
and end up 100,000 in the red,
at the end of the day, it's just a last place!
That's right!
Understood, Boss?
I got it all right! Just one small thing...
"If you're gonna get last anyway..."
That's what you said, right?
Huh? You sh-shouldn't take it wrong, Boss,
I was merely telling the hard facts...
I see. Now I really understand
what you meant...
Make a circle with your hands.
Wh-Whatcha gonna do, Boss?!
No more mooching off me!
Now get lost!
B-Boss!
'Sup!
Y-You came!
That's no good, you gotta be nice to your disciple!
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Look, time to reconcile!
Boss!
He was crying, you know.
Boss! Forgive me!
I-I get it...
From now on, you'll get to take a good look at my head-on playstyle!
Righto.
No worries, mate. Head on!
Wait for it! To play head-on means trying to win greedily!
Riichi.
Oh no, I was too slow with discarding 8m!
And with 5p and 3s!
What?!
N-No worries, mate! Just talkin' to myself, carry on, mate!
Greeding successful!
Hey. If I cut 4m,
I'll have tanpin sanshoku tenpai!
Do you think 4m will pass?
Times like these,
ya gotta believe she'll be right!
It's London to a brick he's waiting on the 25p ya got an anko of!
All right, let's go!
Ron! Riichi pinfu.
Zugan!
Crikey!
Riichi.
Fold.
Hmm, I can chii 2p and get keishiki tenpai with upgrade to sanshoku...
But...
Will the 8s pass?
Chii!
Whatever! Push for tenpai!
Knock-knock! Riichi chanta sanshoku, mangan!
Crikey!
Zugan!
Toyotomi's pitchin' fast tonight!
Boss, ya still got 1,000 points left.
Even at the risk of busting out,
if ya play head on you'll get good hands for sure!
Really!
Wow, it's true! What a great hand!
Told ya!
Pon!
Chii!
Tsumo! Nan honitsu chanta!
Attaway!
Honitsu iipeikou!
Riichi chiitoi!
Pinfu dora dora!
Tanyao dora 3!
Junchan ryanpeikou!
Boss! The head-on's shit-hot!
Yer first in all last!
All right, now it's simple!
Take first by winning a hand!
Perfect plan!
Pon!
Time for a power move!
Kan!
Keep revving up yer head-on, Boss!
You bet I will!
All right, drew a 3p anko!
Haku pon!
Kan this too!
Whoa, amazing draws!
Kan! Kan! Kan!
All right, tenpai for toitoi sankantsu haku dora 3!
She'll be right now!
I say this passes!
It's a Kan!
Boss!
Suukantsu?!
Nothin' personnel, Toyotomi.
Ton, kan!
Now it's a draw.
Th-There's no abortive draw when there's a suukantsu!
Don't be stupid, Toyotomi!
There's no rinshan to draw anymore!
But hey, Shintaro,
I kind of agree with Toyotomi though...
(In Suuankou Tenpai)
I also think it doesn't go to draw in this case.
Toyotomi won't be the one to win this round.
I'll win a suuankou before him!
All right, got it! Then I'll just draw this dora indicator! Don't mind if I do!
No way!
Whoa, 1m tsumo!
Whoa, my winning tile was there?!
Tsumo, sanankou dora 8!
Comeback into first!
Zugan!
Oh? So that's what happened last night?
My head-on playstyle backfired...
But, Toyotomi-kun,
if one player has made four kans, a fifth kan can't be made, didn't you know that rule?
W-Wait, for real?!
Zugaaan...
Duke said, "Don't stand behind me!"
Miho-chan said, "Who's behind me now?"
The Grumman F4F pilot said,
"Don't fly a Zero behind me."
Toyotomi thought, "Maybe it's not so bad to try a model from behind sometimes!"
First
Building
Wassup!
How do you do, Mama-san?
Ah, welcome.
You're also here today, Akina-chan?
What happened, Mama-san?
What happened to them, Mama-san?
They look like their souls left their bodies!
W-Well the truth is, just now...
They were beaten down by me!
What?!
Episode 16 Part 2
Zugan Riichi Gets Point Read
Oh man, I'm bored!
What's Toyotomi doing?
Mama-san, when will he be back?
Toyotomi's working the evening shift today.
He said he had a university lecture
in the afternoon.
Mama-san... Why'd they hold a lecture after the semester and the exams are over?
Oh, is that so?
May I join?
Sure, there's a free spot right here!
I see. All right, nice to meet you.
Wuh? We might have a big fish here.
For sure.
That man... I've seen him somewhere...
Ah, I remember now!
I'm the dealer.
Pon!
Riichi!
Dora
Whoa! That's a ballsy discard.
Hey, buddy.
Cutting safe tiles isn't ballsy, you know.
What's a safe tile?! I drew that to get into tenpai.
Now yer cutting risky tiles too!
I read your wait, is all.
It's 69m, and I have an anko of it.
6m just passed!
Pay attention, you dimwit!
Wutcha sayin'? You're gonna deal into my 18,000 anyway, Shintaro.
C'mon, draw it.
Wait
C'mon, deal in, you fat loser.
The dora...
I'll turn it to baiman! Dora tanki!
The fat guy's 2p was one turn too early...
Wait
Ugh! Would have been ippatsu...
All right, tsumo dora 1!
Furiten?!
And just a tsumo dora 1?
What a cheesy win!
That's what happens when I read
and hold on to all your waits!
Riichi!
Oh, 7m suji trap again? I won't fall for it!
Pon!
You like toitoi, huh?
You have a shanpon of ton and chun!
Bro, even if you dama that pinfu ittsuu,
I won't cut your 4m takame!
He's reading...
our waits...
perfectly...
The point reading big guy?
That's right. He's nicknamed the "Point Read Big Guy".
The mahjong terror
of recent days.
His reading instinct's extremely skillful, and he never deals in!
At this rate, our parlor
will become a graveyard!
I got it, Mama-san.
The man Toyotomi
will put him in his place!
Let's do our best!
Don't worry, Mama-san, I'm enough of a match for him by myself.
Let's do something, Akina-chan!
I-I'll try my best!
Let's do our best—together!
Hey, you two...
Toyotomi-kun, you finish cooking the octopus for me!
No, I-I'll join too!
Oh? Mama-san and the lady colluding with each other...
Rude! I'm playing too!
Riichi!
Made it! I have a dora pair! I can even get haneman!
Dora
There, Suji!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu iipeikou ura 1!
Zugan!
I should have been less greedy and cut 1p genbutsu!
A parlor employee dumb enough to deal into such an obvious suji trap?!
Anyway, sorry Mama-san!
Head bump!
What's so funny?
Mister! I see you're trying to cancel her win,
but this parlor allows double ron!
I see... Then that means you dealt into mangan and 5,200.
Zuga–
Ouch!
Why do you have to dig your own grave?
Excuse me for a minute.
M-Maybe he's...
Aha! Spotted!
You were doing drugs
to improve your instinct?!
Tsk. He saw me...
We can't allow such dangerous people in our parlor,
I'll be taking this to Mama, thank you and goodbye and please don't come again!
Wait a moment!
What the fuck are you saying?
It's just ordinary glucose!
What? Glucose?
Wow, it's actually sweet.
Of course!
It's just a type of sugar.
I'm merely using the nutrients
to nourish my instincts.
Ah, that hits the spot...
Oh, so that's why you're so fat!
I can see it. I can see better already!
Riichi!
Even a big guy like you couldn't read my wait here!
Ah, a 69m wait? That's a nice wait.
Or so it would have been if you weren't playing against me!
No way!
Tsumo!
Nice tsumo,
I knew that 6m was your wait.
If I riichi, he'll read my wait. I'll dama now!
I can read dama too!
2s kanchan, isn't it?
Oh no! How did you know?!
Tsumo, haneman!
There's no way he can read this wait...
I can read shanpon too! 5m and 8s!
Ah! I got exposed like an idiot!
Tsumo! I'm embarrassed,
but it's dealer baiman!
This is bad...
I have to get this girl off dealer quick.
Chii!
Pon!
Tsumo! 300/500 with 1 honba,
that's 400/600!
I'm bust!
N-No good!
I'm 20,000 in the red and in third place!
I need to go on the attack!
She's got an early 58p wait, right?
Dora
What's this? 5p kan!
And then, 8p kan!
Riichi!
With that hand, she can't but cut 67p!
What?!
Impossible!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu tanyao chiitoi!
Dora dora dora dora!
Dora Dora Dora Dora Dora Dora Dora Dora Dora...
What do you know! It looks like you got shadowrealmed in East 1 too!
I'm not gonna hear to that
from the likes of you!
Another hanchan!
Early riichi!
7p penchan, isn't it?
Oh no, you're spot on!
Ippatsu tsumo, dealer's mangan!
So I thought!
Your read was right!
Tsumo, haneman!
So I thought!
Spot-on! Tsumo, 2,000/4,000!
Spot-on! Tsumo, 3,000/6,000!
Kokushi, waiting on 9s!
Kyaa!
I'm no match for your reads!
Tsumo, yakuman!
Shadowrealmed.
Say, big guy, was losing
also part of your point read?
Wh-What?!
You've got a bit mouth for someone
who busted out the first!
We both did now, but I'm starting dealer!
And you're West seat!
In other words...
You're last by placement!
Well done, Toyotomi-kun!
In the end, it was you who dealt the final blow.
If reading their waits doesn't work...
I won't even look at them anymore!
There is only attack!
All right, my takame came out!
Honitsu Ittsuu Iipeikou, Haneman!
For you!
Mate, that's too painful even for you.
Yeah, at least try to read his wait!
Look, you drew a suji!
Coming up! Big guy on table three
busted out again!
I guess floating and sinking
go together in life!
But you're the one
that made him sink! You!
Float or sink, sink or float—
this world is at the mercy of the waves.
Even if you try to go with the waves,
tomorrow's harbor weighs on your mind.
This next story is a tad sad love story
about the Luckless Flowers.
And about a lovely girl
that Kenjin-kun met on Valentine's Day.
Next time:
"My Zugan Valentine,"
and "Akina Triangle."
Don't miss it!
I'll kill myself if you sleep!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa