Mahjong parlor
The Usual Place
Ron! Tsuuiisou! That's a yakuman!
Zugan!
You dumbass!
Why did you discard a tile like that now?!
Oh man, that last round
was a comeback home run for Yasu.
It's all thanks to my karma!
So, where do we wanna go first?
We can't let this go on forever.
Episode 8 Part 1
Tsumo-Jong to Make You Cry
No luck...
Wh-What's that?!
Hey, Toyotomi!
It's me, Akechi-kun!
Open up, we know you're there!
Don't make us wait!
Look, everyone!
On the burnable garbage day,
Toyotomi-kun put out the kitchen waste!
Not these guys again...
Jeez...
Hey! Mind if we hang out with you?
Good day.
Oh, or is it good evening?
H-Hey...
Who's this?
My girlfriend, Rie.
Nice to meet you.
Are you that famous Toyotomi-kun who's oh-so good at mahjong?
Yeah, that's right. Toyotomi-kun's oh-so good at mahjong!
I like guys who are strong at mahjong.
R-Really?
That's why I really love my Ko-chan!
What did you come here for?
Dammit, where is that guy?
Who? Yasu-kun?
That son of a...
He probably went to karaoke alone again.
Sounds miserable...
He must be really unpopular
with the girls, right?
Who's unpopular again?
Oh no! You can't just appear with a close-up like that!
The order of appearing had been settled already. Don't fret.
Who's this?
That's my girlfriend Megumi!
But I call her Megu-megu!
Hi!
Did he say Megu-megu?
What's so funny?!
Girlfriend, sure...
However you look at it,
she's way out of your league.
Well yeah, maybe I'm a bit too good a man for her.
Oh, Ya-kun...
What did you come here for...
Hey! Looks like you're all having fun!
Oh, Shintaro! I was just about to call you.
Well, it's a bit messy here,
but please come in!
Hey, it's my place!
Hi!
Wh-Why is Akina-chan with Shintaro?!
Hey. Akina-chan, what happened?
Why did you come with Shintaro?
'Ts right!
The order of appearing had been settled already. Don't fret.
That's Yasu's line.
Why are you together?!
Oh no! Male jealousy is disgusting.
Don't ruin the mood, man!
Don't worry about that!
The Buddha teaches us that "The world is one family."
How do you know that?
Well, let’s not waste time and do what must be done.
Ya-kun, do your best!
Leave it to me!
Don't lose, Ko-chan!
Absolutely not!
Do your best!
Sure.
You didn't even have to say it.
Just sit back and watch!
Akina-chan even sat down next to Oda!
What's going on?!
Why... Why didn't you sit down next to me, Akina-chan?
Did you do that to show how little you care for me? You wench!
Nice! Riichi!
Hey, it's your turn!
Toyotomi!
O-Oh no! I have to focus
on the game right now!
Dora
All right... Sanshoku iishanten.
I'll take the gamble!
Drop the genbutsu 7s dora!
Damn it...
All right! Great draw!
He cut dora early. It can't be this... All right!
Oikake riichi!
Ron! Riichi pinfu junchan sanshoku dora 1! Baiman!
Did you like it, Rie?
Yes! Amazing! That's why I love you so much, Ko-chan!
No big deal!
You get a kiss!
No luck...
It's no good to deal in like that,
Toyotomi-kun...
A-Akina-chan!
She was on my side all along!
This would've been a haneman on 2p tsumo!
Yeah, right!
Zugan...
I had a good hand too...
No way! You discarded dora!
Enough already.
We can see through your act!
She doesn't have a shred of faith in me...
You should win a hand too, Ya-kun!
Oh, I won't stop at that!
For you, I'll get the first place
and buy you a present!
Wow, really? I'm so happy!
Yeah! You just believe in me and wait!
Okay! I'm waiting!
Trust...
Two people in love share an unbreakable bond of trust.
Meanwhile, for us, it's already over...
Yeah, really? You think so? Maybe this one?
Yes, this! Yeah! Do just that!
Hey, mister!
Did you come from Tokyo?
Yeah, sort of...
Tokyo is my hometown...
A hometown is what one thinks of when one is far away.
But they say "The lovers' bond is close yet far away."
When you're watching,
I keep getting good hands!
No way!
White!
Haku!
Two 5m and one 8m out...
And if I call, it's just a mangan.
Only enough to buy a cup of coffee...
I did it!
We're trying French cuisine tonight!
Really?
Time for ippatsu.
Riichi!
Tenpai! I can see the hidden 234 sanshoku!
But the 9m is dangerous...
Should I mawashi...? Nay!
'Tis the sons of Japan who brave such perils! Forsooth, let us go forth!
Riichi!
Ron!
Riichi ippatsu double ton
honitsu ittsuu! Baiman!
Amazing! I should look up to you!
Zugan...
Shit... Akechi and Yasu both got a baiman...
You'll have to win a baiman too, Shintaro-san.
Shintaro-san?
I'm sure she called him just "Shintaro-kun" before...
When did she switch to -san?
Sorry, Toyotomi-kun! I prefer guys who are strong at mahjong!
Well, it is what it is.
Shintaro?!
Th-There's no way!
I can no longer lie about my feelings! Farewell!
Akina-chan...!
This guy's been weird all day.
Did you eat a fly agaric?
The one with the dots.
Hey! This isn't the time
to be worrying about him.
I have Riichi!
I won't deal in.
Akechi can take the first place...
Yasu can win, but I don't care!
But I know for sure...
Just today...
Just today...!
I would absolutely not...
deal into Shintaro,
even if it costs me my life!
Finally, Toyotomi has declared his vendetta to Oda for all the misery inflicted on him!
But has Akina really switched over to Oda and what is her true agenda?
East 2, South seat, turn 5, 25000 points
Tsumo 9s dora 2s
Foresee the invisible junchan sanshoku
t. sakurai
Riichi!
Amazing, Shintaro-san!
It's only the 6th turn!
Don't mention it.
This is nothing.
Akina-chan's happy about Oda's riichi...
Damn it...
I absolutely wouldn't deal into Shintaro!
Episode 8 Part 2
Tsumo-Jong to Make You Cry
Yes! Tanyao tenpai!
The 7s is suji.
Dora
But Shintaro is the kind of guy who cuts 4 from 468 with no worries.
Fold.
That's tough.
What's up with that tough mahjong...
It's hard!
But that same toughness can sometimes...
backfire!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo hatsu sanankou! Haneman!
Amazing, Shintaro-san!
Wu-ha-ha-ha!
What's so funny?
Didn't I tell you I won't deal into Shintaro?
I drew his winning tile on the ippatsu turn!
I read that the 7s was his winning tile and folded!
You think that's something to be proud of, Toyotomi?
If you had cut that tile,
it would have been just a riichi ippatsu!
Folding and not dealing in,
so out of character! What a jerk!
It's your fault we had to pay for haneman tsumo, you dumbass!
Idiot!
How stupid can you be?
Toyotomi-kun...
Hey, let's be forgiving.
Don't bully the poor guy!
Well if you say so, Rie...
You don't have to bully him, Ya-kun...
You're still winning anyway!
Yeah, I guess you're right...
Now, it's time for me to stage a comeback!
Do your best, Shintaro-san!
That's right...
Why did I need to overthink it?
I have to do whatever it takes
to make Shintaro lose!
Folding was wrong!
Dealing in was right!
I can't let him intimidate me!
I must face him head-on!
The dora is 8p.
Wut?
What happened?
N-No, nothing...
It's just that my haipai was particularly bad...
Really, that's all?
That's a good answer.
Yeah, I'm deep in trouble now.
What a terrible haipai, man...
Something's off with this guy.
Bad draws and bad flow...
Dora
I did it! Turn 4 tenpai!
Tanyao sanshoku dora dora!
Don't mind if I do!
Now it's time for...
Telepathic attack!
Cut 258s!
258s!
Riichi.
I said riichi!
Bad premonition!
Fine! Que será, será!
Like hell! I've been in damaten for ages!
Riichi!
Take that, you thief!
I-It passed...
It's a miracle!
A true wonder...
Maybe luck has finally turned to me...
Are you watching, Akina-chan?
I'll show you that you were wrong to give up on me altogether!
258s deal-in!
It worked! It worked! It worked!
Hooray! In the end, ippatsu from Shintaro! I did it!
I'm so happy... I'm so glad to be playing mahjong!
It makes me cry too...
Yeah...
Are you crying in sympathy?
No.
It's always touching to see other players deal into each other.
Well said... It's soul-cleansing!
Well, then. Thank you for waiting, everyone!
I shall now reveal my hand!
I've been waiting!
About time!
There!
Riichi tanyao pinfu ippatsu sanshoku dora dora ban ban!
Oh man, guess I'll give up!
You're out of luck today!
The cheaper out! Tsumo!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo ura ura. Mangan!
Wait, he tsumo'd?
Wow! How wonderful!
So many of these Luckless Flowers!
Toyotomi died. But with his death,
a thousand beautiful flowers bloomed.
Wait! The hanchan isn't over yet!
If you wanna die,
do it after the game!
No luck...
Ron! Ittsuu dora 1! 5200!
Zugan!
Ron! Honitsu chiitoi!
Ron! Riichi tanyao ippatsu ura 8! Sanbaiman!
Ron! Chinitsu pinfu iipeikou! Baiman!
Ron!
Honroutou toitoi sanshoku sanankou haku dora 3! Sanbaiman!
No luck...
Toyotomi just keeps dealing in!
The guy's pretty unlucky.
He hasn't won a single hand.
Toyotomi, you're actually really good!
You’re just a little off your game today!
Shut up! Just leave me be!
I'm not dealing in because I want to!
Not losing because I want to!
But...
But I just keep dealing into people and I can't do anything about it!
Poor guy Toyotomi-kun...
I wanna help him somehow...
I'll cheer for you, Toyotomi!
With me by your side, you'll win!
W-Wut?
Wait a minute, Rie!
Oh, what a nice hand!
You have to win with it!
Awesome, right?
Kyah! You're getting good draws too!
You're so strong! Now call Riichi! Riichi!
Huh? But with this hand you should reject tenpai and cut 7p...
Don't worry! Cut 4p and call riichi!
Riichi, then...
P-Pathetic.
A man crying over losing in mahjong just to gain girls' pity...
You can’t even voice your own opinion and just follow others... It’s pathetic!
Oh, but that's only because Toyotomi-kun is so innocent!
Exactly! When he wants to cry, he can cry!
Shintaro-san, switch with me.
Please!
O-Okay...
Dora
Strong!
Riichi!
Please be tsumo!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu chinitsu ittsuu dora 1! Sanbaiman!
Zugan!
I don't know him.
Me neither.
N-Not again...
Look, Shintaro-san!
Good job, Hayami.
Toyotomi          Shintaro           Yasu             Akechi
Megu-megu, please forgive me for only winning by this much!
Don't mention it!
I'm just happy you did your best!
You're so sweet, my Megu-megu!
Well, it was a good session.
But we gotta go home now.
It was fun! I've never seen anything like that.
How about we go to Disneyland tomorrow?
Really! Yay!
Bye, Toyotomi!
Unlucky...
At last, Akina gave up on Toyotomi...
Is Akina really never going to come back to him?
In the end, regardless of Akina's true feelings,
the Luckless Flowers quietly bloomed on the moorland.
Please look
forward
to the
next one!
A quiet mahjong parlor
in a Port Town in the Snowy Country.
But even here, in the the "Northern Button" Parlor, the life thrives.
Next time: Gambling Trip Zugan,
Part 1 and Part 2.
Definitely watch it!
Don't fall asleep!