Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Akina-chan!
Hey, Akina-chan!
S-So, Akina-chan...
Oh. It's just Toyotomi-kun.
Looks like she's in a bad mood.
I-It's not like I bumped into you
on purpose, Akina!
So...
Toyotomi-kun.
Are you repeating a year?
Episode 18 Part 1
Welcome to the Mahjungle
I get it… So they're holding me back a year?
We're working adults now.
We're a different race from students like you
who can slack off all the time.
But I thought we were friends...
Hey, Toyotomi!
Congrats on your extra year!
You're hopeless, just going to the parlor day in, day out...
No wonder you couldn't get enough credits!
Th-Those suits...
We've washed our hands of mahjong a long time ago.
Starting this spring,
we're first-year working adults!
Ya were a little slow to notice, huh.
N-No way in hell!
I've gotten completely fed up with you.
Farewell, Toyotomi-kun!
Bye-bye!
Akina-chan!
Akina-chan...
We're in the same year now!
Let's be good friends!
Hey, kouhai!
From now we're even! Even!
Oi boss, somethin' wrong with me face?
No... What did I do last night?
Oh? Ya don't remember anythin', mate?
Ya got drunk as a skunk
in Shibuya to drown ya worries!
Drown my worries? Me? Why?
'Cause you failed a year!
Am I really not gonna make it
to the graduation this year?!
'Course you won't! Ya failed to advance
from third to fourth year.
Not to mention the graduation...
What was that?
So you won't be in fourth year...
Before that!
Boss?
Say it again!
Boss!
Come on, say it again!
Stop buggering me!
We gotta go to work!
First
Building
Welcome!
Hey, coffee please!
Here you go, sir!
I need a hot towel!
Yes, sir!
I heard Toyotomi had to repeat a year...
I thought he'd be depressed,
but he looks so cheerful!
Yeah, this morning he was a bit off his rocker, though.
I wonder if he'll be right.
Hey, fill in for me, please!
Fill-in coming!
East 4, exactly at starting points, I see.
All right, I'm the dealer.
DORA
I've got to play toward a quick win,
but what to discard...
DORA
First I'll get rid of 2s and 8s!
Oi, kid, get on with it!
Y-Yes sir...
Start with this and see what I draw!
Oh, you drew the backfire straight away.
If I draw 3s, it'll be fine.
The flow is toward souzu. I'll cut the pinzu penchan!
Don't worry!
It's still only the early game.
DORA
That's right, nothing to despair about!
I can still make 234 sanshoku!
DORA
I'll cut the dora early!
Unless I draw another dora now!
Z-Zugan.
If I cut it, I draw it...
It's really the law of cut-and-draw!
Oh? I'll pon that.
I just drew the pair.
N-No way...
I wonder why he's so unlucky.
Why?
Take the 58s furiten!
DORA
On turn 5 I've got furiten on both 58s and 14p!
And I've missed a 234s sequence!
DORA
And I've let that guy call his dora pair! This is bad!
I've got to do something
before that customer gets back!
Wh-What's this?! What's going on?
You just need to stay in
for a little more, okay?
Ah, now that you mention,
I've still got some left...
Isn't that right? So take your time
to make sure you leave with no regrets! Okay?
Who is it?
It's your turn to discard.
All right!
10 tiles...
And 2 more tiles...
Totals 12.
I've got too few tiles...
I-I've got to struggle through this round
somehow without getting found out...
What's wrong, Mister Waiter?
You look pale.
N-Nothing.
Nothing at all!
I-I've got a bit
of a toothache since yesterday...
The hell? Did I have the top draws?
Mister, these things can happen
with an autotable...
Sometimes the top
and bottom draws shift...
I-Is that really so?
A-Anyway, this round
I just have to be thorough and fold!
Suji!
Just let the round end
with nothing happening...
Ron! It's a really bad wait though!
Toitoi ton dora 3! Haneman!
Zugan!
Now I'm fully rested!
Hold it!
Uh? What? What's going on?!
I-I'm sorry sir,
it seems the door went off the hinges!
Dora.
Pon!
All right...
If I win this, I'm even!
It's only turn 5, as good as won!
I'm just thinking—he should just tsumogiri that 3m straight away.
Well, maybe...
Boss is an adeptchad so he'll kan it.
No way.
Don't just assume whatever you want!
Just watch, okay?
In this case a pro would...
Cut this one!
H-He's sharp!
4-sided wait
If he cuts 3m, it's a 4-sided wait on 1247m...
But with 9m, it's a 5-sided wait on 12458m!
5-sided wait
B-Boss, I kneel!
So, do you respect me a bit more now?
I've always admired ya, boss!
C'mon!
The discerning viewers should already know which tile he has drawn.
Super Zugan!
Ron! Riichi tanyao pinfu sanshoku, 8,000!
Zu...
Well, thanks for filling in for me, I'm back!
Zugan!
You must be feeling unwell since you've spent there so long, here's a hot towel!
Oh, yes, much obliged...
Extra big cup of coffee and tea!
Really?!
And a special Yokult delivery—
on the house!
And I'll light your cigarette!
After that, a massage!
Really?
And now, pick one for mother...
Pick two for father...
And a flower bouquet for the customer!
Oh-ho! You're making me feel kinda bad, I don't deserve all this...
Not at all, these are my true feelings...
So please enjoy your day!
Amazing! Double riichi!
The infernal mahjong waiter, Toyotomi.
Whoever asks him to fill in
is already dead.
Hey, can you fill in for me?
Yes, I'll be right there!
Toyotomi will probably
repeat a year in mahjong too...
Wuh? I'm on my last ball!
No! Not there!
Wuh the hell!
Another 5,000 yen
down the drain! Zugan! Goddammit!
Let's get engaged!
Rie?!
Akechi-kun!
Yikes...
Who the hell are you?
What's going on?
What's going on? Well...
You could say my love's cooled off...
You shameless rake!
Come on, let's talk...
All right! C'mon!
Faster, you fuck!
No.5-6! 5-6!
GOOD KIDS ABSTAIN FROM INSTITUTIONALIZED GAMBLING.
Damn it, I lost!
All of this month's part-time
money gone to shit!
Ey, I'm walkin' 'ere, you fuck!
What? You asking for it?!
Akechi?
Shintaro!
Wuh's goin' on, you twerps?
Yasu?!
The hell you both
bumpin' into me here?
Man, I'm completely out of luck.
The waves of a downturn in my luck are even reaching into my private life.
Damn right!
Pachinko's no way to make money!
And my women are dumping me...
If that's the case, we'll just go
cleanse ourselves of bad luck!
Yeah!
Episode 18 Part 2
Mahjong Rules 101
First
Building
So, anyone needs filling in?
A substitute runner is at the ready!
What's goin' on, boss?
Never seen ya be such an eager beaver!
Something nice must've happened to him.
No, not in particular...
C'mon, tell us!
I got it, Boss! You're going
on a date with Akina-san, right?
How did you know?
And afterwards just the two of you in Akina's room...
C-Cut it out, you...
As soon as the background music stops,
the two of you lock eyes...
Toyotomi-kun...
Akina-chan!
Ah! No! You fool! Stop it...
Toyotomi-kun, there're some customers
calling from that table!
They say they went to play with you!
O-Okay.
Hey, Toyotomi.
How've ya been?
Long time no see!
Uhh, my shift is almost over
so I'll go home
and let you guys have fun
with someone else...
Toyotomi! Your friends
came over just to see you!
What's with this attitude?!
You've gotta value your friendships more.
But my date...
All right, I'll be the first dealer!
Hey, first dealer!
No, me!
That's it! I'm starting dealer!
S-Starting dealer!
Wuh?! I ain't lost yet, ya know!
Could you guys tone it down a little bit?
Okay.
What?
It's rude to the other customers.
Wuh's that, Toyotomi?! Since when do you boss it over people like that?! Huh?!
Calm down...
We can play it quietly too.
Even if he works here,
it won't help him in the game!
I'll vent my piled up frustration all at once...
All right! Ippatsu!
Riichi tile suji trap!
The only one who'd deal in is Toyotomi, so predictable!
Sir, that's a chombo.
You don't have a yaku.
Huh? You dumbass, look closer!
I called riichi! Riichi!
Riichi is only applied when you say "riichi,"
put out a 1,000 point stick and turn the tile 90 degrees.
Not declaring vocally and not putting
a riichi stick makes this not a valid riichi.
What's with that strict attitude?
It's because ya said we shouldn't make a noise, that I...
No, he's got a point.
I also agree with Toyotomi.
Gib chombo!
You bastards...
All right, I get it! Ya're both out of luck
so you're gonna fuck me over, huh?
Choke on it!
Riichi, asshole!
Here! Now you've got no right to complain!
WAIT
Chase riichi.
What's this guy's deal?
He didn't put a riichi stick
like he said you should!
What a nitwit.
Oh no...
Waiting tiles
I can't cut this...
Ah! The fuck ya doin'?
Ya're in riichi!
Please, sir...
I just told you!
If I don't put a stick,
it doesn't count as riichi.
The hell?!
And I haven't put one, have I?
Therefore, I'm not in riichi.
In other words, I can discard any tile.
You motherfucker...
Oh, nice draw!
Chase riichi!
Waiting tiles
All right! This time it's the real deal!
Damn it! What makes you think
you can do that?1
It's over!
Ron!
The hell?!
Goddammit! What a bunch of bull!
Sir, please don't put
your knee above the table.
Shut your bitch ass up!
Discard your tiles softly.
Ugh! Stop bitchin' about my every move!
Uhh, what to do...
Call!
Sir...
Once you've touched the wall,
you can't call.
Wutcha talkin' about?
I didn't touch it!
Forensics!
Yessir!
Detective, it is Yasu's fingerprint, all right!
How about that?
Would you still claim your innocence?
B-But I must've touched it last round!
You've incriminated yourself, Yasube!
W-Wuh?!
On an autotable, there are two sets of tiles with different colored backs!
Therefore, there's no way you could've touched this set when it's only East 2!
O-Oh no...!
I see... You really don't want me
to pon that chun...
It's the rules.
I get it! I'll just tsumo it instead!
Tsumogiri!
Pon!
Hey! I just remembered it's East 3!
My fingerprint could've been there from East 1!
Slow... way too slow.
Damn it all!
It came out! 2,600!
Chii!
Don't need it!
Ron! Chanta honitsu nan! Mangan!
He's good! With this form, he might even get first for the first time in this parlor!
Oh?
N-no way...
This round's gonna go to draw...
All right, riichi!
What? No way he called riichi!
There's only 4 tiles left in the regular wall! That means he's only got 1 draw left!
No! This isn't an ordinary riichi!
I-It's a 16-sided wait riichi!
Wut? 16-sided wait?
You all right, Mama-san?
Take a good look at my discards...
What do we have here?
What the hell you makin' a fuss ab—
One discard away from nagashi mangan!
And a 258m sanmenchan to boot!
Together with the 13 kinds of terminal and honors,
he's a got an unbeatable 16-sided wait!
Come on! Somebody call! 1p!
No good, I can't call it! Call the nan!
I already drew! Call the 9p please!
All right!
What?
Ugh!
Whaat?!
Tsumo! Nagashi mangan!
Mama-san, does this parlor even play with nagashi mangan?
Ah! Not, actually! Not at all! I forgot!
Here! As you can see, at Ichibankan, we do not consider nagashi mangan to be a yaku!
Sorry... We just changed that rule last week.
What?! No way!
Playing at the parlor where you work
without even knowing your own rules...
It's rude to the customers, isn't it?
I think we should get
a chombo payment for this.
Well, we're all generous here so we'll give ya a pass.
Zugan.
Ron! 7,700!
First: others are always luckier.
Ron! 12,000!
Second: born under an unlucky star.
Ron! 18,000!
Third: everyone sees dreams
as much as you do.
First
Building
Fourth: only when finally in tenpai.
First
Building
Fifth: when in chase Riichi, always denied.
First
Building
Sixth: for your draw, it's always ippatsu tile.
First
Building
Ron!
First
Building
Ron!
First
Building
Ron! Mama-san,
do you play with triple ron?
First
Building
Of course!
First
Building
Zugaaan!
First
Building
It's the cold season.
Take care not to catch a cold!
Now then, on a winter evening
of dancing blizzards...
What did Toyotomi dream
while sleeping alone?
Next time: "South Pole Zugan"
and "Nouveau Riche Zugan."
Don't miss it!
Don't want to you to sleep on it!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Raw provider
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa