Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to tree years.
All right, I'm in tenpai!
It's a 2547p wait, but haneman isn't enough for first place!
It's clear from my discards I have single suit hand anyway...
I have no choice but to...
Call riichi and draw the winning tile myself!
As long as I don't draw the Dora 5m, I can win!
Episode 1 Part 1
Springtime for the Luckless
C'mon, ippatsu tsumo!
Zu—
Ron! Tanyao pinfu sanshoku iipeikou Dora Dora!
Zugan...
Double ron! Shousangen Dora Dora!
Ron! Honroutou toitoi hatsu Dora 3!
Zugan!
My apologies! Riichi junchan ippatsu tsumo, 6000 all! My pleasure!
The first bell tolls for my father...
The second bell tolls for my mother...
The third bell tolls for me!
Th-Those voices!
We've been waiting for you!
IOU ¥30,000
IOU ¥20,000
We're...
IOU ¥40,000
Here to collect these!
Don't let him get away!
Get him!
Whaaat?!
This'll pay for the rent!
Wut? He's got only 30,000 left!
Tsk! Listen up! You gotta earn
at least 100,000 next month, got it?
Salary
So, where do we go for drinks tonight?
What about that new Race Queen Pub?
I like that! I really do!
Z-Zugan...
I'm sorry!
It's you...
Isn't that you, Toyotomi-kun?
It's me!
Your classmate from high school, Akina!
I see...
They took your entire monthly wage?
And they even took
your furniture and futon?
That's awful.
Say, Toyotomi-kun...
Do you still remember the days
when we were in high school?
You were really sparkling with life back then.
All right. Now, for this problem...
Here. Blue ribbons, I win.
Tsk...
Tokugawa, answer this.
Huh?
What's f(x) and g(x)?
Yeah, sure. It's...
Why can't you give it at least a bit of thought?!
Whatever. Why don't we ask Toyotomi to answer that instead?
Yessir! f(x) = k(e²ˣ-1), g(x) = ½(e²ˣ+1)!
Yes! Remarkable, Toyotomi!
You should all follow his example!
You're making me blush!
Oh no! I lost to you again, Toyotomi-kun!
Honor Roll
I just got lucky this time around, Hayami-san.
Not at all, it was your own ability.
Hey, Toyotomi-kun. What do you want to be when you graduate?
A teacher!
The young people these days don't know what to live for.
So I want to become a teacher who can show them how wonderful the life is!
That's so cool!
Back then, your eyes were sparkling
with dreams and hopes.
But that shining suddenly disappeared when were were in our senior year...
Zugan...
I-I don't play mahjong!
We know you do. Don't hide it.
Bastard! Are ya telling us yer parents
didn't teach you to play mahjong at home since you were a kid?!
Ya just don't wanna
hang out with us, is that it?
I-If only for one hanchan!
From then on, your life took a big downturn...
Dat's how it's done, li'l bro!
789 sanshoku with guaranteed junchan?!
Will they get angry if I tsumo this kind of dealer haneman in East 1?
Riichi!
6s is the Dora...
Maybe a 47s wait crossing the Dora...?
Oh, rats!
Damn it, there's no way I can cut this!
Pinfu sanshoku is 5800, so I'll avoid ippatsu and play it safe!
All right! Chase riichi!
Three of the 8p are out...
It's not likely to be a pinzu wait.
It's probably something like 36m or 47m?
I can't push this!
6m is dangerous to them both, and there's two out already!
Two discards
It's awfully dangerous!
Even if I lose sanshoku, it can't be helped!
Wut are these draws?!
Ippatsu!... would have been nice.
Skillful mawashi!
Tsumo!
Pinfu tsumo! 700 all!
Wut?
Ya could've had junchan sanshoku!
Yeah, but you see...
I held back this 4s against your riichi!
That's not my wait, you dumbass!
And I had a Mangan too...
Hatsu sanshoku Dora 1 waiting on 5m kanchan?!
It's not even a suji trap, and still a Mangan if he stays dama!
B-But, this definitely would have dealt into your riichi, right?
Nope, not at all. Ugh.
Riichi sanankou dora 1! Such a good hand and I got unlucky!
Why did he cut his pair of 6p with that hand?!
What the hell is his problem?
Why did I turn my junchan sanshoku 6000 all into a pinfu tsumo nomi 700 all?!
Riichi!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Ippatsu tsumo!
Huh? Wait, really?
That's the same tile you called riichi with!
Ugh... I'm really unlucky tonight...
Riichi ippatsu tsumo pinfu dora dora. Just a haneman.
If I can't even ippatsu tsumo the 1m with this, it's fucking over for me...
You're right...
You also missed a baiman.
Are you off your rocker or something?
What are these guys talking about?!
All right! Riichi!
What's up with these discards...
Let's cut 1p.
Ippatsu!
Wh-What the...
Riichi ippatsu dora dora.
Damn it, Akechi, yer good at this!
Oh no, I was just bluffing really well.
Even a pro wouldn't have expected that!
If he drew any manzu, he'd be in tenpai for baiman!
Wut?!
Looks like I got a tad too many tiles, look!
One, two, three, four, tile tile tile...
Oh! You're right! Ya got 17 tiles!
Haha! Then I can just discard these four. Here!
The penalty for too many tiles is a dead hand!
Wut!?
Why the hell does it have to be so harsh?!
It's not professional mahjong,
we can make an exception!
Exactly!
This is ridiculous!
Ron! Best out! Tanyao pinfu sanshoku iipeikou!
Zugaaaaan!
Three years have passed...
During those, those guys
too away everything you had...
Before!
After...
Toyotomi-kun, please!
Go back to how you were three years ago!
I... I...
I was in love with you back then!
Toyotomi-kun!
Howdy!
Toyotomi-kun! You're the Toyotomi-kun from back then, right? Is that you?
Toyotomi-kun!
Long time no see!
Please...
Stop playing mahjong, okay?
"Stop playing mahjong, okay?"
Along with the pouring autumn rain,
Akina's words seeped forever and ever
deep into Toyotomi's heart.
South 3, North seat, 10th turn, 16400 points Tsumo 5p, dora 8p
6s
Read RB1
Seems like that prick
is serious about quitting.
What should we do?
If he quits mahjong,
our lifestyle is finished!
Don'tcha worry 'bout it!
The stench of mahjong's soaked deep into his body.
It ain't somethin' you can just wipe off!
Episode 1 Part 2
Severance Zugan
Toyotomi-kun!
Wh-What's...
...Going on?!
Hey! Welcome, guys!
D-Don't hesitate.
Let's get to it.
C'mon, Toyotomi!
We're picking seats. Draw yours!
I've quit mahjong.
Don't be such a buzzkill!
Can't you hear it?
The lamentation of the tiles
you've cast aside...
The lamentations of the tiles?
Can't you see how lonely they're feeling without your attention?
Toyotomi!
Wh-What the...
I understand your feelings all too well.
If your determination to give up mahjong and live properly is so firm,
I shan't say anything against it.
However, Toyo-san...
One must not leave the matters unresolved, you know.
Unresolved?
Play one last farewell game with us!
That's all I ask!
Farewell game?!
I expect you to play no less than 10 final hanchan.
Whaat? You can't be serious!
10 hanchan is way too...
All right! Let's get crackin'!
Yeah!
You're the starting dealer!
Serves you right!
Idiot! I'm the best at being starting dealer!
Chun!
Lucky! Now that's a spicy tile!
Piss off!
Ton!
Wuss wrong, Toyotomi?
C'mon, it's yer turn!
You've been silent for a while.
Cheer up, man!
Please... Stop playing mahjong, okay?
No! This is just a farewell game!
Dora
I'll just play the 10 final hanchan
and be done with these guys!
A-All right... I'll focus on playing calmly and extremely carefully...
Professional defensive hedgehog mahjong!
Chii!
What's up with you?!
Don't call on the first turn!
It begins.
He's playing the "poor" mahjong...
Calling a ryanmen on turn one...
Hatsu!
Pon!
He didn't call the chun the dealer cut on his first turn...
Ron! Merciless bandit mahjong!
Shousangen honitsu chanta!
Zugan...
I got one dora, so that's a baiman!
What the hell? Winning without drawing even once?!
Winning with your haipai...
Well, there's no avoiding slipping up like this at least once in 10 hanchan...
It just happened to be at the very start!
east 2 south seat turn 7
All right! Let's win big with this hand!
Dora
Since 47s is dangerous, I'll cut it early!
That's it!
With 2m ippatsu tsumo, it's mentanpin ippatsu tsumo sanshoku!
Dora
I can counter with my own baiman!
Ri-Riichi!
Wut's that? Here's a ton! Someone call it!
Ton? That's a pon from me.
Let's break his ippatsu.
C'mon, draw the 2m!
Please...
The 1m, you say?
Wait a second, I'll call kan on that.
P-Pass.
I drew this one from the rinshan!
Thank god!
At least the 47s is mostly used up!
What are you thinking about?
Get on with it!
You're in riichi, aren't you?
Rather than deal into dealer's haneman, I'll call 4s kan and pay the penalty for noten riichi...
Kan!
1m is the new dora again...
Shucks... Should have gone for the shanpon wait.
Pon!
That means Akechi changed to a 5s tanki wait!
Don't draw it!
The tile... The tile is calling to me!
C-Could it be...
Hey, wutcha doin'?
Just draw already!
We haven't got to touch the tiles for two turns now!
Get on with it!
Okay... Let's do it.
Oh man, I even get to win a hand like this...
Ron!
Double ton and uhh...
11 dora! That's a kazoe yakuman!
Super zugan!
Hmm, I see...
Dora
So that's how it is...
It's finally my time to shine. Let's go!
What are you thinking about?
Riichi!
We could tell you had Gyoza today...
There, pei!
Pass!
Genbutsu!
Shintaro would've been a fine fella if he didn't fart so much!
Shaa!
Pass!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Ippatsu tsumo!
I tsumo'd!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo tanyao dora 4!
I don't understand!!!
Zugan...
Please... Stop playing mahjong, okay?
That's right! At this rate,
I won't be able to quit mahjong!
There's no way in hell
I'm gonna lose that easily!
Huh? Ya cut the 6p?!
Huh? No, I slipped up!
Just a little off.
I actually cut this.
Whoa, the 8p came out?!
O-Oops! I grabbed the tile
next to it again, sorry!
Well, this is the real one!
Did it pass?
Ron!
My best out!
You finally cut it, you nincompoop!
We were playing with triple ron, weren't we!
I've got pinfu sanshoku dora 1!
I've got honitsu chun sanankou. Haneman.
For me...
Yakuman!
Well then. That should be it.
We'll be taking this.
We'll drop by again soon!
You wanted to cut ties with mahjong,
but actually it only deepened our ties!
Man, talk about irony!
Having broken his promise to Akina-chan,
Toyotomi falls deeper yet into mahjong hell.
Will the bright future she envisioned for him ever materialize?
Zugan...
Ugh, that Toyotomi-kun! He used to be so dreamy, but now he's a husk of his former self.
Whatever!
Next time on Super Zugan:
"Happy Birthday Zugan"
and "Rejected Zugan."
Definitely watch it!
Cut on sleeping if you have to!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go "Zugan!"
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle of unmatched wits!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go "Zugan!"
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/ board
Perevodildo
Muzussawa