Okay, let's go for it.
Yeah, good.
Give me just a moment.
Pon.
Oh? Calling already?
Early calling breeds self-destruction.
Pon.
Hey, didn't we warn you earlier?
Early calling breeds self-destruction.
This ain't gonna go well for you, buddy.
It changes the flow of tiles too much.
Kan.
Tsumo.
Toitoi Kan-tsumo Dora 3.
It's a haneman.
Tsk... I'm all out of luck.
I'll have to pay it myself.
And this north was the fourth tile. All right!
By the way, aren't you that mysterious mahjong rogue they talk about lately?
Always with a cigarette in your right hand and a nervous look.
Pon.
Oh, a toitoi chanta?
Discarding the 2-sou after a 1-sou pon, huh?
That's nasty.
Well, either way you can only have Honitsu, or perhaps Chanta?
Now, what should I cut here?
Discarding the 2-sou after the 1-sou pon means
he could've had a wait on a 3-sou, which means...
The dora, 5-sou, is dangerous.
This is a war of nerves.
Just what is on his mind?
Make a move already.
The clock is ticking,
and it ain't just for you.
You jerk!
Stop playing dumb!
W-What is it?! Can it be a ron?
Ron.
Xia Chun Toitoi, mangan.
A shanpon on middle tiles?
You fucker threw that 2-sou as a trap!
Manager, this ain't looking good.
If we put that rogue up against those guys, they'll cause some trouble for sure.
It's just some punk who doesn't know his place.
If he keeps playing like that,
he'll get himself killed anyway.
Oh, that's a pon!
Hey buddy, regret calling that already?
If you were going for a 123 Sanshoku...
you'd want to call the 2-sou here.
Kan!
There, I finally caught up.
Buddy, flip the kan-dora, will ya?
Whoa, that's not bad either!
You only get that by kanning! Luck's on my side now.
Honitsu Toitoi Chun Dora 4, baiman. Alright, let's end this in one shot!
You're not in this for much longer.
Pon!
Tell me, bud, you said I'm not in this for longer - what did you mean by that?
You'd better explain yourself, lest we arrive to some painful misunderstanding.
How'd ya like it? I have San-kantsu on top of it now!
That's Ron.
What? Ron?
Didn't ya just pon the 3-sou now?
Asshole! Think you can get away with making fun of me?!
You bastard!
I am Ishikawa Takashi, the second boss of the Kai Group,
here to represent the interests of my predecessor Kai Shozo.
And you are the Dragon.
D-Did you say Dragon?
The Calling Dragon?
Dragon, our boss risked his life investigating you, just to see you
Hold it, you dipshit!
Didn't you hear me telling you to stop?!
Let him go.
On that day, Kai Shouzou lived within Dragon.
Kai Shozo raised Ishikawa Takashi and always looked after him,
because he believed Ishikawa to be capable of carrying on his back the future
of the Kai Group and the entire Oudou Syndicate.
Ishikawa arrived at a certain general hospital in Tokyo.
He was there to check on Sakurada Michizo,
the head of the Oudou Syndicate, who was shot at
by a member of Miyoshi Group because of their prolonged feud with the Kai Group.
For Ishikawa, that meant that everyone's expectations of him were set high.
You guys will wait here.
"High expectations."
Namely, the dying wish of the head of the Kai Group,
former lieutenant of the Oudou Syndicate, Kai Shozo,
that would become his final assignment for Ishikawa.
Good job, boys.
Sorry to ask, but could you kick that door open for me?
With all due respect, sir,
this place is run by the Kawachi Group.
No one is allowed to enter without the boss' permission.
Oh? Interesting, I didn't know that.
I am Ishikawa, the second boss of the Kai Group,
and yet he still won't open for me?
Coward! Open this door at once!
Now, if it isn't boss Kawachi?
Long time no see.
Ishikawa, what did you come here for?
I've been put in charge of boss' hospital room. It's none of your business.
I came to check on the boss.
What was that?
Are you seriously telling me that you didn't know that only those
who shared a cup of sake with the old man can get to meet him?
The reason I came here today is to share a cup with the boss.
What?!
Ishikawa, who do you think you are
to be allowed to drink sake with him?
Mind you, it was the fight your predecessor, Kai started,
that brought our old man to this state.
Ishikawa, you asshole!
Ishikawa...
I'm not moving an inch from here until I get to share a cup with him!
Oudou and Kai are the two strongest organizations in Eastern Japan,
with undisputed mastery over the Kanto region.
That makes the Kai Group, with 2,000 men in its ranks,
the most important group in my organization.
They won't tolerate anyone messing with their "night" businesses.
If you hit them, they hit back two or three times harder.
That's the Yakuza for you.
I'm not interested in listening to your boasting.
I'm going home.
Wait, Dragon.
Come on, Dragon. You know I'll make you mine.
I am quite certain that you have it in you -
the thing I'm looking for.
You're absolutely fearless,
that's an important gift.
But not as much as your extraordinary luck.
I knew it ever since we first met at the boss's mansion -
you're a monster, who lives by fighting alone.
So? Why don't you become mine and keep growing as a player?
It seems, the boss also has a lot of admiration for you.
Sorry, but I answer to nobody. I'm not anyone's property.
Dragon, I carry on my back the lives of 2,000 members of the Kai Group.
What of it?
Dragon, you shouldn't humiliate me like that with your rudeness.
I need to set an example for everyone!
Chi.
You're hoarding souzu tiles this time, huh.
Hey, buddy, don't get carried away.
You may have been winning so far,
but it was through sheer luck.
Mahjong is a game you can only win if you have the skill.
Watch closely, buddy. I'm about to show you what real mahjong is.
There it goes!
It's true that only one thing matters in mahjong.
It's the victory.
Chi!
Y-You! It wasn't souzu?!
Dragon...
What was that?
Gunshots?!
Ron.
Dragon... Dragon, you...
Dragon! Give me your luck!
Give it to the old man, Dragon!
Ishikawa may enter.
Why?
The boss is going to meet him.
Shozo...
Please, ma'am,
take good care of Ishikawa.
With time, he'll be the only man strong enough
to carry the fate of Oudou and Kai on his back.
The only thing that can defeat him is luck.
If he had luck, he could be the man to rule over all of Japan!
Sakurada Michizo's last child, Ishikawa Takashi, is now born.
Dragon...
You continuously kept refusing even my predecessor, the first boss,
but I, Ishikawa, will definitely make you play for me.
With your luck, I can become the best in Japan.
Hey, bud, how are you planning to get out of this?
Kan.
The one crying will be you.
Dragon. Dragon!
I just wished to spend one more joyous evening playing mahjong with you.
B-Bastard! You'll regret making fun of the Yakuza!
I'll kill you!
Dragon, come with us for a moment.
Boss Ishikawa is determined to play against you.
D-Dragon? The Calling Dragon?
If you refuse...
You'll die.
Tell this to your Ishikawa: my life...
My very cheap life, is heavily overestimated.
Hey, Ishikawa's goons!
Ain't you taking the tough image too far?
I guess the whole group starts acting up when the boss changes, eh?!
I'll have you know that the guy you've got a gun on is one of my men!
Hold it, Dragon.
Who said you can leave?
Say, it must be fate that we meet again here.
It's been a long while
since you last played me.
What? Murota took Dragon?
Yes.
Murota said if you want Dragon, you must take him by force.
Ugh... I see.
So Murota took Dragon...
That guy is using Dragon to try me.
Try me, Ishikawa Takashi!
How should I deal with him?
How would a man, entrusted with the lives of 2,000 men by the first boss, act?
It took me ten years to be able to speak in front of the president.
Do you understand, dragon?
You said you hate the Yakuza right off the bat.
We're going to the Umemiya Gambling House where we first met.
I'm still amazed by your method of playing even now when I remember it.
Just doing one pon after the other and gettin' a Tsuuisou like that.
Isn't that right?
Is that woman I rewarded you with doing well?
I was also the one who introduced you to the boss after that.
Imbecile! When you meet the boss,
you greet him with a bow!
The memory of his encounter with Kaito was brought back to life in Dragon's mind.
It's your turn.
Oops.
Tsumo.
Pinfu Ittsuu. Right.
Tanyao Iipeiko.
2,000 all.
Aren't you a Yakuza?
Hm? What'd you just say, kid?
Isn't it considered shameful for a Yakuza to deceive others?
Why don't you take those sunglasses off?
Looks like the fun and games are over, Shozo.
It seems I'm losing my knack, boss.
To think I'd be caught by a kid of all people...
Not bad, kid.
It looks like Murota didn't even notice.
Hey! Boss Kai is calling you!
Come back!
If he needs something,
he can come with his own feet.
You prick!
Hey, you can't lay a finger on that guy!
That guy is mine,
let him do as he pleases.
Pon.
Dragon, it's better that you don't take the Yakuza lightly.
You can be quite well-off with us.
What do you say, huh?
Chi.
Professional gamblers deceive people for a living.
Dragon, aren't they the perfect prey for you?
Ron.
I hit the bull's-eye, didn't I?
You even gave up on a San-ankou to make me draw that.
You've done well, for some feeble 1,000 points.
Come clean, you.
Huh? Don't mess with me!
Pon.
Goin' for a Ryuuiisou now?
Dragon, it seems to me you never lose.
But those who don't know the pain of losing, don't know what a true battle is.
He who gets up first after a defeat is the strongest.
Riichi!
Dragon, I'm going to let you taste the anguish of defeat now.
You're not in this for much longer.
What? What do you mean I'm not in this for longer?!
Pon.
Wh-What?
You're calling the tile you just discarded you bastard?
Asshole, it ain't a Ryuuiisou?
You don't carry the burden of even a single person on your back.
Unwavering faith in yourself is required to win.
If the taste of defeat still lingers in your mouth, you've already lost.
Kawachi sent his small fry for us.
If you know that I'm the second boss of the Kai Group,
Ishikawa Takashi, don't hesitate
and shoot!
Can't hit me, huh?
This bulletproof glass is the proof the Kai Clan has nothing to fear from you!
The conference was a mess, wasn't it?
Even before the boss' memorial service was over, a huge internal feud broke out.
The rumor is some men from the Kawachi Group
already went missing without a trace.
Wasn't it the Kai Group who did it?
Some say, the Kawachi Group fabricated it themselves.
But that guy Ishikawa Takashi, the current leader of the Kai Group,
has great acumen, isn't that what they say?
Dragon knew it full well -
it won't be long before Ishikawa Takashi would stand in his way.
It was his intuition of a man who had lived his whole live amidst conflict.
Dragon's blood was boiling.
Pon.
Got no time for a kan, eh.
It's a ron.
Chinitsu Toitoi Tanyao!
I see. I've heard the rumors, but it seems even they don't do you justice.
Are you Miyoshi-san?
So you knew who I was from the start?
It's not my first game with a Yakuza.
Wh-What was that?
F-Fuckers...
K-Kai…
Long time no see, Dragon. You're just one tile away from Suukantsu, eh?
I was looking for you,
but I also got to meet Miyoshi, it seems.
I should be grateful to you.
Spare me your thanks.
Just calling off your dogs that follow my every step would be enough.
You're as unamiable as ever.
Motherfucker...
Now then...
Miyoshi, it's your turn.
What's taking you so long?
Kan.
It's over.
I'm waiting, Dragon.
You and me still have a game to play.
Dragon, you always play with your life on the line.
For that reason, I'll put my life on the line as well.
It'll be our first and last life-or-death battle!
The battle that night was impressed vividly into Dragon's mind.
It was at the metropolitan office of the Oudou Syndicate
where Boss Sakurada invited his close associate,
Maruko Sadagoro, for a game with Dragon.
Chi.
Pon.
Dragon, if I win, you'll be mine.
And if you win, you're free to do whatever you want with my life.
Chi!
Pon!
Kai has been calling in retaliation to Dragon.
Audentes fortuna iuvat.
This was the tactic that Maruko taught Kai.
Chun Honitsu!
That night, it was as though Kai pulled tiles at will.
He had the heavens on his side.
At last, "All Last."
Dragon discarded the 5-pin and I can see all 4 of them.
The 7-pin is safe.
Chi.
A closed 7-pin!
Dragon, was that Chi necessary?
If you can't win with a haneman tsumo or a sanbaiman from one of us...
you got no chance to win.
I'm not stealing tiles with my calls.
I'm imbuing them with life.
Stop meddling in my affairs.
Another 7-pin, what a hassle.
What on earth is Dragon waiting on?
Could it be another 7-pin?
It can't be pinzu again...
It'll be fine, I'm in luck today!
The heavens are on my side.
Shozo!
Shozo, what's wrong?
I-It's nothing.
Sit the fuck down and relax.
Dragon! Let's settle this!
It's over.
D-Dragon...
Hey, Dragon...
Shozo, think about yourself.
What a wonderful victory!
Hold up, Dragon.
You haven't forgotten about the settlement, have you?!
A promise is a promise!
You must take my life now!
Wait a minute, Dragon.
If you have a hint of humanity in you,
how can you leave without even acknowledging Kai's words?
My daughter... Kai's wife,
she didn't tell anyone else, but...
A 12 mm bullet has lodged in his lung.
It needs to be taken out as soon as possible!
However, he only has a fifty-fifty chance of surviving the operation...
He absolutely refused to undergo the surgery!
My daughter held onto me as she cried....
He only has three months left...
And Kai bet those three months
on you!
Don't say another word, old man...
You're making me look pathetic.
What's wrong, Dragon?
Hurry up and take my life!
Dragon!
Didn't you say that you're carrying the burden of 2,000 people on your back?
Cherish that burden.
Dragon...
B-Boss!
What? The boss was shot?!
They sent an armed assassin?!
Kai was right there with him -
what's the meaning of this?!
I beg you humbly.
Don't let the boss perish now.
All I've done up to this point
was to expedite his ascent to the position of the strongest boss in all of Japan.
You may claim my own life several times over!
But don't let the boss perish now!
I'm begging you humbly...
I felt you might come home today.
I've been waiting here for quite a while.
"Auspicious Alliance", huh?
Quite the witty name they've picked.
No matter what happens, that stinking scum doesn't seem to know what shame is.
Men that have no shame don't deserve to live.
Isn't that right, Tamura?
Boss... Today's the day.
Oh, is that so? Finally the day of his weekly visit to his mistress?
Yes. We have people on standby at her apartment complex.
Tamura, get out of the country by tomorrow.
You can kick back and relax in Manila. Sounds good, doesn't it?
At that moment, a seed of uneasiness
sprouted in Ishikawa's mind.
Tsumo!
He hoped to dispel that uneasiness with the ura dora...
However...
he couldn't find even a scrap of good luck.
Stop!
It must have been a lot of work.
To think that the bait I've set would work this well...
It seems, Ishikawa also underestimates me.
In other news,
At Narita Bypass around 6 a.m. this morning, a car had burst into flames.
The passengers were all pronounced dead at the scene.
Based on his personal belongings, one of the victims
was identified as Tamura Koichi,
from the Kai Group, part of the Oudou Syndicate.
Additionally, bullet marks were found on the bodies.
Some suggest that it was related to the shootout
that occurred at an apartment complex in Setagaya last night.
The authorities believe
that this is one of a growing number of internal conflicts within the Oudou Group.
An emergency investigation
into the "Auspicious Alliance", that split off from that organization, has started.
This was Ishikawa Takashi's first taste
of humiliation, which shook his determination to the core.
It seemed like one man was looking at him
through a clearing in the dark clouds, sneering at him.
That man was not Kawachi,
and it was certainly not Murota....
2,000 lives were weighing heavily on Ishikawa's back.
It's Dragon! Bring that goddamn Dragon to me!
Ishikawa Takashi went for the only gamble that could support his plans.
Look, I got a tsumo!
Menhon ittsuu tsumo, double nan...
A baiman!
Looks like you're out of luck today.
The point gap is almost 8,000 points now!
How'd ya like a little hanchan with a sashiuma between us?
What's the rate?
How does a hand sound? Plus time.
That is, if I win, you'll have to give me a hand, and come with me for a while...
A kan on the 6-pin. If he's going for a sanshoku, then he's got a 6-sou triplet.
I don't mind your little sashiuma, I'll riichi!
Kan.
I knew it, he had that 6-sou triplet.
He just let the 6-sou pass.
If he's waiting on the 4th 9-sou, it can't be anythin' but Kokushi.
Let's play!
Sanshoku Doukou Dora 2, mangan.
T-Then, the 5-sou would've passed?
That was your winning tile too, wasn't it?
Your boss has come up with quite the elaborate scheme.
I came here under direct orders from boss Ishikawa.
Wh-What?
So you just used me to test the waters?
In any case, we haven't got much time.
Let's conclude the next game at once.
If I win, Dragon will follow me to meet Ishikawa.
He discarded a pair of the chun?!
Hey, I didn't think you'd do something so foolish...
You'd better not be making fun of us!
Kan!
The only one who believes is yourself.
The only one who you can believe in is yourself.
Nothing personal, but this game ends here.
Dragon, I'm the one who accepted boss Ishikawa's final orders.
People call me a hitman...
Just behave yourself and come with me to the boss's place.
So in the end, it seems the boss didn't have faith in either of us.
However, this round isn't over yet!
Dragon, excuse the repetition, but I'm going to say this once more.
Boss Ishikawa made me into what i am.
If he calls something black, then it's black, even if it's actually white.
My life is entirely in boss Ishikawa's hands...
Dragon...
Don't make me have to kill you.
What?! They've killed Takashina?
Got it! Bring everyone to the main office!
Ishikawa, you punk!
Tsumo!
Mangan.
Dragon... You really are quite strange!
You discarded the same tiles as me in the last two rounds as well!
They're even in the same order.
Dragon! Is it a coincidence, or is there some purpose to this matching game?!
Show me your hand!
The tiles one discards are the outer world.
The tiles in one's hand are the inner world.
One's insides are the one thing that can't be shown.
Dragon, I want to see those "insides" of yours!
Dragon...
Are you... Are you trying to mock me?!
Huh?!
Huh? Don't you know?
Wh-What did you say?!
They got the chief?!
Underboss Murota Sakae was shot in the street.
Upon hearing that news,
the syndicate's adviser and a dozen members hurried to confirm it.
Perhaps due to the inclement weather, the phone line was out of service.
In any case, they made a beeline straight for the designated hospital.
Dragon,
my draws are getting very interesting now that I'm playing against you!
Perhaps I'm grabbing hold of some of that monstrous luck of yours?
Pon.
What's the matter?
Why isn't everyone here yet?!
W-Well... There was a call from the police saying that you had been shot...
You fools!
I am clearly just fine!
Murota! It's the end of the road!
It seems, there's no such thing as "impossible" for you.
However, I'm not one to believe in such fantasies!
Dragon! Let me introduce you to the concept of impossible!
Too bad, Dragon.
Just a tanyao.
Ishikawa...
Riichi ippatsu tsumo
tanyao and San-ankou, haneman!
Dragon!
Do you see the two chrysanthemum flowers in between the doorframe?
The big one is for Murota,
and soon there will be one more!
Next to Murota's will be another flower -
a deep crimson chrysanthemum!
Unfortunately for you, Dragon,
I won't let go of your luck until then!
So you're laughing at me, huh, Dragon?
I haven't given in to your luck yet.
Furthermore... I'm not so foolish to rely on the luck of other people.
You've finally gained enough momentum to start mocking me, Dragon!
Good! I'll take you on this round!
This is Dragon's tile, I can't discard it.
Look, Dragon, it's a 2-pin.
Pon.
That sly Dragon...
What on earth is he waiting for?
Impossible? No... Possible!
I win!
I see now, Dragon. Are you doing that just to spite me at any cost?
Dragon!
You truly are The Calling Dragon
Pon!
It's like you release a flash of light with every call.
Oh, yet another flash.
But no matter how hard you try, I will emerge victorious in the end!
Dragon! Just give up already!
You're torturing yourself.
Stop throwing your life away.
Everything will become easy!
You will live in comfort
if you give your life up to me...
Pon.
D-Dragon, you...
So you still intend to defy me?
Very well, Dragon!
I'll put this syndicate's crest on the line for this bout!
With the crest on the line,
Dragon is not going to live,
regardless of whether he wins or loses.
Everyone present saw it that way.
Pon!
The south 3rd round... Dragon started with a call of the 8-sou.
Dragon, I'll pon that.
Pon!
Dragon! That hatsu is mine! Kan!
Kai told me that
getting into a calling war with you would cause nothing but trouble...
But I won't back down anymore!
You have to win the fights that you start.
That's...
That's the way of the Yakuza!
You're not in this for much longer.
Wh-What was that?
Kan!
Dragon...!
Dragon... Did you win?
If Dragon flips over that tile, he'll be killed for sure.
Everyone's attention was concentrated on Dragon's hands.
Tsumo.
Keep yourself together, Kitajima.
Why are you taking out your gun?
B-Boss...
Calm down, Kitajima.
Don't let your spirits down.
What would I do if you lost your cool?
In a battle, winning means heaven,
and losing means hell.
Isn't that right, Dragon?
Let's start the final round, Dragon!
As the darkness disappeared,
the flow of time returned to the room.
Ever so slowly, with great reluctance,
the storm had turned to calm.
Pon!
Kan!
Dragon, I'm going to win!
Kan.
Dragon...
Dragon, I finally understand.
You are an incarnation!
An incarnation sent to me by god!
I can see that god truly detests me!
He sent you to this world... You, Dragon!
With the sole purpose of humiliating me!
The Kai Group's Lieutenant Sotoda Yuji clearing his throat
was the signal to kill the Dragon.
But then suddenly...
Kawachi!
Ron.
Stop. Put down your guns.
Dragon, please hear me out before you go away for good.
This match is over.
There's nothing left to say.
Do it.
Wait I said!
Kitajima, what's the meaning of this?!
Boss, you can't kill Dragon!
Don't do it!
That man is absolutely vital to you.
You must know this more than anyone else, boss.
The reason he was born into this world
was to make you the greatest in the whole country!
It's because of his monstrous luck!
Boss, this is my last request...
Please don't kill that man!
It's too lonely up north
I'll take the southbound train
Don't worry about me
I'll write to you when I'm settled somewhere
If you hesitate to leave me now,
I'll be the one you'll have to cling to
I've been holding on so tight to the weight of all the days I've loved you
I say good bye
I'm a lonely woman looking for a town that suits me
Love is always cruel
It hurts those who believe in it too much
If I hadn't met you
I'd have had a life that was a little too ordinary
Now, with no one to see me off,
The lights of the station house begin to move
I'm enduring the heat of my tears
I say good bye
Please understand, “good bye”
It's a word of love
If I hesitate to say goodbye now,
I'll become a woman who has no choice but to cling to you
I've been so heavy with love, I've had to bear it
I say good bye
Please understand that I say goodbye
It's the language of love