Pon!
What a boisterous young man.
At this point, you're just fighting yourself.
You gotta think about other players at least a bit.
It's good manners!
Should I kan?
Ron.
Itsuu Chankan Dora Dora, mangan.
So, are you still not convinced?
I am the rumored Calling Dragon.
Hey, bud, you've been pretty quiet with your calls so far.
You shouldn't do that, you announce them with a bang.
Chi.
Hey, watch this, bud.
I'm gonna show you the essence of calling now.
Oh, another 1-sou, huh.
Despite appearances, you have guts, don't you?
Allow me to call it.
It's the 4th 1-sou, won't you call it?
Try me!
B-Baiman?
What about it, self-proclaimed Calling Dragon?
The naked wait you're so proud of went down the drain.
The famed Calling Dragon is defeated by a newcomer?
Tsk. Even the Calling Dragon loses sometimes.
Hey, you'd better not get carried away.
We know you're fake.
Did you really think a sloppy thug like you
could make a convincing Calling Dragon from the rumors?
Huh?
That one always keep his head down and remains stoic.
And every time he calls,
a flash of light is produced,
because he imbues the tiles with life.
Are you saying I'm not the real Calling Dragon?
The real one is long gone from this realm.
The Dragon is dead.
Well, what's the point shooting the breeze with you?
Well then, shall we start it?
Ron.
Kamicha bud, is this why you called the 6-pin?
If you hadn't called, your shimocha would've won by tsumo.
What ferocity, is it a Sanshoku Doukou?
Tsumo.
As expected of the Calling Dragon.
He's just the guy Ishikawa thinks he is.
It's almost time, Boss.
Sotoda, if that weasel doesn't bow down to me...
then kill him!
B-Boss?
Let's turn this into a festival... A festival of gunfire between east and west!
Kaito Takeshi - now, he is considered the most powerful man in not just
the Kansai region, but within the entire Japanese underworld.
He leads the Kansai Group.
It includes well over 500 different organizations.
Without a doubt, he is the don that controls all of Japan.
In order to become the successor of the Oudou Syndicate,
Ishikawa needed the Kaito seal of approval no matter what.
There was no one in Japan's underground world who didn't not know Kaito's name.
Ishikawa is now sitting in front of that man.
Ishikawa, it must have been quite the hassle making the journey here.
Not at all. The sight of Kyoto in the snow alone has made it most worthwhile.
Politics again.
Yakuza don't need politics.
Isn't that right, Ishikawa?
It's swallowing me...
To think that I, Ishikawa Takashi, would be so overwhelmed in the face of the don...
B-Boss?
Dragon...
That laugh was a sorrowful cry to Dragon,
a cry that he would never hear.
Dragon... Dragon! Do you dare to laugh at my face? My, Ishikawa Takashi's?!
Lord Kaito, I am Ishikawa Takashi, second leader of the Kai Group.
I came to Kyoto with the intention of giving my life up.
Kan.
Oh? You came to Kyoto to give your life away, you say?
Is there really something of such importance here? Tell me more.
Boss Kaito, please do not continue to make a mockery of me.
You never know... Tomorrow this white snow may become a red rain!
Boss Kaitou, I shall state my request once more.
Please give me your approval when I become the new Oudou president!
This white snow may become a red rain tomorrow, huh?
You should know, Ishikawa.
The weather migrates from west to east.
Won't that same crimson rain
fall in Tokyo the day after tomorrow?
Here's my advice, Ishikawa.
Hurry up back to Tokyo!
It seems that some greenhorn from Sotoda-san's men dropped dead.
What do you know - apparently, the red rain prefers the east over the west.
Boss, I need to go out for a moment.
Who could attack the Kai Group now...
When I think about it, there's only one man who would rebel against me, the new boss.
At that moment, the name of Motomiya Haruki came to Ishikawa's mind clearly.
Judging from the car's license plate, it was Motomiya's work.
So I thought.
He's the only candidate I could think of.
The only man idiotic enough to stand up to me, Ishikawa Takashi.
Tsumo.
That was fun.
Dragon, when you see Ishikawa, tell him this:
"You'll never usurp the syndicate for yourself."
All right?
Emergency exit
Motomiya Haruki, the Brawler of Tokai.
He is one of those men
who are born to become a yakuza.
He got tattooed when he was fourteen.
He lived his whole life without parents.
That's why he chose two parents as the image to be put on his back.
Let me reiterate. He tattooed his back on his fourteenth summer.
He is Motomiya Haruki.
A yakuza by birth.
What was that?
Try to say it again! C'mon!
Your Lieutenant was murdered!
A drowned body was found in Yokohama Bay at dawn today.
After a short investigation, the man was identified as Wakabayashi Tamotsu,
an executive staff at the Motomiya group, part of the Oudou syndicate.
Authorities believe it was a result of infighting between syndicates.
Ishikawa!
Ishikawa, you punk...
Oh, you had a good 2-man and 3-man double mentsu going on.
Very well done.
Hey, Kid, you're trying to make fun of me, dontcha?
What an insistent 1-man.
Ron.
A set-up with the 2-man and 3-man.
He said it was his habit to glimpse the shimmering landscape.
Motomiya was born in Yokohama
Other than that, you won't get a word about his past out of him.
We just know he like seagulls ever since he was a child.
He liked seagulls because they could fly freely anywhere they want.
Boss, they got another one.
What's with those looks, you motherfuckers?!
So what if they got a few of our guys?!
How can you even call yourself yakuza?!
Listen, this is a watershed moment!
Keep going!
Fire from all guns!
You gotta admit, Motomiya Haruki is going strong. Don't you think?
But even so, the one defending is Ishikawa Takashi himself.
Is he stupid?
Calling again, kid?
Ooh! I'm scared.
Since this is the first call of the game.
Hey, any more and my tenosynovitis...
will...
...act up.
Currently, Ishikawa
could see the shadow of the west behind Haruki Motomiya's back.
Motomiya is indeed unrivaled when it comes to fighting.
However, even he wasn't stupid enough to start a fight he can't win.
The shadow of the west lingered distinctly behind Motomiya.
It was a giant shadow of Kaito Takeshi.
Motomiya was once again contemplating the shimmering landscape.
Of course, Motomiya knew that he was no match for Ishikawa.
Not because of a difference in organizational abilities,
but because of a certain "star"
everyone is born under, which Motomiya didn't quite understand himself.
Despite that, Motomiya...
still wanted to fly higher than anyone else.
Ron.
By then, the messenger of the west
had already visited Dragon.
Ishikawa!
I'll kill you!
Motomiya disappeared?
Our men are seriously worried.
Please come back to safety.
Motomiya disappeared, huh?
That cretin... Is he seriously aiming for my head?
That man would come to me, even if he'd need to be disguised for that.
And then he won't hesitate to take my life the moment I slip up.
That's the kind of man he is.
That conviction was shared by gangsters who grew up on the same battlefield.
Motomiya-san, when my boss says something, he means it. You can trust him.
When he took control of the Kanto region, Motomiya-san,
he intended to put you in charge of the eastern part of the country.
But there is one condition for that.
Ishikawa Takashi - he wants you to do away with that man.
I know you hate his guts too.
So why don't you take that man's head
as a souvenir,
to the delight of both you and my boss?
Dragon, let me spell it clearly for you.
I went all the way to Tokyo to meet you.
The reason is a certain someone asked me very politely to go and check on you.
That's because you're a man
who made even Ishikawa Takashi himself change his plans,
Calling Dragon.
Our goal is to determine Ishikawa Takashi's worth using your evaluation.
Hm. It's a good call, Dragon.
Kan.
All your calls are so terrifying, Dragon.
Thanks to that, my tiles are all shiny and sparkling.
I get it now, Dragon.
You make your calls for others' sake.
I've got only one thing to tell you.
Huh?
As sad as it sounds, people only live for themselves.
It's just you who keeps inquiring into others' lives.
Foolish act.
Motomiya, if you're gonna come, come quickly!
I'll help clear up your fucking hazy mind!
Boss, preparations are finished.
Got it.
The waves were rocking the boat calmly.
A single seagull wandered around.
It wandered, as though in search of a place for repose.
Ishikawa.
Motomiya.
Ishikawa!
Motomiya!
If you're gonna shoot, do it!
Stop babbling, Ishikawa!
Motomiya...
Why didn't you shoot?
Ishikawa...
Why?!
Hey, Ishikawa!
As sad as it sounds, I am a creature that only lives for myself.
Motomiya, why didn't you shoot?
Why aren't you giving me the final blow yourself?
Ishikawa...
For how long do you plan to keep humiliating me?!
As sad as it sounds,
the sky was dreary that day.
Gimme a gun.
And now...
The sky cried.
From what I could gather, Ishikawa and Motomiya
have always been close,
and ate from the same bowl.
Both are disciples of the first boss of the Kai Group, Kai Shozo, right?
Tell me, Dragon, doesn't that name bring back memories?
Kai Shozo.
That name is not an item of the past.
He still lives...
inside me.
Ishikawa! Pull the trigger already!
Mo...
Motomiya...
Boss Kai is crying in his grave...
Motomiya… Open your eyes!
You need to come to your senses...
Won't you follow me for a minute?
Hurry up and get in.
The rain keeps splashing water into the car.
Ishikawa!
Motomiya...
We can't start talking yet...
Not until you've properly righted the wrongs as a chivalrous man would.
Isn't that right?
Unavoidably, the rain soaked Ishikawa's shoulders,
adding to the weight of 2,000 lives already burdening it.
You'd better move start moving, Dragon.
My boss hates being made to wait.
Wh-What?!
K-Kaito is in Tokyo!?
S-Say, you're quite certain of it, are you?
T-They shoved Dragon into the car?
For Kaito Takeshi, Kanto - especially Tokyo - was a long-cherished dream.
He made it through endless ordeals.
This was the one job he could never accomplish.
Conquer!
Lord Kaito Takeshi set foot on this land,
where he would meet his end.
What is it about Kaito Takeshi?
Look, aren't you guys gangsters and all?
Kaito is here alone, yet you're scared out of your wits.
You burst into tears over his sakura signboard.
Whoa!
That's the one.
Another kanchan, huh.
It'll be 2,600.
Too bad for you, boys.
I'm feeling very lucky today.
Motomiya...
Ma'am...
Ishikawa, watch me closely!
I'm going to right the wrongs like no one else ever did. Or ever would.
At that time, Dragon
was in that hell for a long time already.
Boss, a call from madam Sakurada.
Sakurada?
She is crying over the phone.
Ishikawa here.
I understand.
I will personally take responsibility for Motomiya's life and protect him.
Madam Sakurada, please don't cry any more.
M-Madam...
Motomiya Haruki, 33 years old at the time.
He was a handsome man, who still had that childlike image lingering on his profile.
Dragon, would you please kan this.
Dragon, it can't be this one, can it?
They said you were the poster child for luck, Dragon.
But in our world,
you can't win through sheer luck.
Not unless you furnish it with a good strategy.
You can't take the sky.
I don't know about heaven or earth.
There is only "now."
In a blink of an eye, you
are not in this for much longer.
You big dumbass!
Think you can send your small fry to deal with me and call it a day?!
"Small fry."
"In this for much longer."
You easterners sure love to speak in some incomprehensible phrases.
Ishikawa...
Ishikawa!
I need to ask for a favor.
Please save Motomiya!
He came to see me last night,
and now he went to his death.
He apologized to everyone before dying.
Please, Ishikawa!
Why does it have to be this way?
You and Motomiya were as close as brothers, weren't you?
Is this what it means to lead a gangster life?
Does it really have to be that extreme?!
Ishikawa...
I can't afford to lose Motomiya.
At that time, Motomiya was long chucking to himself, standing behind Dragon.
First: Chivalry is about respecting justice.
Second: A chivalrous men would not be swayed by emotion.
Third: A chivalrous man lives for his lord.
And he's not afraid of death!
So scatter the fuck off! I am Motomiya Haruki from the Oudou Syndicate!
Motomiya-san, you are the small fry here.
Kaito...
Hey, kid, didn't I tell you to stop?
It's just shameless. The true Calling Dragon is sitting here, right before you.
By the way, bud.
You said this funny hooey before.
"The Calling Dragon is not with us anymore?"
What are you talking about.
I'm right here, in flesh!
Wh...
Are you really...
Ah, never mind that. I said something thoughtless on the spur of the moment.
He's dead, all right?
He's not with us anymore.
K-Kaito...
Dragon… Dragon!
Give me your luck!
Give it to Motomiya!
Dragon, allow me to pon that one as well.
You know, Dragon, with you in the game, tiles always move in interesting ways.
Is this also the doing of your good luck?
Sorry to bother you, Dragon,
but we'd like you to stick around for a wee bit longer.
Dragon, do you know why boss is sitting at a table with the likes of you?
You're the bait.
The delicious bait
that attracts small fry.
Is that where your luck ends, Dragon?
I know not the extent of my own luck.
Much less...
If I have any luck to spare for others.
If you say any more,
your words will lose any meaning.
Kan!
Dragon!!
Kaito...
It seems, Calling Dragon was killed alongside him back then.
Kaito's underlings did it.
Boss!
Kill that man! Hurry up! Kill him immediately!
Hey bud.
What is this rubbish you're saying?
The Calling Dragon is right here, alive and well!
That reminds me, we haven't heard your name yet, kid.
You could tell us if that's not a bother.
So how about it?
Witness! I'm the Calling Dragon!
You shut it already.
Come on, please.
Tell us your name, kid.
Dragon.