The Calling Dragon
Soaring Dragon Chapter
All right. I'll take that.
Kan.
Pon.
Pon?
Kan!
Tsumo.
C-Calling Dragon?
Pon.
Quit messing with me!
Take this!
Pon.
Hurry up to
The time is not yours to waste.
S-Shut it!
B-Boss!
You fool! A cheap trick like that doesn't deserve to be called cheating!
Calling Dragon, I was looking for you.
For me? Let go of his hand and maybe I'll hear you out.
Ron.
You said that you hate the yakuza.
But being a pro gambler is even worse.
The yakuza don't deceive other yakuza.
But for gamblers like you, it's a way of life.
They're lower than dirt!
Well, maybe once you're in front of the president, you'll learn to stay in line.
Dragon, take off your sunglasses.
And put out your cigarette.
Won't you give me the ball?
Hey.
Y-Yessir!
Thank you.
I gotta go, little missy. We can play some more once the grown-up talk is over.
Hey, Murota! You came by yourself? Where's your boss, huh?
I see... So his wife's been hospitalized?
That's tough for both of them.
But she was taken in by ambulance?
In that case it must be serious.
Guess Kawachi's gone soft.
His wife is more important than a promise between bosses now?
Shozo! One's wife takes precedence.
My apologies... Once my boss is done with the formalities, he'll come here immediately!
Murota, that's enough.
More importantly, hurry up and call in Dragon.
Yessir!
Hurry up and greet the president!
Cretin!
Kneel down and pay your respects!
It's fine. No need for greetings when we're about to face off.
You know what they say - might makes right! Don't they, Calling Dragon?
Tsumo.
That was too quick, Shozo.
I was about to get a yakuman...
That's quite the joke, president...
It's your turn.
Oh, my bad.
Tsumo.
Another quick win, eh, Shozo?
You'd better watch out.
Next time I'll get my yakuman!
Tsumo.
Aren't you supposed to be a yakuza?
Hm? What did you just say, young man?
Isn't it considered shameful for yakuza to deceive others?
Why don't you take those sunglasses off?
Looks like the fun and games are over, Shozo.
Guess I'm losing my knack. To think I'd be caught by a kid,of all people...
Hey, not bad, kid.
Now...
It looks like Murota didn't even notice.
No offense to you, though, Murota.
He was putting his winning tile on top of the wall and switching it out...
How about that kid, eh, Shozo?
I want him.
President, it's been so long since I met a guy that I absolutely needed to get my hands on!
Shouzou, I'll give him to you.
Refine his skills!
Understood.
A Calling Dragon, huh?
Hey! Boss Kai has called for you. Come back!
If he needs something, he can come to me himself.
What was that, you jackass?!
Hey! Dontcha lay a finger on him.
That guy is mine.
I'm feeling great today, little missy!
I'll play ball with you until you get sick of it.
Okay!
Dragon, guess I've come to you, just as you asked.
All right.
I'll hear you out.
At that time, war was threatening to erupt in the east.
Gangster Blood Feud
Sakurado (Influential Gang) Mobilizes
A member of the Shimazu Syndicate,
a part of the Oudou-affiliated Kai Group, was stabbed to death.
Miyoshi Family suspect Morita (22)
The assailant was M from the Miyoshi Family, a rival of the Oudou Syndicate.
Gang member Morita brutally murdered on the street!
It goes without saying that the Oudou Syndicate
Retaliation by the Sakurado-affiliated Kai Family?!
immediately enacted retaliatory measures against the Miyoshi Family.
Miyoshi Family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at his mistress's house!!!
The Oudou Syndicate boasts of having forces throughout the entire Kanto area.
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to the Miyoshi family's lieutenant Ishii (41) shot dead!
It is the most widespread crime syndicate in eastern Japan.
That's what being a yakuza is all about!
If someone hits you, you hit them back - several times harder.
I'm not here to listen to your bragging.
Stop wasting my time.
I am quite certain that you have it in you -
the thing I'm looking for. That's a big deal.
You are mine, Dragon.
Sorry, but I answer to nobody.
I'm not anyone's property.
Dragon, I'm carrying the burden of 2000 Oudou and Kai members
on my back,you know.
So?
Stop making fun of me...
I need to set a good example for them!
Shozo, how did that dispute with the Miyoshis turn out?
They're as good as dead! If we keep it up, they'll be completely wiped out by next week!
Now's the time, Shozo...
You need to pull out.
Huh? B-Boss!
It seems that the Miyoshis are getting the western syndicates involved.
If the east and west go to war, there'll be no end in sight...
It's time, Shozo.
Understood...
Hey! I'm getting off at the next exit.
B-Boss, this is insane!
You can't be walking out alone right now!
I need to tell the car in front...
I don't care.
I'm getting off.
I can win with that one.
What the hell are you talking about?
Shit!
Chi.
Take this!
You're so naive.
Huh?
Who the hell is this guy?!
Mahjong
Dragon...
Oh? The fuck was that sound?
A gunshot?
Huh? Hey, what'd you just
Ron.
Dragon...
Dragon!
Give me your luck!
Give it to the boss!
Wh-What was that?!
Dragon went with Miyoshi?!
Where? Where the fuck are they going?!
Mahjong Club Peaceful
I run a gambling den for the Miyoshi Family.
I've heard the rumors about you, Calling Dragon.
Apparently you're a pretty good gambler.
But rumors aren't always true!
Seeing is believing is what they say.
You know what I mean?
Let's play just one game. I want to get this over with as soon as possible.
Really?
Pon!
It's ron.
Urk!
Chinitsu toitoi tanyao...
So you're Miyoshi-san?
Looks like the cat was out of the bag from the very start.
Now I saw it and I believe it.
You really are an amazing gambler!
Don't take this the wrong way, Dragon.
It just so happens that this parlor is one of the boss's hideouts.
That's all there is to it.
Don't get cocky!
I'm getting used to the yakuza's idea of entertainment.
Wh-What?
What was that sound?
Probably just some punks getting into a fight.
Nobody knows that I'm here.
Come on, let's resume the game.
Going for suukantsu, eh, Dragon?
Like that'll ever happen!
Riichi.
Well, now!
K-Kai!
You're supposed to be dead!
As you can see, I lived. And indeed, I'm as alive as ever! I'm immortal!
Long time no see, Dragon!
You know him?!
Dragon, it's all thanks to you that I was able to find Miyoshi here.
I'm truly grateful!
I don't need your thanks.
You can just call off the dogs that keep following my every step, and we're square.
You haven't changed a bit, my boy!
Oh! Pardon me butting in.
I didn't mean to interfere while you're in the middle of a game. Please go on.
I believe it was your turn?
S-Shithead!
Kan.
Dragon, you're just one step away from suukantsu!
Motherfucker!
Now then, it seems it's Miyoshi's turn. Hurry up to draw!
Kan.
It's over.
Dragon! Where are you going? The game's not over yet.
Listen, keep your eyes on Dragon at all times, understand? He is my treasure!
I won't die before I get my hands on that guy!
The fact that Kai Shouzou of Oudou's Kai Group assassinated Miyoshi himself
sent a shockwave throughout the underworld.
It showed that the Oudou Syndicate was a force to be reckoned with.
But more importantly, it was an exclamation
that put Kai Shouzou's and the Kai Group's names on the map.
Meanwhile, the Miyoshi Family, which had lost its leader,
was on its last legs.
Their destruction was inevitable.
Due to Kai's actions, the conflict came to a tentative end.
However, as time passed,
it felt like unsettling noises began to break the silence.
Hmm...
Don't think I've seen him.
He's probably never been here before.
Fuck if I know. We've not been seeing him lately. No, it's the truth!
I don't know.
I really know nothing!
When I woke up this morning, he was already gone. That's all I know.
I should be the one asking you.
Where is he?
Will he ever come back to me?
It's useless, Dragon!
You can't get away from me!
Just you wait, Dragon!
I'll be seeing you real soon!
Inn
A-Are you sure?
There's no room for mistake.
It's the Calling Dragon.
One can't forget that irritating face he has!
C-Calling dragon! But why is he playing in a place like this?
Riichi.
D-Did he just riichi?
Dragon declared riichi!
N-Now that I think about it,
he hasn't called even once yet!
Restroom
C-Calling Dragon? There's no way!
Why's he in a gambling den like this?
I've got no idea either,
and it's creeping me out!
And it seems like the Oudou Gangs are always on his tail.
Oudou Gangs?
Listen up! You absolutely cannot lose!
Underestimating the yakuza is a way to get yourself killed!
What's wrong?
Your hands are shaking.
Shut it!
Kan.
Pon!
That means I haven't had three meals, not even one, and it's my first or second time.
You're Calling dragon, aren't you?
Why did you come to this backwater den?
You're not gonna find anything worth your while out here.
Kan.
I just felt like it.
Calling Dragon, can I ask you one more thing?
Why haven't you called before?
If the rumor's right...
D-Did you say Calling dragon?
I-It can't be true!
Prove it!
Riichi!
Kan.
I feel like my life grows shorter every time I call.
Just one call should enough against you guys.
On that day, Dragon glided deftly through the silence.
It was as if he had abandoned his fate to the flow of time itself.
Dragon, I've been waiting for you to come out.
That was quite a long game.
Did you have fun?
Dragon, stab me with this. Here.
You weren't trying to run away while I was gone, were you?
Now come! Hurry up and stab me!
I wasn't running away from you.
I just felt like going out.
Dragon, I've had just about enough of playing this cat-and-mouse game with you.
Isn't it about time to settle this once and for all?
Dragon, have a match with me.
A match to end all matches.
If I win, you're mine.
If you win, you can take my life and do whatever you want with it.
Dragon! If you're a man, then put your life on the line and come at me!
Come and put your life on the line!
"Come and put your life on the line?"
Really now, Shozo?
Did you seriously expect him to come here just because of those words?
He'll come.
I know he will.
Dragon's mahjong isn't half-hearted.
He's always gambling with his life...
I guess it's just his bread and butter.
It's in his blood, even.
He knows that fighting is the only way he can continue to exist.
He's going to keep fighting until it finally destroys him.
Because that is his destiny.
That's just how Dragon is.
Dragon...
You're late.
The passage of time
means nothing to me.
The first round began under the most strange of circumstances.
Pon.
Apologies, that's a pon for me.
Shozo, now you're calling too?
It sure is a strange evening.
Pon.
A battle of pons! How fascinating!
Maruko, was it you who taught Shozo this tactic?
If you want to catch a tiger, you have to enter its den.
Seems like you could've made daisangen, Dragon...
Tenpai.
It looks like you're out of luck today, Dragon.
Chi.
Pon.
Ah, 2,000, 4,000.
Dragon, you're going to lose today.
The heavens are on my side!
Chun, honitsu!
There was no doubt that Kai Shozo had the heavens on his side that night.
Mahjong 841
It was as if he was drawing tiles at will.
Pon.
Shozo, are you okay?
You're sweating a lot.
Yeah... Don't worry about me.
I just got a little scratch that's itching...
I'm taking this pon, Dragon.
I'm going to win this game, Dragon.
You are already mine!
What's wrong, Dragon?
Or is your hand too messed up?
Chi.
Is that chii really a good idea, Dragon?
You can't win unless you get a haneman direct hit or sanbaiman tsumo.
I'm not stealing tiles with my calls.
I'm imbuing them with life.
Stop meddling in my affairs.
What is Dragon waiting on?
Could he have another middle wait?
That would be...
Eh...
I'll be fine. I'm in luck today!
The heavens are on my side!
Shozo!
What's wrong, Shozo?
I-It's all fine.
Please sit down.
Dragon!
It's do or die!
It's over.
Dragon...
Hey, Dragon!
Shozo! Hey!
What a wonderful victory!
Hold it, Dragon.
You still have one matter to settle, remember?
A promise is a promise.
Take my life!
Not so fast, Dragon kid.
If there's a shred of humanity left in you,
how can you leave without even acknowledging Kai's words?
My poor daughter... Kai's wife, she didn't tell anyone else, but...
A lead ball was lodged in his lung.
It needs to be taken out as soon as possible!
However, he only has a fifty-fifty chance of surviving the operation...
Yet he absolutely refused to undergo the surgery!
If only you could see how bitterly she cried as she held onto me...
He only has three months left...
What Kai did was...
bet those three months on you!
Hey pops, don't say a word more.
You're making me look pathetic.
What's wrong, Dragon?
Hurry up and take my life!
Aren't you carrying the burden of 2,000 people on your back?
Cherish that burden.
Dragon!
Ch-Chief!
Wh-What did you say?
Chief was shot?!
Why didn't anyone protect him?!
Where were his bodyguards?!
Wh-What?! Kai was with him?
What the fuck has he been doing?!
That morning, 36 of the Oudou's upper leaders assembled in secrecy.
The pressing topic, naturally, was the shooting of the Oudou
Syndicate president the previous night.
The meeting was tumultuous from the very start.
The anti-Kai faction pinned the blame on Kai for the incident,
and demanded that he step down from his position.
Kawachi Koichi, the leader of the anti-Kai faction, said:
So, how about it?
Shall we hold a secret ballot in order to reach a consensus regarding this incident?
Nah, no need for a vote.
I'm prepared to accept the consequences at any time.
However! I need to give them payback before then. Until I'm finally satisfied...
With those words from Kai,
the meeting was adjourned.
One week later,
a man's corpse was discovered on Mount Takao, brutally murdered.
The corpse was lidentified as S, 36 years old, a member of the Miyoshi Family.
It was confirmed that he was the one who shot the Oudou Syndicate president.
Whoa, I'll be taking that pon.
Kan.
Would you look at that!
You...
Huh? Are you talking to me?
You're not in this for much longer.
Pon.
Look, kid, I don't understand what this whole "in this for longer" means.
But if you keep talking shit, you're in for a world of hurt!
Huh? What'd you just say, kid?
It's a ron.
Ron?
Please stop!
Please!
Stop it!
The Kai Group,over 2500 members strong, including the low-ranking ones,
began a massacre under Kai Shozo's command.
Listen up! We're gonna kill every last one of those Miyoshi bastards!
Ooh! Here we go! I really needed this one.
Ron.
I went this far so that the president
would become the greatest boss in the whole country!
What am I supposed to do, if...
If he's gone?
What have i been living for this whole time?!
Please!
Don't let him die!
I'd give my own life many times over!
Just don't let the old man die now!
I'm begging you!
For the first time, Dragon felt a certain kinship with Kai's soul.
You, the .
Earlier, you said that I'm not in this for much longer, isn't that right?
I'd really appreciate it if you explained what the fuck it meant!
You don't carry the burden of even a single person on your back.
Stop pretending to be a yakuza.
Perhaps the true meaning of this phrase could only be revealed
to those who follow the path of destruction.
Ron.
It was as if Dragon could now hear Kai's cries clearly.
Give me your luck!
Give it to the old man, Dragon!
Tsk.
Pon.
That's it...
That's gotta be it!
Withdrawal of Japanese territory ba salesman
From that day on, Kai Shozo lived in Dragon.
Mutual Aid Hospital
At the same time, Ishikawa Takashi, the second Kai Group boss,
showed up at a hospital somewhere in Tokyo.
Of course, he was here to visit the Oudou boss Sakurada Michizo,
who was admitted to the hospital as a long-term inpatient.
But for Ishikawa, it was also part of the plan
for fulfilling an important expectation, pinned on him.
You guys wait here.
Namely, that important expectation
had been the last wish of his predecessor Kai Shozo, bequeathed to him.
Nice work,everyone.
How about you let me in?
With all due respect, sir, this room is for Kawachi Family members only.
No one is allowed inside without the boss's permission.
Oh, really? I didn't know that.
I am Ishikawa, second boss of the Kai Group! Will you still not let me in?
Ishikawa, these will probably be my last words, so listen carefully!
As long as the Oudou Syndicate exists, the Kai Group will be its wall of iron!
The Kai Group is the backbone of the Oudou Syndicate.
Do you get it, Ishikawa?
The Kawachis or any other group cannot be that iron wall!
The Kai Group must be the one to carry the Oudou Syndicate upon its back!
The Kai syndicate is the iron wall that protects the boss!
Hurry up and let me in already!
More aggressive calls, eh, bud?
You're gonna mess up the flow of tiles if you do that!
Let's go with riichi for the time being.
Whoa! A ron!
How stupid!
Now, now, it's been a while, Boss Kawachi.
You've been getting pretty full of yourself these days, Ishikawa!
The president's room is Kawachi territory!
It's off limits to the likes of you!
I'll get straight to the point, if I may.
I was told by the missus herself to come visit the president today!
Madam Sakurada told you?
Well, fine. Have a seat, Ishikawa.
Or should I say "new Kai boss?"
You've received quite the promotion!
now listen up,greenhorn.
I don't know what Madam Sakurada told you, but the only ones who can see the president
are his closest officials.
Well, I guess that can't be helped. It was decided at the executive meeting, after all.
You never received the cup of sake directly from the boss either.
You see, in the Yakuza world,
you can only be admitted into the family by receiving a cup from your superior.
Don't take it personally.
Get it, Ishikawa? You'll just have to work your way up as the new Kai boss, bit by bit...
I understand...
I understand, but I'm not backing down!
In fact, I came here today in order to share sake with boss.
Until I share a drink with him, i won't move a single step from this spot!
I-Ishikawa, what the...
Later, Kawachi's close associates revealed that at that time,
Ishikawa stood before Kawachi's, looking as fierce as the yaksha tattooed on his back!
Riichi!
Kan!
You...
Huh?
You won't be winning in mahjong any time soon.
What was that, you little shit?
W-Wait a minute!
Who the hell are you?
Dragon.
I-I see...
But man, can you believe this?!
Calling Dragon himself!
In a gamble, losing means death.
Continuing to win is life.
It was Kai Shozo himself who once said that.
And now, Dragon once again renewed his search for life-or-death gambles.
In the end, it truly was just in his blood.
It was his destiny and he couldn't change it in a thousand years.
Until i share sake with him, I won't move from this spot!
Kai Shozo had left one last person for Dragon: Ishikawa Takashi.
It was then that the battle to decide their fates truly began.