Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to tree years.
All right, I'm in tenpai!
It's a 2547p wait, but haneman isn't enough for first place!
It's clear from my discards I have single suit hand anyway...
I have no choice but to...
Call riichi and draw the winning tile myself!
As long as I don't draw the dora 5m, I can win!
Episode 1
Springtime for the Luckless
C'mon, ippatsu tsumo!
Zu—
Ron! Tanyao pinfu sanshoku iipeikou dora dora!
Zugan...
Double ron! Shousangen dora dora!
Ron! Honroutou toitoi hatsu dora 3!
Zugan!
My apologies! Riichi junchan ippatsu tsumo, 6000 all! My pleasure!
The first bell tolls for my father...
The second bell tolls for my mother...
The third bell tolls for me!
Th-Those voices!
We've been waiting for you!
IOU ¥30,000
IOU ¥20,000
We're...
IOU ¥40,000
Here to collect these!
Don't let him get away!
Get him!
Whaaat?!
This'll pay for the rent!
Wut? He's got only 30,000 left!
Tsk! Listen up! You gotta raise
at least 100,000 next month, got it?
Salary
So, where do we go for drinks tonight?
What about that new Race Queen Pub?
I like that! I really do!
Z-Zugan...
I'm sorry!
It's you...
Isn't that you, Toyotomi-kun?
It's me!
Your classmate from high school, Akina!
I see...
They took your entire monthly wage?
And they even took
your furniture and futon?
That's awful.
Say, Toyotomi-kun...
Do you still remember the days
when we were in high school?
You were really sparkling with life back then.
All right. Now, for this problem...
Here. Blue ribbons, I win.
Tsk...
Tokugawa, answer this.
Huh?
What's f(x) and g(x)?
Yeah, sure. It's...
Why can't you give it at least a bit of thought?!
Whatever. Why don't we ask Toyotomi to answer that instead?
Yessir! f(x) = k(e²ˣ-1), g(x) = ½(e²ˣ+1)!
Yes! Remarkable, Toyotomi!
You should all follow his example!
You're making me blush!
Honor Roll
Oh no! I lost to you again, Toyotomi-kun!
I just got lucky this time around, Hayami-san.
Not at all, it was your own ability.
Hey, Toyotomi-kun. What do you want to be when you graduate?
A teacher!
The young people these days don't know what to live for.
So I want to become a teacher who can show them how wonderful the life is!
That's so cool!
Back then, your eyes were sparkling
with dreams and hopes.
But that shining suddenly disappeared when were were in our senior year...
Zugan...
I-I don't play mahjong!
We know you do. Don't hide it.
Bastard! Are ya telling us yer parents
didn't teach you to play mahjong at home since you were a kid?!
Ya just don't wanna
hang out with us, is that it?
I-If only for one hanchan!
From then on, your life took a big downturn...
Dat's how it's done, li'l bro!
789 sanshoku with guaranteed junchan?!
Will they get angry if I tsumo this kind of dealer haneman in East 1?
Riichi!
6s is the dora...
Maybe a 47s wait crossing the dora...?
Oh, rats!
Damn it, there's no way I can cut this!
Pinfu sanshoku is 5800, so I'll avoid ippatsu and play it safe!
All right! Chase riichi!
Three of the 8p are out...
It's not likely to be a pinzu wait.
It's probably something like 36m or 47m?
I can't push this!
Two discards
6m is dangerous to them both, and there's two out already!
It's awfully dangerous!
Even if I lose sanshoku, it can't be helped!
Wut are these draws?!
Ippatsu!... would have been nice.
Skillful mawashi!
Tsumo!
Pinfu tsumo! 700 all!
Wut?
Ya could've had junchan sanshoku!
Yeah, but you see...
I held back this 4s against your riichi!
That's not my wait, you dumbass!
And I had a mangan too...
Hatsu sanshoku dora 1 waiting on 5m kanchan?!
It's not even a suji trap, and still a mangan if he stays dama!
B-But, this definitely would have dealt into your riichi, right?
Nope, not at all. Ugh.
Riichi sanankou dora 1! Such a good hand and I got unlucky!
Why did he cut his pair of 6p with that hand?!
What the hell is his problem?
Why did I turn my junchan sanshoku 6000 all into a pinfu tsumo nomi 700 all?!
Riichi!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Ippatsu tsumo!
Huh? Wait, really?
That's the same tile you called riichi with!
Ugh... I'm really unlucky tonight...
Riichi ippatsu tsumo pinfu dora dora. Just a haneman.
If I can't even ippatsu tsumo the 1m with this, it's fucking over for me...
You're right...
You also missed a baiman.
Are you off your rocker or something?
What are these guys talking about?!
All right! Riichi!
What's up with these discards...
Let's cut 1p.
Ippatsu!
Wh-What the...
Riichi ippatsu dora dora.
Damn it, Akechi, yer good at this!
Oh no, I was just bluffing really well.
Even a pro wouldn't have expected that!
If he drew any manzu, he'd be in tenpai for baiman!
Wut?!
Looks like I got a tad too many tiles, look!
One, two, three, four, tile tile tile...
Oh! You're right! Ya got 17 tiles!
Haha! Then I can just discard these four. Here!
The penalty for too many tiles is a dead hand!
Wut!?
Why the hell does it have to be so harsh?!
It's not professional mahjong,
we can make an exception!
Exactly!
This is ridiculous!
Ron! Best out! Tanyao pinfu sanshoku iipeikou!
Zugaaaaan!
Three years have passed...
During those, those guys
too away everything you had...
Before!
After...
Toyotomi-kun, please!
Go back to how you were three years ago!
I... I...
I was in love with you back then!
Toyotomi-kun!
Howdy!
Toyotomi-kun! You're the Toyotomi-kun from back then, right? Is that you?
Toyotomi-kun!
Long time no see!
Please...
Stop playing mahjong, okay?
"Stop playing mahjong, okay?"
Together with the incessantly falling autumn rain, Akina's words soaked into Toyotomi's heart. But how deep?
South 3, North seat, 10th turn, 16400 points
Tsumo 5p, dora 8p
6s
Read RB1
That little fucker might even be serious about it!
What should we do?
If he fucking quits mahjong, our lifestyle is finished!
Don'tcha worry 'bout it!
The stench of mahjong's soaked deep into his body...
It ain't somethin' you can just wipe off and throw away!
FAREWELL MAHJONG
Toyotomi!
Huh?
Wut the?
Hey! Welcome, guys!
Don't hesitate! Let's get to it!
C'mon, Toyotomi, we're picking seats! Draw yours!
I've quit mahjong.
Don't say such sad stuff!
Can't you hear it?
The lamentation of the tiles you've cast aside...
The lamentations of the tiles?
Can't you see how lonely they're feeling?
Toyotomi!
I understand your feelings all too well.
If your determination to give up mahjong and live properly is so firm, I shan't say anything against it.
However, Toyo-san...
One must draw a clear line in one's affairs, isn't it?
Draw a line?
Play one last farewell mahjong with us!
That's what I'm saying!
Farewell mahjong?!
I hope you'll play at least 10 hanchan.
Whaat? 10 hanchan, that's way too
All right! Let's get crackin'!
You're the starting dealer, get fucked!
Heh, idiot! I'm the best at being starting dealer!
Chun!
Now that's a spicy tile!
Fuck off!
Ton!
Wut, Toyotomi, it's yer turn!
He hasn't said anything since before, looks like he's in a bad mood.
Stop playing mahjong already, okay?
No! But this is farewell mahjong!
If I just play 10 hanchan, I can be done with these guys!
I'll focus on playing calmly and avoiding a big loss...
Professional defensive hedgehog mahjong!
Chii!
What's up with you?! Don't call on the first turn!
That's it, Yasu's poorfag mahjong...
Calling a fuckin' ryanmen on turn one...
Hatsu!
Pon!
He didn't call the chun the dealer cut on his first turn...
Ron! Merciless bandit mahjong!
Shousangen honitsu chanta!
Zugan!
I got one dora, so that's a baiman!.
What the hell? Winning without drawing even once?!
Winning with your fucking haipai...
Well, in 10 hanchan one screw-up like this is bound to happen...
It's just coincidence it was at the very start!
EAST 2 SOUTH SEAT TURN 7
All right! Let's win big with this hand!
(3p is dora)
Since 47s is dangerous, I'll cut it early!
Got it!
With 2m ippatsu tsumo, it's mentanpin ippatsu tsumo sanshoku!
I can counter with my own baiman!
Riichi!
Wut's that? Here's a ton! Someone call it!
Ton? That's a pon from me.
Let's break his ippatsu.
C'mon, draw the 2m!
Fuck!
The 1m, you say?
Wait a second, I'll call kan on that.
P-pass.
I drew this one from the rinshan!
Good grief! At least the 47s is mostly used up!
What are you thinking about, get on with it!
You're in riichi, aren't you?
Rather than deal into dealer's haneman, I'll call 4s kan and pay the penalty for noten riichi...
Kan!
1m is the new dora again...
Fuck, should have gone for the shanpon wait...
Pon!
That means Akechi changed to a 5s tanki wait!
Don't draw it!
The tiles... the tiles are calling to me!
No... this can't be!
Hey, wutcha doin'! Just draw!
We haven't got to touch the tiles for two turns now!
Get on with it!
Got it...
Whoa, I even get to win a hand like this...
Ron!
Double ton and uhh...
11 dora! That's a kazoe yakuman!
Super zugan!
Hmm, I see, I see ..
(7m is dora)
Is that the case...?
It's finally my time to shine. Let's go!
What are you even thinking about?
Riichi!
You had gyoza, haven't you...
C'mon, pei!
Pass!
Genbutsu!
Farting's what this Shintarou's good at, huh...
Shaa!
Pass!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Ippatsu tsumo!
I tsumo'd!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo tanyao dora 4!
What the fuck?!
Zugan!
Stop playing mahjong already, okay?
That's right! Like this, I won't be able to quit mahjong!
I shan't let myself lose like this!
Huh? Ya cut the 6p?!
No, that was a mistake!
I screwed that one up!
I wanted to cut this one.
Whoa, the 8p came out?!
Oh no, I cut the tile next to it again, sorry! This is the real one!
Did it pass?
Ron!
My best out!
You finally cut it, retard!
We were playing with triple ron, weren't we!
I've got pinfu sanshoku dora 1!
I've got honitsu chun sanankou. Haneman.
For me...
Yakuman!
Well then! That's it!
I'll take care of this!
We'll be back soon!
We played mahjong to break off, but it turned out to just deepen our friendship!
How ironic!
After he broke his promise to Akina, Toyotomi falls yet deeper into mahjong hell.
Will a bright future ever be in store for him?
Zugan...
Oh, that Toyotomi! He used to be so dreamy, but what should I do now...
Whatever!
Next time on Super Zugan:
"Happy Birthday Zugan" and "Rejected, Dejected"
Don't miss it! Don't want to you to sleep on it!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening, get y'all with the midnight fever zugan zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the
The international star of pop, Minami Haruo!
Isogu na sawagu na awateru na
Don't hurry, don't worry, don't panic!
Pai wo tsukameba sengoku roman no yume ga waku
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance!
Unputenpu to riichi wo kakeru
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Tomete kureru na, toimen-san
Don't stop me, toimen-san!
Zugan to ikaneba naranu no da
You just got to go "zugan"!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha kamicha mo jan-nakama
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
Shoubu kaketara nasake-muyou no nerai-uchi
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy!
Kimi wa ageman suteki ja nai ka
Aren't you a great luckslut?
Boku to mangan tsumorou yo
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me!
Zugan to shiawase tsukamou zo
Zugan! Let's grasp happiness in our hands!
Super Zugan!
Yami de yakuman matsu kokoro~
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Tonde hanami ga saku mono ka~
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
Koko wa sanmenmachi-dokoro
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Yuku zo kanchan kokushi-musou no Sekigahara
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle of unmatched wits!
Tsumo ni mo makezu ni yarinuite
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
Katte nomihosu biiru ga umai
The beer you chug after winning tastes the best!
Zugan to otoko wa inochigake
Zugan! A man's gotta put his life on the line!
Super Zugan!
Zugan to zugan to ikaneba naranu no da
You just got to go "zugan"!