Dama in friendlies is punishable by MCD
Toyotomi Hideyoshi, King of the Negatives.
Born and raised in Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou
A "play by feel" master of Ippatsu.
Born in Chiba.
Tokugawa Yasube
An absolute nyagger with zero knowledge on theory.
Born in Chiba.
Akechi Kouichi
A by-the-book calculative and
reasoning-dependent player.
Born in Chiba.
Hayami Akina
Technically Toyotomi's girlfriend.
Born with incredible luck.
Born in Chiba.
/mjg/ presents Super Zugan
Riichi!
Heh, there it is...
I see...
Happy Birthday Zugan
Man since when were you the type
of guy to discard tiles like that?
Heh.
You're not gonna make it if you're the
sort to discard genbutsu to a riichi...
To make your read yet discard a harsh tile...
By doing so your intuition will blossom
and you'll be able to see through
the opponent's tiles!
That passes.
Pass!
Looky looky!
Come on, what'll you do with this one?
I'll let it pass...
What in the world kind of hand are you even making?
As it goes on, the one who riichi'd
will be the one cowering instead.
This is the best feeling!
Here!
Y-You're... really gonna discard that on haitei?
Eh?
That was... haitei?
Ah,
Tanyao nomi.
Ron on takame! Riichi Itsuu
Haitei Dora 1 Ura 1
Zugaaaan~
It was a dream...
Hello, Toyotomi here.
Ah, Toyotomi-kun?
I'm Hayami.
Akina-chan?!
Truth is, it's my birthday today.
Huh, is that so!
So would you like to come over for today?
Let's celebrate with the two of us.
I'll be in charge of menial things
such as cooking and the like so...
Toyotomi-kun can be in charge
of buying the cake, alright?
Welcome!
One of these decoration cakes, please!
Is it someone's birthday today?
Hehe, yup!
A girlfriend?
Can you write it down as "Akina" for me?
Should I add "from an enviable
little guy" to that?
Thank you for your patronage!
Is it your girlfriend's birthday?
Oh come on! Don't ask me the same thi-
What a coincidence!
For us to meet in a place like this!
And what I see over there is a cake is it not?
T-This is-!
Let me see!
Come on, might as well let us
deliver the cake at this point!
Ah! Don't touch that!
There's nothing to worry about, pal.
You will be coming along as well, after all.
Come on! Chop chop! Let's go!
Gaaan~
Jansou
You sure bought a grand one didn't you?
Must've cost a fortune.
Yet what happened to your fortune's
worth of dept, I wonder?
tweet twee-
Don't tweet me, junior.
We'll have you pay us back for
even a margin of that debt.
Hell's with a cake like this anyways!
Please! Just let that cake be!
Humph! If you can win, maybe.
Defeat us and the cake shall be yours.
Tsumo.
Chun, Menzen Honitsu.
Tsumo!
Tanyao, Pinfu, Dora 2!
Riichi, Tsumo, Sanankou.
Damn, this is some tanoshii mahjong.
Bet bet!
Oh come on, why'd you always have
to make a grim face like that?
You're spoiling the fun.
Ron! Pinfu, Dora 1!
2900 as dealer.
I will win this!
I'll win and spend a very happy
birthday with Akina!
Chi!
Pon!
The hell?
What's going on with that call and that pond?
There's been two hatsus discarded
already as well...
It's either an Itsuu made out of souzu
or a 123 shape sanshoku, right?
He sure doesn't learn, does he?
Ron!
Sanshoku Doukou Nomi!
That's a 2900 yoroshiku!
Toyotomi did a renchan...
How could this be?
This is my first time seeing it...
Ron! Tanyao Nomi!
Tsumo! Chun!
As the three saw Toyotomi's renchan
for the first time in their lives...
They could not help but make
their confusion apparent.
Yet Toyotomi continued to stack his wins.
And at last...
S4
It's All Last with me leading 15000
above the second place.
I'm winning by a landslide!
Nice!
I got a dora ankou!
Riichi!
Aye, same here.
Good! I got to tenpai as well.
If I'm to aim for the hidden Sanshoku,
then it's best I cut South
for the penchan on 7s.
But 7s is unlikely to come out of Toyotomi...
Shintaro's riichi looks dangerous after all...
On that note, Toyotomi's more
likely to drop 8s as a one-chance...
so I'll deliberately...
Tanki on the 9s!
Three riichis on the same turn huh? Dammit!
Come on!
It came!
A 369 wait mangan! Chun Dora 3!
If it plays out well, sanankou stacks
as well raising it to haneman!
Judging by the discards, a 9s
has 90% chances of passing!
And as long as it doesn't connect to the dealer,
there's no chances of a gyakuten.
I won...!
With this... Victory is mine!
Akina-chan, I'll soon come to you!
Congratulations, Akina-chan!
Thank you, Toyotomi- kun.
Woah, this stew's delicious!
The salad's amazing too!
What's wrong, Akina-chan?
I just thought it almost looks
like your birthday instead!
But I'm really glad you came...
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu South Dora 1, 12000!
Dahaha! Riichi Ippatsu
Pinfu Itsuu! That's 8000!
Oh boy, we both read well didn't we?
You took the words right
out of my mouth friend.
Huh? Wait, triple ron was allowed, right?
Aye! Anything goes!
Well sorry then, that's a ron from me too.
Riichi Ippatsu Honroutou
Chiitoitsu Ura 2, 16000.
Su-
Super...
Zugaaaaan~
SUPER
ZUGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAN
I beg of you... I'll play another round so...
Don't touch that cake!
Oh right, Toyotomi.
You're wearing a rather nice
jacket there ain't you?
Hey Toyotomi, you dropped
off some spare change there.
Thanks for the cake!
Sure got some nice things today, huh?
Sure did.
Toyotomi-kun sure is late...
If only...
If only he had left after slowly
eating that cup ramen...
He might have never even come across that trio.
But alas...
He could not possibly know the true worth...
Of this 129 yen cup of ramen...
Alright, riichi!
The true essence of mahjong
lies not in reading the pond...
Much more importantly...
It is to pinpoint with precision what your
opponent is thinking in minute detail.
Like "Ah, this guy will sip on some
tea in exactly 30 seconds".
That musn't be 29 seconds or 31 seconds.
But to drink it in precisely 30 seconds!
That is what one must read!
Yasu will light a cig in the next 7 seconds...
1,2,3,4,5,6,7..!
DID I DEAL IN?
You sure did.
Deal in, you did.
Riichi Sanankou Dora 1!
Come on, give me the sticks already.
"You can keep the change" you say?
Wow, how generous!
A tub...
That's right, a tub!
Rejected, Dejected
And that's yet another riichi!
What is he...
...doing?
Huh, Genbutsu. He tightened up.
The true essence of mahjong is...
A breath holding race of four under a tub!
The first to come out of the water is the loser!
Tenpai! Kanchan wait on 5m!
Pon.
Come on, swim to the surface!
Just come on already and...
Raise your head!
Tsumo!
Menzen Honitsu Iipeikou!
Just that? Look, tsumo!
Hontoutou Chiitoitsu.
Tsumo! Suuankou!
Akina-chaaan!
Good morning, Toyotomi-kun!
Sorry for being late.
It's all due to that nightmare I had...
I mean, nevermind! Let's go!
I wish to someday do the do with Akina-chan.
I wish for Toyotomi-kun to someday
stop playing mahjong.
Hey, let's try drawing some
fortune telling slips!
Sure!
I got 6!
I got 12.
Sweet, Great Luck!
How about you, Toyotomi-kun?
JAPANESE
W-Wanna try drawing another one?
Another one!
JAPANESE
Another one...
Another one!
Another one... Another one... Another one...
AnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnother
AnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOneAnotherOne
Dear Customer?
How about you stop here?
Givu me rasuto chansu!
JAPANESE
That'll be 5000 yen for everything.
But hey, even if it cost 5k, you managed to
draw a Lesser Luck, so it all paid off didn't it?
I really like that resilient part
of yours, Toyotomi-kun.
Oh? Look!
They're doing a dancing ritual over there!
What's wrong Toyotomi-kun?
Why are you scared like that?
Toyotomi-kun!
Jansou
Maybe that dream was precognitive...
Hey, Toyotomi!
Yo, it's such a coincidence!
You might as well call it fate, huh?
Weren't the three of you supposed to
go to some hot springs this week?
And go we did.
But I just got this urge to
see your face, you see.
So we came back halfway through.
And unless we get some new years allowance
from you, we can't buy souvenirs.
Hm? Ain't the slip a bit too small as it is?
Yasu... You just stay quiet, will you?
But yeah, that's how it is.
So, with hot spring manju being our starting
cash prize, let's start the first hanchan!
Huh?
Kokushi tenpai waiting tanki on South...
There's already one in the ponds...
Fuck it, riichi.
What now?
Shintaro's gimmick is ippatsu
tsumo after all, right?
I'll call it.
You little.
Hah, here comes a spicy one.
Aaah, I should've riichi'd that one too...
I would've won it with that 7s, but since
I'm yakunashi I can't win off of it...
Even though I have dora to boot...
Just tsumo it!
Rats!
Pass it!
There it is! Yakuman, Kokushi Musou!
Ron! 5200!
Sukaan~
(zugan -> sukan = dead broke)
Wait a second! That south
Toyotomi just tsumogiri'd...
If I hadn't called I'd have
tsumo'd then and there!
I didn't think about it in
the heat of the moment!
Sukan-po~
What an unlucky man I am!
At this pace... I'll never get
to eat hot spring manju!
Don't worry about it. These things happen.
I really like that resilient part
of yours, Toyotomi-kun!
T-That's right!
No matter how many times I get Great
Misfortune, I'll still draw a Lesser Luck at
the end.
Men these days have to
stick to it until the end!
Stickier than fermented beans!
I'll stick to it so hard they'll
make a fence out of me!
Watch over me Akina-chan!
I did it!
Suuankou Tenpai.
Hmm... I'll wait on it on the chun.
Chun might be a hell wait, but as long as it's
not in the dead wall, it's as good as mine!
As for 1p, as long as nobody has an
ankou of it, it should still get dropped.
But if I cut chun, then it'll be a 13p wait!
On top of that... 3p would
make it a simple sanankou!
I cannot possibly win this
hand as a mere sanankou!
Ah, to hell with it! There's no way they'll both
get dropped in the same turn anyway!
I'll wait on my 1p tank!
3p!
Geh?! Don't drop a 1p on me now!
This one... Is unnecessary.
To hell with your iipin!
Humph... In the end, the true
essence of mahjong is...
A breah holding race of four under a tub!
The first to come out of the water is the loser!
That's it! The dream from this morning!
The first one to raise his head loses!
And I cannot possibly afford to lose here!
That got me by surprise!
For me to get a Kokushi back-to-back... damn,
this is some crazy luck!
I'm at 47000.
32000 here.
I'm 80000.
Keep a tab of it, alright?
Ah, Akina-chan!
You left me all alone to play that mahjong
of yours again, didn't you?!
I don't know someone like you anymore!
Wait, there's a deeply profound reason behind all of thi-
A calm Autumn Day.
With it's vast clouds in the endless sky.
Call for the eventual change of seasons.
Where through come summer and into spring.
Lest will Toyotomi's spring ever arrive?
I ask to the vast sky with it's red dragonflies.
Unknowing to the path they thread
in the blue skies.
To which they reply, "Tomorrow shall come".
"Don't lose, Toyotomi!"
"Fight on, Toyotomi!"
If we turn Toyotomi-kun into an augmented
superhuman mahjong machine,
he might be capable of defeating the trio!
And he might return to the old Toyotomi-kun if that happens!
Next time! Super Zugan
The Toyotomi Machine of Terror and
Some title but more importantly Akina butt.
Don't miss it! Don't want to you to sleep on it!