Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
Hello?
Who is it?
Toyotomi ...
Zu... ga... n.
THE DREADFUL TOYOTOMI MACHINE
You lost against those three at mahjong again, didn't you?
Zugan.
I've made a mistake.
Tsukanpo.
I told you that you need to quit mahjong...
... but after all, that was just running away from the problem.
If you give up after losing to those people, you'll be labeled a failure together with them!
Tsukanpo?
That's why you need to strike back at them like a man!
Huh?
Tho... those are the famous ...
lucklet flowers!
Tsukanpo ...
Toyotomi, come with me for a second!
- This is ...
- My friend the mahjong pro, Mr. Ide's dojo!
Ah, Hayami! Long time no see.
This is the Toyotomi who wants to take special training from me, a Tokyo U graduate?
Yes! Please be nice to him!
Huh? Uhh ...
Got it. As a Tokyo U graduate, I'll certainly train Toyotomi to be the strongest mahjong player for you!
Aaa! No! No! Akina! AAA!
Do your best, Toyotomi!
What is this room?
I may not have told you before, but actually, I've graduated from Tokyo University.
I've already heard that three times from you!
From now on, I (a Tokyo U graduate) will teach you the foundations of mahjong using my computer program!
What's this? It's just a mahjong video game ...
TOKYO UNIVERSITY GENIUS IDE'S PERFECT MAHJONG
Indeed, until now, there's been heaps of stuff called "mahjong video games".
However, none of them are able to recreate mahjong's artistic and theoretical qualities.
That's because they're all made by upstart plebs fresh out of high school!
I like strip mahjong though ...
Idiot! That's why you're so bad at mahjong! And I (a Tokyo U graduate) am always right!
I get it, I'll do what you say, I'll do what you say!
Hmm ... Like he said, it's pretty professional looking ...
All right, let's win this! The dealer is my toimen, Ide-pro, huh ...
I have two dora. That's a decent hand!
Huh?
Tenhou ryuuiisou!
ZUGAAAAAAAN
What the hell is this game?
I (a Tokyo U graduate) must always be perfect, even within the computer!
It's quite a shit game though!
Tenhou chuuren poutou!
Zugaaaaaan!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo daisangen!
This shit again for the 2627th time since last night ...
All right ...
Let's move on to the second stage of training!
Eh?
What the hell is it this time?
This is my (Tokyo U graduate) invention, the psychic strengthening machine!
Psychic strengthening machine?!
Now, I shall let you experience virtual reality mahjong.
You will have to keep watching the images without blinking.
I can't even do that when I want to!
As you watch, your psychic state will be displayed here as a waveform.
Let's begin.
Ron! Mentanpin sanshoku iipeikou!
Zugaan!
That chair is an electric chair, through which a million volts of electric current [sic] will flow whenever your mental waves become disturbed.
Wh- what the ...!?
If you don't want to get shocked, don't let your psychic waves become disturbed.
Without a strong psyche, there is no victory in mahjong!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Ippatsu tsumo!
Ahahahaha! Yakuman!
Zugaaaaan!
Good, it's a success.
AFTER ONE MONTH
Toyotomi!
You did it, Toyotomi!
For that month, you really did your best at Mr. Ide's place!
Huh?
Toyotomi?
It's no use saying anything to him. Inside his head, it's nothing but winning at mahjong, and he won't respond to anything else.
Huh!?
He's a machine. Putting trivial emotions aside, he can steadily progress his hand with composure and logic.
He has been reborn as a machine to play mahjong.
I didn't ask you to change his personality too!
It's in order to win.
The one who has made the greatest sacrifices will win in the end!
That's ...
I'm a Tokyo University graduate!
Let's roll.
What? That's some nerve you got to challenge us.
Hey, the look in his eyes is different from usual.
Gettin' cocky, huh?
I-it's starting!
I'm a Tokyo U graduate.
What the hell?! He's sorting his tiles so fast!
This hand.
To aim thoroughly for 567 sanshoku, discard 4s.
However, the disadvantage of ending up with a bad wait is too big.
Discard 5m to lock in 678. This is the widest hand.
Even if I draw 5p, I can discard 5s and expect mangan with riichi on the dora suji.
Finally, there is discarding 5s, but this makes the hand extremely narrow if I draw 58p or 36s.
On the other hand, it leaves both kinds of sanshoku feasible.
However, if I draw 8s and try to go for 678 sanshoku, it's one move slower.
That being said, here discarding from the 5s anko early is the optimal move.
Huh? He discarded 5s?
Calm down. He's a machine.
Between drawing a tile and discarding, he calculates through a million possibilities in just 0.5 seconds ...
and makes the optimal move out of all those!
Toyotomi ...
Rooon! Sanshoku doukou sanankou tanyao dora 3!
Baiman!
Zugaan.
He dealt in!?! What was that about the optimal move?!
Hmph. Things like these are included in the calculation too.
Look closely at him!
You're right! The way he says "zugan" like always is composure itself!
Ron! Junchan sanshoku pinfu iipeikou!
Zugan.
Lucky! Pinfu ryanpeikou dora dora!
Riichi!
That's riichi ippatsu chinitsu ittsuu dora 1!
Zugan.
He's a machine!
Huh?
The precision to deal the takame every time! The stamina to keep dealing in without flinching!
No ... it can't be ...
Yes ... he has become ...
... without exaggerating, the world's strongest ...
DEALING IN MACHINE!
Remodeled into a perfect dealing in machine by the Tokyo University mahjong player Ide: Toyotomi!
Ron!
Daisangen.
Will the time ever come when he will make it?
Hang in there, Toyotomi!
Zugan.
WWYD? South 1, East seat, turn 12, 21100 points
Draw: 8m Dora: 3s
Tanyao go brr
First class ski trip! First class ski trip!
C'mon!
Ah, too bad! You win tissue paper, that's not good!
Zugan!
Let's go! All last, yakuman!
Hey, Toyotomi!
Akina!
SIGN: MAJSOUL GACHA / RATEUP NOW!
Let's goooo ...
Congratulations!
- Yay! I did it!
- Akina, you're amazing!
SNOWSIDE ZUGAN
Let's go, Toyotomi!
Okay!
Whee!
Toyotomi! Hurry up!
I'm going now! Let's go!
Let's go?
Well, that's just like you, Toyotomi!
Akina looks so cute!
But, when two people ski, that means après-ski is a matter of course!
I'm gonna come first, Toyotomi!
Just the two of us, Toyotomi ...
Yep, just the two of us, Akina!
I'm feeling a bit tipsy ...
Well, let's go to bed already then, Akina!
Oh, you shouldn't do that, Toyotomi ...
Agina ...
What's that?
This voice!
Oi! Move, move, move, move!
What the what the what the what the what the ...
That was really ...
Well! If it isn't Toyotomi!
What a coincidence!
Wew, what are the odds?
Neighboring rooms in the same inn!
You guys followed me here!
What are you on about? We won the ski trip from that same lottery too!
Makes sense that we get to stay in the same hotel!
What?! These guys too?
Hah! Meeting you here makes skiing a lot more fun!
Yeah! Let's start!
Akina!...
Hey, don't act like a spoiled kid!
Yeah, men belong in the men's world!
t. sakurai
Akinaaaa!
Pon!
That's a pon!
I'm gonna pon that chun too.
Riichi!
Shan't stop!
4m!
What a chad!
That's what I call ultra-cool mahjong!
I got to tenpai but I can't discard 4s ...
It's time for the trustworthy technique: genbutsu of two players!
Weak.
Passing the bump that is Yasu and swerving around Shintarou the frozen tree: magnificent mawashi-uchi! My parallel technique!
Ron! Tanyao sanshoku dora 1!
Zugaaaaaaan!
Zugan.
Toyotomi | Oda | Akechi | Toku
Zugaaaan ...
What's wrong, Toyotomi, last place again?
Let me play instead, Toyotomi.
Let me play instead of you.
But you're hopeless, Akina ...
I'm better than you!
Well, that's one way to put it.
Hehe, play, play with me, play together, play (get it), hehe.
Yasu, wipe your drool off.
That's a pretty good haipai.
Discard starting with the honors, like this!
Oh no, I dropped my pair of pei!
Wow ... it's another pei!
Really? That's a win for me!
I would have won from the start and you didn't tell me, Toyotomi!
Haha, lucky ... Tsumo dora 1 is 1000 all, you know.
Yay! Look, Toyotomi!
Huh? He fell over ...
Heh, that's because he's a pussy.
That's fine, I can do it by myself.
Riichi!
Because she's luckshitting ...
Wow! Ippatsu tsumo!
What!?
What, got a problem with it?
C'mon, do I have to get luckshitted on this hard?!
Ah, my bad, my bad! The tiles were stuck together, ya know!
So, pinfu ryanpeikou dora dora, or, chiitoitsu dora dora ...
Which one should I go for, hmm? Hmm?
4p was the girl's tsumo!
Riichi with this one!
Huh?
Hehe, shortcut to haneman!
Yay! I got tsumo!
Look!
The hell? 47p shanpon? Bruh ...
What a retarded wait ...
Uhh, with riichi and tsumo, and toitoi too, right?
Riichi tsumo ... toitoi?!
Oh, it's this late already, huh?
Gotta go sleep!
I'm thirsty and hungry!
Hold it!
Didn't you faint?
Yeah! I'd know!
Huh?! Fainting? What's that!?
If you want to go back to your room, pay up that 16000 all first!
Well, Akina, you just won all my money back!
Go Akina! Go Akina!
We've got a good rhythm here ...
Let's go! Double ton dora 3, ni-
Riichi.
The hell?!
What was that? This is a top hand!
It came out! My kanchan!
Riichi ippatsu double ton dora 3!
With ura being 6m, that's dealer's baiman!
Well that rocks, huh ...
What an amazing girl ...
She's first place by 300k!
Amazing, Akina! Two people dealt in and you got a yakuman!
Toyotomi, I'm sleepy ... Can I go to bed?
Yeah, sure! I'll handle it from here.
Even you should be okay with 300k points, Toyotomi.
Sorry, but I'll leave the rest to you.
Of course!
There's no way I can lose to these guys now! Easy win, easy money!
Toyotomi ...
Easy win playing against us?
There's no way I'm gonna lose to you.
All so intimidating, guys!
But a 300k point lead is not that easy to close!
Ron! Mentanpin sanshoku!
Just 8000, 300k is still a ways off ...
A ways off ... I'm basically first place already, just accept it and go for second, huh?
Ron! Menhon double ton! Damn it, that's not even haneman ...
I really needed a dora ...
Haha, 12000 is not that big either ...
It isn't!
Ron! Chiitoi dora dora!
Double ron! Ittsuu dora dora!
Oh, it's already this late, huh?
See ya tomorrow! I'm sleepy too, you know.
- Wait a minute!
- Quitting when you're ahead isn't allowed!
We won't let you sleep for another 10 hanchans!
And thus, Toyotomi's hellish après-ski night did wear on.
Ah! That dream of spending the night with sweet Akina, whither is it now?
Good morning, Toyotomi!
Huh?
Zugan.
It can't be ...
Aaa! Toyotomi, you idiot!
Zugan!
[EUROBEAT INTENSIFIES]