Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
It's from Mom!
Dear Hideyuki,
Are you doing fine?
I worry about you every day, looking up at the autumn sky.
It's getting colder day by day,
so be careful not to catch a cold.
As a result of his age, Dad's gotten a bit frailer again.
You should call us to let Dad hear your cheerful voice once in a while!
And keep doing your best in your university studies!
Yours truly, Mom
Mom ...
P.S. The student lifestyle seems to use up a lot of money.
Together with homemade umeboshi, I've sent you 50000 yen extra this month.
Treat yourself to some nice warm meals with it, okay?
MOOOOOM!
LUCKSHIT ZUGAN
What do I do now? I wasted all my textbook money on horse races ...
What? You're making fun of me, right?
It's autumn and I don't even have anything to wear!
Look! What is this?!
We're still all in summer clothes, huh ...
The autumn wind really stings ...
Anyway!
There are two methods to break out of this stock market recession brought on by the collapse of the bubble economy!
What are they?
The first is another cut to the official interest rate.
And the other is ...
Gigabuck lending from the Toyotomi Bank!
It's the only way!
Yeah!
Financial reconstruction without raising taxes!
A sound compensation for our losses!
STUDENT COOPERATIVE TEXTBOOK STORE
If I hadn't gotten that money from Mom, I wouldn't have been able to buy my textbooks!
Uh, Monetary Economics and Accounting ...
... and, uh, General Introduction to Marketing, please!
Thanks for waiting!
Took a while, didn't it?
Déjà vu ...
Toyotomi Hideyuki! We already know everything about where you go out and about!
Thou shalt give up all hope and obey!
Nooo! Please forgive me, Your Honor! I don't have any ducats ...
Eh?! There is no use in arguing! Take him away at once!
Yes sir!
What's that?
Zugan ...
Tsukan!
What's your problem? Complaining about your luck the moment you sit down to play ...
That's why ya can't ever win, bro!
Put some fight in it! Fight!
Zugan ...
Hee hee, losers!
I'm actually iishanten for tanyao dora 3!
I'm just pretending to be tilted so they don't notice!
2m!
Pon!
Nice! My kanchan filled up.
This's got to be riichi!
Zugan ...
C'mon, give me a good draw!
Real lucklet hours ...
However ...
Shan't fold!
Really? It came out?
That's ron from me.
Just riichi ippatsu.
Hey!
This one's uradora!
It got expensive: mangan!
What?! That was like the last tile!
Check 'em!
Checking them digits.
Getting the last 7s to come out on ippatsu ...
Well, it's got to be that!
Oh no no ...
Oh no ...
That which is called hell's gathering trumpet ...
AAAA!
Oh no! It's really the luckshitting alarm!
What?!
To luckshit (verb):
Mahjong jargon for stacking up point sticks in a splendid amount.
When mahjong players feel they have entered luckshitting mode, even just a little bit ...
... raising the alarm in advance for their opponents is considered good etiquette.
Mahjong: indeed a game only for the truest of gentlemen!
Wow! This is a pretty good hand!
Double riichi!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Luckshit tsumo!
Double riichi ippatsu tsumo chiitoi, 6000 all!
Big luckshit!
REEEE!
Just this after a hanchan, huh ...
My form's kind of bad today ...
Kys faggot.
REMATCH
Tsukan.
Tenpai!
I can win a tanpin sanshoku!
>dama
ngmi
Come out!
Riichi!
Wait a ...!
What?
I called riichi!
Dealer's riichi, you know.
At last I truly see ...
Whenever I'm in tenpai with a good hand ...
It's a trap!
It's an obvious trap!
Making such a good hand, and drawing that riichi's winning tile on the ippatsu turn?
I shiggy diggy.
All right, Mr. Big Shot, chop chop!
Well, there's no rush.
Wut?
Once I draw that tile, my fate is to destroy my hand or deal in ...
It's all right now ...
I shan't die kicking and screaming!
But, I wish, I wish ...
At least let me have dreams for a little while more!
Hey you! Stop crying and draw already! C'mon!
Got it.
Just look at it.
It's his winning tile just like I thought.
The god of mahjong seems to like inequality!
Good grief!
Well then! Let's just fold with genbutsu.
Wait!
What kind of boomer crap are you saying?!
Akina ...
You're still young, aren't you?!
Why aren't you risking it with this hand?!
Well, going from previous experience, this is usually the dealer's winning tile ...
Such weakness is for boomers!
Aaa!
Young players should have the willpower to make a comeback even when they deal in!
t. sakurai
That's no good, Akina!
If it passes, it will pass!
It passed.
We did it, Toyotomi!
Hehe, riichi, that was a riichi!
(TN: This is against the rules.)
Oof, sketchy ...
Rooon! Mentanpin ippatsu sanshoku!
Yay!
What?!
Now it's your turn to luckshit, Toyotomi!
Let's go, luckshit alarm!
This is bad! Even if it's just Toyotomi, once he hits the groove it's bad!
Gotta get him off the dealer fast!
Holy!
I tsumo'd ...
As dealer, tsumo dora 1 is 1000 all ...
Wait! I'm in luckshit mode right now!
Discarding this one and going furiten riichi on 369p 47p is the only choice!
Riichi!
That's right!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
Luckshit tsumo!
SUPERB! Big luckshit!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo tanyao sanshoku dora dora! Bang bang!
Nooooo! We're gonna get bullied! It's here!
ALL LAST
Wow! So many point sticks! You guys really choked, huh?
If we see some blood later, that's on me.
It's alright now, Toyotomi!
Since you have enough money, I'm gonna go!
Right on! Leave it to me!
I did it! 369m three sided tenpai!
The dora is 7m.
Push straightaway like a retard: luckshit riichi!
Huh? It stopped!
Toyotomi screwed up.
No matter how hard you are luckshitting, when you are first place in all last and can win with dama ...
... no matter if you have a 3 sided wait or a 100 sided wait, you must NOT riichi!
It feels like you'll win even if you riichi. However, it's a trap!
A textbook example of a trap!
Fodl.
Same.
Shan't fodl as dealer!
Pass pls!
THE SPICY HAITEI
C'mon, tsumo with haitei!
Fffffffuuuuuuu
Wut?! It came out?!
Ron! Menhon haitei chiitoi dora dora!
Super Zugan.
It's my turn now!
Check it out! Suuankou tsumo!
Zugan!
Secretly, Toyotomi took a part-time job as an office cleaner to learn how to wipe the floor (with his opponents) ...
Oi! Scrub harder!
You're a real scrub at wiping the floor!
Don't do that dumb smile when you skip a spot!
Dear Mom,
I got your package.
Your umeboshi were really tasty!
I bought textbooks with the money you sent me.
Take care of your health too, Mom.
Give my earnest regards to Dad.
Mrs. Toyotomi Noe, Anegasaki City, Chiba Prefecture
However, this letter did not end up getting mailed in the end.
East 3, West seat, turn 9, 27600 points
Tsumo: 5p Dora: 4s
Read RB1
AKINA AGAIN
Wait, which round are we in again?
Toyotomi, how much points you got?
Exactly 10000, huh ...
So next round is East 4.
Having Toyotomi around really is useful.
Yep.
Wut?
You can look at Toyotomi's point sticks to know which round it is.
Whoa!
After East 1, he ends up with 20000 points.
After East 2, he usually still has over 10000.
Then, he gets shadowrealmed in East 4.
Up to minus 25k in all last, you can tell pretty precisely.
Got it.
A real convenient lad ...
I made it!
Pinfu dora 1 with possible tanyao and a three sided wait!
That's a riichi!
Chii!
Look!
White!
Pon!
Look!
Pon.
3m.
Chii!
2m!
Pon. Look!
Chii!
6m!
Zugan.
Ron!
AAAAAA!
Zugandhi.
Whoa, Toyotomi got shadowrealmed! Time for South!
Riichi!
Nonviolent resistance.
Ippatsu!
Toyotomi! Toyotomi!
Huh? Akina!
You were here after all!
So what's up today?
Well, there's a concert by Yoneyone Club today ...
Wanna go?
Gettin' asked out by a girl!?!
I'm a huge fan of that band as well, what are the odds?
Anuttara-samyak-sambodhi ...
What the hell is that?!
Akina ...
I'm sorry, but Toyotomi can't go with you.
What's wrong?
Right now, Toyotomi's losing by this much.
As long as he's got these losses, there's no way we'll let him get out of here.
That's the rule around here.
Ya don't say! By how much is he losing?
Wut's dis?
The Chiba dialect really spread to her too, huh?
Minus 120k?
Aight! I'mma get that all back for ya!
Ya clear off to yonder, bro!
Dumb girl.
"I got a bit lucky the first time so I'm gonna play again?"
She really thinks she can win against us twice in a row!?
By the way, if Akina loses, she can pay off her losses with something else than money ...
What the!?
I wonder what!
Paying with her body or what?!
Yasu, she can hear us!
Whatcha all yappin' about?!
Let's go, chop chop!
EAST 1
Wow! That's a pretty good hand!
Ah, that's a chii!
Ryanmen chii with a good hand?!
Maybe honitsu?
4p!
No ... She wouldn't have discarded 7s that early with honitsu.
I've got a triplet of the dora ...
It's got to be just a tanyao sanshoku!
Hayami's wait is obviously 3p kanchan!
This one!
Oh, should I ron it?
A real cheap wait.
Well, let's win this, howzat?
Just shousangen, dealer's mangan.
What the?! If ya'd waited a turn, ya'd've tsumo'd the hatsu!
Whaaat?! No way!
If I cut 3p instead, I'd get tsumo'd for 16000 all ...!?
Aaa! Should've skipped ron!
Toyotomi, you're such an idiot!
She's crazy about him ...
Guess girls ain't got the nerve to gamble, huh ...
t. sakurai
This is it ... If I hesitate, I'm not gonna make it against these lads ...
Get her off the dealer quick!
Ah! Wait a second!
Oh no no no!
Uhh ...
Sorting her tiles like that ...
Closed chinitsu! Haneman!
Super cheap wait!
AAAA!
Hee hee! Let's go!
Chiitoi dora dora tenpai, hehe!
To aim for Akina, 8p will come out real easy from her!
Wut?!
It was the 2s after all!
The nan's gonna come out for sure!
Wut?!
Pei? Go for this one? Wait ...
Shan't change anymore!
Not this!
What the hell?!
Aaa! I drew a triplet of dora!
Rooon!
Super expensive wait!
Pinfu ryanpeikou dora dora!
Nothing but suffering! Curse my life!
A traveler ... why come you here?
Rejected by fortune and luck, I have lost all dreams and hope.
Gaze upon the sea.
When men grow fond of the sea at times like these, they can lay bare their true selves.
From now on, I shall live for my memories ...
What is this power?! She's wearing us down hand by hand!
She's beating us down so hard we don't stand a chance to recover.
However, she has no idea what's she doing!
What a luckshitting girl!
You did it! And we ended up 60k in the green too!
It really worked out well in the end, my Akina's show of strength!
Yep, Toyotomi!
Super Zugan.
All right lads, accept that you lost, don't be shy!
Hey, Toyotomi! Since we made a real comeback win, we should go eat something tasty to celebrate!
Okay! Sushi! Steak! Spanish food!
No way! There's no way we can eat all of that!
Yeah, I guess you're right!
But before that: concert!
Damn it!
I won't allow it!
I shan't allow this at all!
Overcoming the long age of darkness and finally achieving happiness like a normal person: Toyotomi!
His heart was as clear as the autumn sky.
However, just like a clear autumn sky, his happiness was not meant to last long.
A haiku:
Players' deal-in tiles:
Gathering them, before long
Double shadowrealm.
Thank you for listening.
TN: The original haiku by Basho is
Heavy rains in May:
Gathering them swiftly flows
Mogami River.