Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
How about it? Akina's already beat us twice.
But she's only played us twice.
In the long run, we're certain to win.
Ya sure? I think that girl's luck is the real deal.
The real deal?
Just like how Toyotomi's a natural lucklet,
I feel like that girl's retarded luck is something she was born with.
Hmm, you bet!
You're a pussy.
As soon as we get a grip on her, we'll invite Hayami to a hotel for a mahjong all-nighter.
I call it:
Operation Hoihoi Anglerfish!
YOU ARE PERFECTION PART 1
Whee! Let's go!
Whee! Tsukan.
You can't return at all, huh?
Why is she still with Toyotomi?
Bro, it makes total sense.
Didn't ya hear that wherever Toyotomi goes, Hayami goes?
Heh, he's got no clue like always!
Okamoto Fuyuki's clueless like always!
Takada Kaiko's pretty dumb too!
- Idiot ...
- Gulp.
- Shh!
Well, it's pretty hard!
These grade schoolers've been getting smart lately!
Well, the president of batting is doing his best!
Sorry for the wait!
You were pretty fast!
C'mon, let's start!
Hey, me too, me too!
Who ever said we were gonna play with you?!
We came here today to play mahjong with Akina, bro.
Just because Akina brought you along doesn't mean you get to act all cocky!
Wh- what?!
It's fine! Let's all just play together, okay?
Well, so be it. Draw for who skips?
Whoever draws the 1m sits out first, and then in order, all right?
4m.
2m.
3m.
1m!
Your draws are shit like always, huh?
Tsukanpo.
Riichi!
A fast hand like always ... Chii!
Genbutsu!
Aww, I didn't tsumo.
Good wall shift!
4p?
She might have tsumo'd ...
Aight! Tsumo only. 400/700.
Aww! I had such a good wait too ...
If Shintarou had drawn 8p or 9p, the 7p'd have come out.
What the hell?! If I didn't call, she'd get 4p for ippatsu tsumo!
She'd win a haneman!
EAST 2
Riichi!
The fuck is this girl?
Out of nowhere on the third turn ...
It's tanpin sanshoku if I stay closed ...
No, I have to.
7p chii!
Fuck, I called a completed group ...
No ippatsu? Whatever.
7m.
If I didn't go for it, it'd be Hayami's draw ...
I made it!
C'mon, tsumo!
Tsumo! 500/1000!
Aww ... I had such an expensive hand ...
What the hell's that?!
Getting ippatsu tsumo on a fucking 7m penchan?!
Holy rigged luckshit.
Whatever ... Calm down, calm down.
I already cucked her out of her haneman twice.
Her luck's gotta have left her a bit.
Riichi!
Her luck was so supposed to ebb and then she riichis on turn 2?!?
And I can't call it ...
Call it, Shintarou!
Oh, uh, I already drew!
Let him call! Otherwise she's definitely gonna tsumo!
Aight! Yasu, call it!
Wut? How the hell am I supposed to call with this kokushi?!
Oh no no no no no ...
Riichi hatsu ippatsu tsumo!
AAAAA!
All right, my dealer turn now!
Aight, fags! Get her off the dealer even if it kills ya!
Yes sir!
Huh?
Double riichi!
Somebody call this!
Call!
Bruh, don't say dumb shit like that when I can't call your tile!
Call this!
What about this!?
Call it plox!
We're fucked.
It's over.
Goodbye, my point sticks ...
6000 should be enough, right?
All- huh?
No ippatsu!
That's right! There's no way she can tsumo ippatsu every time!
She had me worried for a sec there!
Yep, why did we get all fired up about that, hehe ...
Whoa! Second draw tsumo!
Whoa! The uradora is 3m!
Double riichi tsumo menhon chun sanankou ura ura!
6000 all wasn't enough ...
What the?! Ya'd've gotten ippatsu tsumo with the 7m!
Wow, really?!
Wait: 123567m
She missed an ippatsu tsumo dealer's baiman and got a sanbaiman anyway?!?!
However, this girl started by calling riichi on turn 4 ...
Turn 3, turn 2, double riichi, her tenpai got faster every fucking time ...
Which means that the next one is ...!
Yay! I already won at the start! Bo-ring!
Tenhou ...
Well, there's no point in going for anything other than the fastest tenpai now!
Riichi! It's cheap, somebody deal in!
It's just a riichi nomi!
You fag! Lying to us so ya can get second place?!
Retard! Don't say such retarded shit!
Oh, it came out! That's my winning tile!
A bit of a waste, but 9600.
Well at least we know who's gonna be last, kek.
Faggot ...
Aight, second place, let's go!
Ron!
Wh- whaaat?!
Pinfu sanshoku dora dora! 8000! Pay up, fag!
Ya were aimin' for me?! FOR ME?!
Until now, these three friends' teamwork had been based on the great assumption that they wouldn't steal points from each other.
Now, this strong bond was broken.
I'll get my renchan whatever it takes!
Ron! 1000 plox!
This fag ... Breaking off my last dealer turn with his shitty 1000!
- Here you go, fag!
- Ow!
Hey! That's not the right way to give people sticks!
Oh really?! My bad then!
My bad?! It hurt!
What?! Aren't ya supposed to be buddies?!
Right now, getting rid of Hayami's luckshitting is the highest priority.
Well, I guess Shintarou's right. Whatever ...
Gottem! Junchan sanshoku dora dora!
Aaa! You won!
Heh, what a scrub! Should've checked the discards!
Hey! Here's your fucking point sticks, faggot!
What the fuck did ya just do, you little niggerfaggot!?!
Shut up! You started it with your bullshit win first!
Stop it, retards!
- What's your problem?!
- Ow!
Next game is your turn to sit out!
So fuck off!
No, you fuck off!
[seething continues]
If they keep seething like this, maybe I can even win!
No! I'm certainly going to win!
Next hanchan, I'm definitely going to finish 3rd!
You can do it, Toyotomi!
Oda & Co's so-called terrifying Operation Hoihoi Anglerfish ...
Collapsed quickly before Akina's retarded luck.
However, the struggle is not yet over.
What Akina didn't know is that Toyotomi's ultimate lucklet skill was about to reveal itself!
South 2, East seat, turn 8, 18900 points
Tsumo: 3m Dora: West
>muh sanshoku
ngmi
All right ...!
Boring ... My turn to sit out, huh?
Wow!
YOU ARE PERFECTION PART 2
Akechi, who's usually so calm, just spurted noodles out of his nose!
Does Hayami have such an amazing haipai?
I'll chii that right away!
Sanshoku dora 1 iishanten.
Hey, nice call!
Chii!
Alright, I'm in tenpai!
Wow, pretty!
36p shousuushii tenpai ...
That stylish Akechi is so dumbfounded that a shrimp is hanging from his nose!
Is she in tenpai?!
I did it! Turn 3 tenpai with possible pinfu! SUPERB!
3p!
Whoa! It came out ...
Shan't ron it.
Toyotomi looks so happy, I don't want to throw him so deep into the shadowrealm right away ...
Relax. If it's 36p, I can easily tsumo it!
Aaa! She drew it?!
What the ...
There's definitely something going on ...
5p, huh ...
Those discards, letting me call 2s and 2p ...
5p should pass.
What is this sudden chill?!
It's gonna be like a pinzu chinitsu or something ...
Yeah, something like that!
What a flowmaster!
Phuh, tsumogiri.
My shousuushii that was only 48k just became a quadruple yakuman worth 192k ...
It'd be mean to ron him now after skipping earlier ...
What does she have with this guy?! Just ron him, ron him!
Well, I'll just draw!
Reeeee!
Tch, the 5p passed, huh?!
Whoops.
Gasp! Shintarou's still got a white!
Since he cut one earlier, it'll come out next turn for sure!
C'mon! Tsumogiri!
Why is this guy such a lucklet?
But since I can ron Shintarou's white with a yamagoshi trap, I'll skip ron!
C'mon! Drop the white!
It came out!
8m ron!
No!
Don't do it!
- Ron! Ron!
- No! No!
Don't ron me, okay? Please?
Toyotomi ....
It can't be helped, huh ...
Wow, you're so sweet! I love you, Toyotomi!
Heh, get rekt!
Ron! Pinfu only!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Mahjong is a cruel game, baby.
Toyotomi, you idiot!
Wew, Toyotomi, you're such a cruel guy.
Ya made poor Akina cry.
What, it's just 1000 points! Is she really so arrogant that she thinks she can never deal in?!
Shut up, Toyotomi.
Akechi, ya still got a noodle sticking from your nose.
I'll have ya know that Akina ...
It's fine, Akechi. Sorry. Let's continue.
Tch! Girls are such a bother sometimes! C'mon!
Ron! Tanyao iipeikou dora dora!
Zugan!
That was fast! It's only turn 6!
Heh, at least cheer up a bit!
Ron! Pinfu sanshoku dora 1!
Zugan!
Haitei dora dora!
Zugaaan!
Riichi menhon nan sanankou!
Zugan!
Honroutou shousangen!
She's totally focusing on Toyotomi!
It's revenge! This is her revenge!
I didn't win a single hand cuz ya kept dealing in, ya tool!
Enough is enough!
Even if it's just a drop of water in a raging fire, I'll get back some points in all last!
Pon!
Chii!
Naked tanki!
Hehe, make sure ya don't catch a cold, bro!
I'mma open riichi!
Riichi!
It's a 25p wait riichi, lads.
TN: Dealing into an open riichi is a yakuman.
What's that!?
There are three of each already out!
Still two left. Now check Toyotomi get them!
Well, someone's got to have them in hand ...
I feel like I'll draw them ...
Super Zugan!
Looks like he drew it for real!
He dropped the dora from his hand!
Wew, this one's live!
TN: "Live" means "not discarded yet", not "unsafe"
Pon!
C'mon, tsumo!
Don't be 5p ...
Sketchy ...
Pon!
Oh no no no no no ...
[mindbroken by the cunny]
What's wrong?
A- Akina ...
What is it?
Sorry for ronning you for 1000 earlier ...
That was my fault, I regret it now ...
Don't say stuff like that! I don't care about that any... *twitch* more at all!
It's fine now, so just discard quick!
That's a face that says "I really care".
More like "I'm really pissed".
Bye!
Ron!
Daisuushii tsuuiisou!
ZUGAAAAAAAN
Triple yakuman!
If ya cut 2p, it'd be just a single yakuman, what a retard!
Zugaaaan!
With Toyotomi playing, we still somehow broke even!
It was really fun, guys!
We should all meet up again!
What are you so excited about, Toyotomi?
Huh?
Nobody said that includes you.
Without Toyotomi, the ones who are gonna lose are us!
Yeah, you're right!
Uhh, Hayami, could you go back on that and let Toyotomi in too?
All right! Then, let's go, everyone!
Uhh, what about me?
Since you're the only one who lost, you can walk back home as a punishment!
Noooooo!
Akina ...
At last given the cold shoulder by Akina: Toyotomi!
The cold rain pouring down on this bribery ... could it be the tears flowing from his broken heart?
Don't try and stop me, mother!
The man Toyotomi: where will he go?
TN: This line parodies a famous poster from the 1968 student unrest.