Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Oi! Be right back! Fill in for me!
Toyotomi! Number 4 needs to fill in!
All right!
I'm up by about 10k, so you can take it easy.
Okay!
Wow, it's just the 3rd day Toyotomi's working here, but he's really doing well!
Whoa, nice haipai!
Go easy on us, all right, Mr. Job Student?
Aye, mate.
Riichi!
What?! Double riichi?
BEFORE LONG, ALL LAST
Riichi.
Crikey! Again?!
Give us a break!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo pei!
Toyotomi, what the hell did you do today?!
Well, you saw me, right?
But isn't something bad bound to happen sooner or later?
No way! It's all skill!
OBJECT X FROM STRAYA OSAKA
Akina ...
Who the hell is this?!
C'mon, fight me!
Who are you?!
Stop it!
Oi, s'matter, mate?
You're the customer who got shadowrealmed by me in the mahjong parlor where I work!
That's some bloody good exposition!
Aye! I'm just a uni student who ain't got a brass razoo to gamble with.
But, seeking to calm me ticker, once in a while I chance into a parlor.
What the hell are ya on about?
In that parlor, me ticker ...
Ya gave me peace of mind in that place, mate.
Ya flogged all me point sticks like it was nothing!
And what's more, ya flogged me of me place to sleep.
Bro ...
But, happiness is found amid sorrow, mate.
And I shan't give up that bloody chance once I've found it!
And it's you who gave that chance to me, boss!
Boss?!
Of course, mate!
I had a hunch back in that parlor ...
Aye! I respect this bloke from the depths of me ticker!
This bloke's ripper to be me boss!
Really?!
Aye, she'll be right, mate.
So who the hell are you?!
Wake the fuck up!
Oi, boss! Ya look buggered, mate.
Of course! I didn't get a wink of sleep tonight!
Ya got work today, mate?
No.
Then how 'bout we get a group going for some hard yakka of pussers bones?
No, just go back to Straya!
What do ya think this is, bush week?
Ya'r me boss, mate!
Oi, Sheila! Another cuppa, please.
Who the hell are you!
Hey guys! Have you been here long, Toyotomi?
No, I just got here!
Crikey!
Much obliged to me boss.
Ah, I'm Hayami, nice to meet you. Who is this?
Akina, ignore him!
By the way, do you perhaps play at mahjong, dear Akina?
Yeah, I do!
Ya bewdy!
Playing pussers' bones with such a spunk's been me dream since ever!
Let me go!
Who else should we invite?
Hey, that's my address book!
Akechi, Oda and Tokugawa're gonna rock up, and maybe even Baba!
Tea 'n' bickies! Okay!
Pillows! Okay!
Point sticks! Okay!
Matches for the fags! Okay!
Righto!
Boss and the missus can sit down already!
Long time no see!
Ya'r right on time, mate!
EAST 1
Oi, Baba! Hear up, mate!
By the way, who is this guy?
In Osaka, I'm called Ken the Pouncing Cunt!
Whoa, really ...
Scary ... Baba-pro is still a pro after all. Isn't he being a bit rude?
I'm a C League pro.
Ya bewdy! Mate, this haipai's a pearler!
Oi, ripper!
Bit loud, aren't you ...
Haku.
Pon nya!
Chun.
Scary stuff.
That's suji.
Oi, wait a minute there, mate.
Did I deal in?
Nah, it passed, mate. Made ya bloody spooked though, didn't I?
What a faggot!
Wally's the pretty bone, so with the trolley bus I get blood and blanket with two pretties.
That's a bloody mango, mate!
All right, riichi!
Crikey!
Pon nya!
Pretty bone pon nya!
She let me pluck the pretty bone too!
Gotta be a shonky reachie!
Oi, crikey!
Pass.
Righto, let's tie up this honey mango!
Crikey!
Kan nya!
Wally kan nya!
Dirty oldies and all pairs with ten pretties!
That's a counted yakka mango!
Oi, gimme a good pluck!
Bloody hell, mate!
Yay, it came out!
Riichi only!
What the bloody hell's that?!
Hey! I got 7 ura dora!
Mangan?
That's a baiman.
Bloody cunt!
Ayami, mate.
TN: He's forgotten Akina's name.
Ya came a bloody gutser calling a reachie with the pretty bone!
Oh, why's that? It's a suji trap.
As if I'm gonna bugger off with me bloody exy hand!
But you discarded the 8m anyway!
t. adeptchad
Yeah-nah, whatever ya reckon.
So what's the problem then?
About time to show how strong pros are to Akina!
The ideal discards.
Riichi!
If I win this hanchan ...
Baba, you're amazing!
I've always wanted to be held by such a strong guy!
I'll "hold" ya all right!
Like that ...
Heh, nice 3p kanchan!
Oi, Baba, it ain't funny, mate.
If I know his wait, I'm dead set to win this!
- 6s.
- Pon!
- 5s.
Dinkum colour, all mids and pairs!
Good on me! Coming back for a double mango right after getting do boned!
5m.
Ron!
Boss!
I shan't let ya discard the five rick!
What? It's the riichi's genbutsu!
As if! The reachie's ridgy-didge, but ya gotta fold against the other blokes too!
I reckon ya need to go for the one chance squadron, mate!
What the hell's your problem?!
Iipeikou dora 1!
Crikey!
Holding me squadrons and me gates!
And she's got a pair of Baba's traffic lights!
Hooly dooley!
Boss!
I gotta tell ya something!
All right, mate?
There's a few things ya should never let go of in ya life!
I'm talking about friendship and justice, mate!
It's the loyalty!
The deep bond between boss and his true blue bloke!
Fair suck of the sauce bottle ...
Me losses are boss's losses!
What?!
But, boss's wins are me wins too!
Aye, we two shall never be sundered apart, mate!
Fuck off with that selfish shit!
AND THEN, ALL LAST
No worries, mate.
I flogged the pro good and I'm in first place by heaps!
It's still not over yet, ya know.
Aye, got it, mate!
I got a 10k lead in all last, I can win this with me peepers closed, mate!
You said it, now you gotta win with your eyes actually closed.
Whatever ya reckon! Just watch me win this, mate!
But, youse gotta say the bones out loud!
6s.
3p.
Chun.
Ton and riichi!
Oi, wazzat?
Crikey! That's a seven double-ups if I ever saw one!
I'll discard the jimmy rick!
Yay, it came out!
Riichi ippatsu menhon shousangen chanta dora dora!
How much is that as dealer?
TN: You should be able to solve this
Oi, boss!
It was just for a jiffy, but good on ya for taking care of me.
Aye, see ya later, alligator! Hooroo!
This world is cash! Cash makes the world go round!
That is the Way of Osaka Finance!
TN: A popular '90s manga
The mysterious man from Osaka: self-called Ken the Pouncing Cunt!
To be continued.
South 1, West seat, turn 9, 19200 points
Draw: 5s Dora: 7p
Discard 9s for damaten but 6s for riichi.
TN: ?????
All right, Toyotomi, you're the daihinmin again!
Zugan!
Boss! Boss!
Deal 'em to me too, mate!
Kenoath, mate, ya'r me boss!
Shhh!
All the seats in this tourist express are reserved, so if they find out there's 5 of us we're screwed!
Whatever ya reckon, mate, but I wanna play too!
Who the hell are you?
Actually, I don't know either.
That's right, who are you?
Yous a bunch of bloody dags!
Boss 'n' Akina 'n' Baba too!
We did all that hard yakka playing pussers bones together yesterday!
My name is Kenjin.
I come from Osaka.
I hadn't a brass razoo, I was all buggered up!
That's when I met me boss.
I was never your boss, bro ...
When I say ya'r me boss then ya'r me bloody boss, mate!
Righto, mate? I'm your personnel from now on.
If it weren't for me boss's future'd be all buggered up!
All right, let's continue playing daihinmin!
Let's go, let's go!
Bloody hell, boss!
You again? We let ya come with us already so shut up!
HOT SPRING FEVER ZUGAN
Howzat! I'll start.
Carn!
Ace!?
Pass.
Heh, what an idiot, starting off with that card!
Ya don't know the rules?
If ya got the same mark lined up it's fine too, right?
Yeah, with at least 3 cards.
So howzat?
Pass.
Oi! Onya! I done won this bewd!
Zugan.
Oi, mate, gimme two aces!
Shouldn't have let you come with us ...
I'm scared!
It's fine!
Relax!
Oi! Oi! If ya can't stand this either then ya'r a bloody dag!
Stop it!
Crikey!
Baba!
Come help us!
Since it rained yesterday, it's nice there's so much water flowing!
Yeah, it is.
Welcome to our inn!
Thank you so much!
There's four of you in all?
Yeah, there's four of us, not five!
Oi, I'm not lying! That's why they call me "honest Yasu"!
Well then, please take it easy.
- Should've shut up, retard!
Ow!
Oi, boss, ya can come out now.
That was horrible, let's go take a bath!
I'll go too!
Comfy!
The hot water's really nice!
Boss!
What's your problem?!
Well to be fair, that door's direct access to the sheila's pool!
What?!
Everybody dive!
Lucky! There's nobody here!
It feels so good!
You're all a bunch of pervs ...
So why did she slap just me?
Boss! That's love, mate, love!
All right, let's go, let's go!
All right.
I have to win this freeloader's share too.
Boss, do your best!
All right!
To widen the hand, what should I discard?
Nah, whatever ya reckon, mate!
Here ya should keep the nan a safe tile and cut the 4m!
You should really shut up!
These blokes've got quick hands!
If ya greed ya'r gon get outpaced!
Riichi!
Aye, told ya so, mate.
Hehe, now deal in quick!
I have no safe tiles! What should I do?
Leave it to me, boss!
We'll use the method of elimination!
The method of elimination?
All right! First off, the 25p we have 4 of is no good.
We also shan't discard the 36s we have 3 of.
The 4m and 5s are ura suji, so those are the mainline!
The 6p riichi discard was either from 566 or from 246!
So that means 3p and 4p are the most dangerous!
So that mean ... 3m!
Of course, we shan't discard that either because it's dora!
We shan't discard anything at all!
Oh for crying out loud, mate!
Well, ya told me to figure it out, so why ya gettin' all sour now?
Oi, it don't matter if I told ya whatever!
So what are ya gonna discard?!
When I don't have safe tiles, I'll cut this and advance my hand!
Wut? It passed.
All right ...
6s!
That's the same tile!
All right!
Slam! 4m riichi!
Muh sanmenchan ...
C'mon ...
The cheaper out ...
Riichi pinfu tsumo dora 1 ...
Ya what, mate?
Ya forgot to check the ura!
Poggers!
Boss!
Menpin tsumo dora 3!
That's a haneman!
EAST 2
Here ya should ride the flow and riichi!
I don't know where the dora is ...
I'll play it safe and dama!
Ya'r a bloody pussy, mate.
What are you two whispering about?
Riichi!
It came!
Let's cut 9m and call riichi!
Let's go ...
Hey!
Hindsight is 20/20! C'mon!
Wow!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo chiitoi dora dora!
Aww, come on!
I was waiting on the white too ...
Check 'em!
Boss ... I kneel ...
What about the ura?
Aaa, it didn't come up?!
It should have come, what is this?
You're getting unlucky, boss.
What are you guys on about? Riichi!
NEXT ROUND
Rich people ... what was it again?
Shouldn't pick fights, boss.
Ron! 3900.
You were in the game too, hehe.
Oi, do yer best, mate!
Ron! 2000!
Dama 2000? Are you okay winning that?
It goes to next round so that's even good for us!
Ron! 1300.
Doesn't matter!
Ron! 1500.
Too small! Don't care!
Ron! 2900 is 3200!
Whatever!
Tenpai.
I'm the only one noten, really?
Boss, this isn't the time to be the only one laughing ..
ALL LAST
Uh, 24000 points!
I got 24800.
25000 exactly.
26200 ...
A solid first place with 2200 over last place???
Boss ...
Wh-what?
Now, the time to repay my boss has come.
The truth is, in Osaka I am called "Getaway Ken".
My profound apologies for not revealing it earlier.
My technique of running away in all last ...
Drink your beer and observe it carefully!
I'll leave it to you.
TURN 4
A ryanshanten with sanshoku chance. The dora is 9m?
Shan't need it!
What are you ...?!
To take 1st, you need a fast hand more than points!
Read RB1.
That's no way to get first place!
You can! You totally can!
You missed tenpai for sanshoku dora 3!
Doesn't matter.
This iishanten has a much better shape!
Let's go.
Ron!
Pinfu dora 1! 2000!
2200 more than last
deal in for 2000
LAST PLACE
Bloody hell! Just no luck today!
La-last place ...
If you get last, it will last ...
Gambling is about luck after all, boss!
We're going back!
Let it flow away ...
All of the sad memories ...
Let them flow away in this river ...
Boss! Am I just a paper lantern to you?!
"The record with my memories of you of yesteryear is still playing..."
Is what Toyotomi was thinking.
"Let the pain, let the pain fly away."