Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
Sir? We have a delivery for you.
We have a delivery for you, sir.
Thanks, now where did I put my signing seal ...
No, it's fine!
Rather, please take care of this package.
Thank you for your work.
What the?!
A babby?!
BABY JANSHI PONTA
Oi, why so cranky, mate?
ASDFAFDGAFGHDFHGSAFHG
Yeah, it's an ankle biter!
Berro berro bah!
Aww, he's heaps cute, this kid, boss!
So is he yours?
My kid?!
There was a letter in there, it's not mine!
I'M TIRED
PLEASE BE NICE
t. SINGLE MOM
No way! I'm still a virgin so there's no way I could have a kid!
All right. I'm going to school.
Wait! Why are you going to school right now?!
I'm actually a faithful and serious student.
And I think we should let the police know about the kid asap.
Hooroo!
What a cold-hearted guy!
I feel sorry for him ... I should give him some toy!
I only have this ...
Look! Come play, they're blocks!
Chinitsu ...
You know mahjong?!
No way ... Then, what's the wait? Can you tell?
Shewen!
What!?
That's a coincidence, right ...
What's the cheaper out for this hand?
He's a genius!
So that's what happened.
So that Toyotomi's got an illegitimate child, huh ...
Akina, it's time to forget that guy and be happy with me!
Ridiculous.
You think Toyotomi knows how babby is formed?
Well ... Oh, that's ron!
Riichi ippatsu chinitsu!
Whatever you say, it's exactly what happened!
Well, speak of the devil.
Toyotomi, is that baby even related to you?
Great question!
This is a gift from God, my wonder baby!
Why you!
It really is your baby after all!
No it's not ...
This is a heaven-sent baby, Ponta the mahjong genius!
Ponta the baby genius?!
Well, just watch.
Heh, fucking Toyotomi! There's no way a baby can win in a mahjong parlor! Don't fuck with me!
All right, turn 3 damaten. I got this in back.
Wow, what a nishe dwaw!
Dama! Dama!
Wow! Uncle's in dama?
Don't say dumb shit like that.!
3m waith!
A 3m wait!
Have ya stooped so low that ya have to rely on that brat?!
Aww, looks we hit bullseye, Oda!
His voice is all shaky! Look, riichi!
That fucker! Discarding the fucking dora ...
Don't fuck with me!
Mentanpin ippatsu sanshoku dora dora iipeikou!
Wow, and we got double ura! Dealer's sanbaiman!
So! Have you realized his true power?!
Ya got too cocky thinking it was just a brat, Shintarou.
What?!
There's no place for affection in the world of gambling.
You must not go easy even on women or children.
Oh, it came out! Sanshoku dora 1, 5200!
He's loud! Stop crying! Hey, give me my point sticks!
Ow!
What's this brat's problem?!
Oh no! Why is Ponta being so difficult?
You pissed yourself.
Oh no!
All right, let's get you cleaned up!
Don't overdo it.
Okay, now let's play!
Aww,  we cleaned you up and now out draws are good too!
Riichi!
I said I'll go easy on him, but if he calls riichi then I'll call.
Chii!
Wut? Don't eat the tile!
Give it back!
We'll make you puke it up!
He's really chewing on it!
Ew, it's all dirty! Shan't call it anymore!
If you don't call ...
Ippatsu tsumo!
As expected of you, Toyotomi.
Leveraging the baby's strengths and winning ...
You two are really parent and child after all!
That's not true, Akina!
No use for excuses, boss.
That combination is the real deal.
But if I broke off that bond?!
The white's only been cut once.
Perfect!
Riichi!
Oi, mate! I was tenpai too!
Crikey! Could have swapped my pair with the 1p ...
Ron!
Riichi chiitoi honitsu! Haneman!
I won! With these guys as opponents, it's the real deal!
Ponta is a mahjong genius!
All right! I'll turn you into the world's strongest mahjong master!
Daisuke!
Who are you?
I'm Daisuke's mother!
Give Daisuke back to me!
Ponta's mom?
Don't call him that.
He's called Daisuke! Give him back to me!
He's genius baby Ponta, no Daisuke!
I'm sorry! I'll never abandon him anymore, just give him back!
Righto, mate!
Never! I'll raise Ponta myself!
Toyotomi ...
Doesn't matter if you call him Chiita or Ponta, give him back!
No!
Understood. Toyotomi Hideyuki v. Ponta's mother.
You shall bet the baby and consider the winner the true parent!
Splendid! Another case closed!
TN: Tooyama no Kin-san's catchphrase
Riichi ippatsu be careful of fires!
TN: A pun on Honda Shigetsugu's letter to his wife
So?
I'll do it!
Like hell I'll lose!
Chun!
It came out! Closed honitsu shousangen!
I see, Daisuke ...
Ronning your mommy ...
Won't you give your mommy a second chance?
Ponta is a mahjong genius! And he'll win it for me!
I see ...
3s dora pon!
Whoa, lady! You can't show your hand before winning!
Daisuke! Deal in with the 3p!
Come back home to your mommy!
Ponta will never deal in on purpose.
What are you doing, Ponta?
Nooooo!
Ron! Tanyao dora 3!
Daisuke! You came back to me after all!
Mommy will never let you go anymore!
Ponta ...
Boss! Now ya got me instead of Ponta.
Another case closed by me.
Riichi ippatsu and drive safe.
Ponta ...
Thus, the baby returned safe and sound to his mother.
What was coming and going in Toyotomi's heart as he was left all alone in the metropolis:
Indeed, jealousy and longing.
Toyotomi felt that he might vent these bittersweet feelings by composing a letter to his hometown, to his own mother.
East 3, South seat, turn 5, 23200 points.
Dora 4s, draw 7s.
muh tanyao
>6p
ngmi
Point stick blade!
Riichi!
Crash!
Report!
THE JONGPUTER IN A SMALL POND
Oh no! I lost ...
Riichi ippatsu honitsu hatsu sanankou dora 3, baby!
You're really strong ...
That's right! I'm strong, definitely strong!
It would be a shame not to show my strength!
Isn't that right, mai waifu ....
I love strong guys!
I'll give you a reward!
Got it, baby!
Now there's only one thing to do ...
Become a pro mahjong player and make everyone go "wow"!
Like a rising supernova!
Wait.
MUNICIPAL LIBRARY
That faggot!
You'd never think he'd be hiding out in such a place.
He's trying to outsmart us, huh? It won't be a walk in the park!
Toyotomi ...
Hey! Wait!
Calm down and come with us!
Help!
What's this whistling?!
Over there!
Who are you?
State your name!
I am the one who has defeated all jongputers far and wide: the hidden genius mahjong star!
Have you got the guts to gamble with me, bros?
Let's go.
Yeah, time to go.
Whoa, whoa, wait a bit, baby!
What?
I said I wanted to play with you guys too!
Nobody asked.
Just go to a parlor or whatever if you really want to.
Wait a second, Shintarou ...
Mark my words, this guy's an easy mark.
You've hit the mark ...
Indeed.
That means ...
One of us will have to skip ...
Yeah ...
Yep.
Well, you should have just let me join from the start, baby ...
What's this! Faggot!
Riichi!
Already a haneman, success guaranteed!
What could it be ...
Fold.
6s!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu honitsu ton hatsu!
Why the hell did ya cut 6s against these discards?!
Don't go easy on the jongputer kid!
Fuck off! I was in closed honitsu tenpai too!
If you let this guy steal your flow, that's no good.
Riichi!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu honitsu iipeikou!
Why the hell did you cut 3s?!
You're the one getting your flow stolen!
Retard!
I was in tenpai! Fuck off!
All right! My camouflage is perfect!
Riichi!
TOYOTOMI'S WAIT
Don't you know how to fold?
If I deal in, it's worth the same anyway!
At last I truly see ...
This guy is what is called a "jongputer specialist".
Mahjong video games have been getting better lately, but 2 player is still the norm.
That's why dealing in and getting tsumo'd is usually worth the same.
Naturally, this means you have to push like a retard.
Here (1s dora) you would normally cut 9m and go for either sanshoku or ittsuu ...
Obviously cut 9p and go for insta-riichi nomi!
Adeptchads~
How about it!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu nomi!
It keeps coming out ...
This kind of riichi nomi players are scary when they get lucky!
Riichi!
I'm a lucklet so better just match the 1p!
Ron! Ippatsu!
You retard! Look!
Shintarou cut it right before me!
Huh?
No huhs, you were in furiten!
I was only looking at my toimen ...
An easy trap to fall for for (you).
All right! Let's get those sticks back!
Chii!
You can't chii from your toimen, retard!
1000 point penalty!
Playing mahjong against humans is harder! Look!
Chii!
Don't let him call tiles you know he needs!
Yasu never looks at the discards.
What are ya complaining about? I'm in tenpai, you know!
It's my turn now!
Riichi!
All right! I made it to tenpai, baby!
Go!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu honitsu iipeikou!
Check it, baby!
Heh, it's not the same against humans.
Nope. Keiko and Shio from Family Mahjong were even stronger.
Huh. In that case ...
Riichi!
Am I stronger?
No way, baby!
Well, in that case ...
Riichi!
Riichi ippatsu tanyao chiitoi!
Still not the real deal, baby!
Riichi.
Well, then I'll riichi too.
Just riichi ippatsu!
Shouldn't you cut a safe tile with such a shit hand?!
A win is a win.
t. sakurai
But I shan't change anything from my youth!
It would just be a soulless insta-riichi nomi computer mahjong!
I know well what you want to say. However ...
It's faster this way after all.
Riichi.
Fools!
I'll show you how it's done!
A human playstyle, by humans for humans!
Ron!
Hi!
Akina! Come swap with me! It's the perfect players for you!
Oh no! You've only got 1300 points left ...
Watch it, jongputer kid!
I'll show you the ultimate human jongputer!
Chii!
Pon!
Naked tanki! Superb!
Ron!
Haku nomi.
This isn't the strip mahjong at the arcade!
Are you guys glad right now?!
With the skill I've honed at the jongputers, I'll certainly get this girl to strip!
Pon!
What are the odds ...
But I've got confirmed kokushi too. I'll take the 50/50.
Pass!
Ron! Daisuushii tsuuiisou!
Check it, baby, two!
Zugan.
The dreadful jongputer kid was vanquished by the even stronger human jongputer Akina.
However, the fight is not over.
There is no certain proof that no second or third jongputer will appear.
Until the day people reclaim the SOVL of mahjong ...
Hang in there, Akina!
Fight, super lucklet Toyotomi!