Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
Ron!
Tsuuiisou! That's a yakuman!
Zugan!
You retard! Why did you discard a tile like that?!
Ah, it seems the ending was an upset home run for Yasu.
Such benevolence!
All right, thanks! Let's go!
Not like this ...
TSUMO-JONG TO MAKE YOU CRY
PART 1
Zugan ...
What's that?!
Hey, Toyotomi! It's me! Akechi!
Open the door, I'm telling you! C'mon!
Look, everyone! Toyotomi put the wrong trash out!
Not these guys ...
Hey! We just came over to chill.
Good day.
Oh, good evening, I suppose.
Well ...
Who is this ...
My girlfriend, Rie.
Nice to meet you.
Are you the Toyotomi who's famous for being a super skilled mahjong player?
That's right, Toyotomi's super skilled at mahjong.
I like guys who are strong at mahjong.
Really?
That's why I love Kou-chan!
What did you come here for?
Tch, where is he?
Who, Yasu-kun?
That son of a ...
Probably gone to a karaoke alone again.
How lonely ...
He really looks like someone who isn't popular with girls ...
>not popular with girls
No, you can't just show up like that!
Who will show up's been settled already.
Don't worry.
Who this?
That's my girlfriend Megumi!
But you can call her Megu-megu!
Hi!
>manlets
What's so funny?!
>gf
Whatever way you look at it, she looks way out of your league.
Yeah, I'm a bit too good for her.
Oh, Ya-kun ...
What did you come here for ...
Hey!
You all look like you're having fun!
Oh, Shintarou!
What are you doing here?
Well, it's a bit messy here, but please come in!
Hey, it's my place!
What's Akina doing with Shintarou ...
Hey, Akina, what's going on, that you came like this with Shintarou ...
Yeah!
Who will show up's been settled already.
Don't worry.
That's Yasu's line.
Why are you together?!
No good!
Guys shouldn't be jealous of each other!
Don't ruin the mood!
Don't worry!
That's why they say "The world is one family, and everyone is a friend" (t. Sasagawa Ryouichi)
What the hell is that?
Well, let's promptly do what must be done!
Ya-kun, do your best!
Leave it to me!
Don't lose, Kou-chan!
It would be extremely painful.
Do your best!
Okay!
Goes without saying. Just sit back and watch!
Akina sat down next to Oda!
What the fuck?
Why ...
Why don't you come sit next to me, Akina?
Does she think she can just pass me by like that?!
Idiot!
Riichi!
Hey, it's your turn!
Toyotomi!
Oh no!
I have to focus on the game!
All right ... Sanshoku iishanten.
I'll take the gamble!
Drop the genbutsu 7s dora!
Damn it ...
All right! Great draw!
He cut dora early.
There's no way! All right!
Oikake riichi!
Ron! Riichi pinfu junchan sanshoku dora 1! Baiman!
Amazing! That's why I love you so much, Kou-chan!
Heh, that was no big deal.
Kiss!
Zugan ...
It's no good to deal in like that, Toyotomi ...
Akina!
She was on my side all along!
This would've been a haneman on 2p tsumo!
Yeah!
Zugan!
I had a good hand too ...
No way! You discarded dora!
It's okay, no need to show off!
She won't even believe me ...
You should win a hand too, Ya-kun!
Whatcha talking about?
I'll get first for Megu-megu and give you a present!
Wow, really? I'm so happy!
Habeeb it and just wait!
I'm waiting!
Trust ...
Two people in love are bound by a strong bond of trust ...
And the two of us are ...
Hey, mister! Did you come from Tokyo?
Well ...
Tokyo is my hometown ...
A hometown is / what one thinks of / when one is far away
(t. Murou Saisei)
But they say "The lovers' bond is close yet far away"
(t. Sei Shonagon)
When Megu-megu's watching, I keep getting good hands!
No way!
White!
Haku!
Two 5m and one 8m out ...
And if I call, it's just a mangan.
That's unbased.
I did it!
French cuisine tonight!
Really?
Time for ippatsu.
Riichi!
Tenpai! I can see the hidden 234 sanshoku!
But the 9m is dangerous ...
Should I mawashi?
Nay!
'Tis the sons of Nippon who brave such perils!
Forsooth, let us go forth!
(TN: In classical Japanese, parodying the gunka "Shussei Heishi wo Okuru Uta")
Riichi!
Ron!
Riichi ippatsu double ton honitsu ittsuu! Baiman!
Amazing! I look up to you!
Zugan.
Shit!
Akechi and Yasu both got a baiman ...
You'll have to win a baiman too, Shintarou-san.
Shintarou-san?
But she called him Shintarou-kun before ...
She switched to -san!
Sorry, Toyotomi!
For me, it's guys who are strong at mahjong!
Lmao get outskilled, faggot.
Shintarou!
Noooo!
I can't lie to my own feelings anymore! Farewell!
Akina!
This guy's been weird since we came here.
Did you eat a fly agaric? The one with the dots.
Hey! This isn't the time to be worrying about a guy like him.
Riichi!
Shan't deal in.
Akechi can take 1st, Yasu can win, I don't care!
But however.
Today ...
Just today ...
I SHAN'T
deal into that faggot Shintarou! Even if it kills me!
Finally, Toyotomi has declared his revenge for the seething Oda caused him!
But has Akina really switched over to Oda?
East 2, South seat, turn 5, 25000 points
Tsumo 9s dora 2s
Foresee the invisible junchan sanshoku
t. sakurai
Riichi!
Amazing, Shintarou-san! It's only the 6th turn!
What? That's normal.
Akina's happy about Oda's riichi ...
Damn it ...
I absolutely SHAN'T deal into that faggot Shintarou!
TSUMO-JONG TO MAKE YOU CRY
PART 2
Superb! Tanyao tenpai!
The 7s is suji.
But Shintarou is the kind of guy who cuts 4 from 468 with no worries.
Fodl.
Tough.
What's up with such tough mahjong ...
It's tough!
But that toughness can sometimes ...
backfire!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo hatsu sanankou! Haneman!
Amazing, Shintarou-san!
What's so funny?
I told you I shan't deal into Shintarou!
I drew his winning tile on the ippatsu turn!
I read that the 7s was his winning tile and folded!
What are you boasting about, Toyotomi?
If you had cut that tile, it would have been just a riichi ippatsu!
Folding and not dealing in, so out of character! C'mere!
It's your fault we had to pay for haneman tsumo! Retard!
- Idiot! Brainlet!
- Toyotomi ...
Don't bully the poor guy!
Well if you say so, Rie ...
Don't bully him, Ya-kun ... You're still winning anyway!
Yeah, you're right.
Now, it's time for me take 1st!
Do your best, Shintarou-san!
Yeah, why was I overthinking it?
I need to make that faggot Shintarou lose!
Folding was wrong! Dealing in was right!
I can't let him intimidate me!
I can't win unless I win!
The dora is 8p.
Wut?
What happen?
Oh uh, nothing in particular ...
It's just that my haipai was particularly bad ...
Oh, that's a good answer.
Yeah, I was worried about getting such a bad haipai, haha ...
Something's off with this guy.
Bad draws and bad flow ...
I did it! Turn 4 tenpai!
Tanyao sanshoku dora dora! Easy!
Now it's time for ...
Telepathic attack!
Cut 258s!
258s!
Riichi.
I said riichi!
Bad premonition!
Que será, será!
No!
I've been in damaten for ages!
Riichi!
Take it, you thief!
It passed ...
It's a miracle, a kiseki ...
Maybe luck has turned to my side ...
Are you watching, Akina?
I'll show you that I'm not something you can just throw away!
258s deal-in!
In the end, ippatsu from Shintarou! I did it!
Tears in my eyes ...
Are you crying in sympathy?
No.
It's always good to see other players deal into each other.
It's the soul of mahjong ...
Thank you for waiting, everyone!
I shall now reveal my hand!
Riichi tanyao pinfu ippatsu sanshoku dora dora ban ban!
[autism sounds]
I give up!
You're unlucky!
The cheaper out! Tsumo!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo ura ura. Mangan!
Wait, he tsumo'd?
How charming!
So many lucklet flowers!
Toyotomi died.
And after he died, a thousand beautiful flowers bloomed.
Wait! The hanchan isn't over yet!
If you want to die, do it after the game!
Zugan!
Ron!
Ittsuu dora 1! 5200!
Ron! Honitsu chiitoi!
Ron! Riichi tanyao ippatsu ura 8! Sanbaiman!
Ron! Chinitsu pinfu iipeikou! Baiman!
Ron!
Honroutou toitoi sanshoku sanankou haku dora 3! Sanbaiman!
Toyotomi just keeps dealing in!
He's pretty unlucky.
He hasn't won a single hand.
Toyotomi, you're actually really good!
Your condition is just a little bad today!
Shut up! Stop it!
It's not like I keep dealing in and losing on purpose!
But ...
But I just keep dealing into people!
Poor guy!
I should help him somehow ...
I'll cheer for you, Toyotomi!
With me watching, you'll definitely win!
Wut?
Hey, Rie!
Oh, what a nice hand!
You can do it!
Kyah! You're getting good draws!
You're strong! Now call riichi!
But with this hand you should reject tenpai and cut 7p ...
Don't worry! Cut 4p and call riichi!
Well then, riichi.
Disgraceful.
For a man to cry about losing in mahjong and get pitied by girls ...
and not even express his own opinion, doing exactly what he is told: I think it's disgraceful!
That's just because Toyotomi is pure!
Yeah, when he wants to cry, he can cry!
Shintarou-san, switch with me.
Please!
Strong!
Riichi!
Please be tsumo!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu chinitsu ittsuu dora 1! Sanbaiman!
Zugan!
I don't know him.
Me neither.
Bros ...
Look, Shintarou-san!
Well done, Hayami.
Megu-megu, forgive me for only winning by this much plox.
No way, I'm just happy you did your best!
You're sweet!
Well, we've played enough. It's about time to go home.
It was fun! First time I've seen something like that.
How about we go to Disneyland tomorrow?
Yay!
Bye, Toyotomi!
Zuganpo.
At last rejected by Akina: Toyotomi!
It seems that Akina will never come back to him.
After all, no matter what Akina's true feelings were
the lucklet flowers bloomed only in silence.