Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Tommy? Are you there?
Akina ...
Gomen nasai, Tommy.
Naze?
I've treated you badly on purpose, Tommy.
I thought it would inspire you to defeat those three ...
Tommy, yurushite kudasai!
Iya, daijoubu.
Do you hate me now, Tommy?
Booba!
I don't ...
Tommy!
Nakadashi no yorokobi ...
GAMBLING TRIP ZUGAN
PART 1
Am I dreaming?
If you think about it, there's no way Akina would dress up as a bunny girl ...
If it's a dream, I should be quick before I wake up!
Let's go!
No, Toyotomi, let me go!
She's stark naked now!
AAAAAAAAA
Wake me up inside!
No! Take some responsibility before waking up!
That was a nightmare.
Oh no, my head's exploding ...
Even after being betrayed so completely, I still can't forget Akina ...
Shall I go on a journey?
So I've come to this forgotten place at the end of the world ...
Art thou mayhaps a traveller?
I've come looking for my forgotten self.
Gaze upon the sea.
At suchlike times, it is best for men to gaze upon the sea.
Hello :D
They're all shivering at the thought of me winning all their money.
Glose door :D
Fug ids gold :DD
Jusd sdand dhere and freeze :D
Ah, sorry!
Fug whad a smal guy :D Wearing de ebin drench gaod :DD
Luogs lieg a redard :DDD
Gibs monie's wen I ron's yuo :DDD
Blays widh us :DD
Fug no :D Blay's ad dhis dabel we all sugg :DDD
No dis is de ebin dable :D
I guess I was born with a natural charisma ...
I'm popular no matter where I go ...
Well then.
Can I join this table?
Fug :D
Deys is de sdrongesd adepdchads :D
Saunalainen algohoolig mahjuonggers glub :D
"Whisky and water" Utsuki!
"Hoppy" Toubara!
And "High Sour" Gento!
These three appeared to be a bunch of alcoholics at the first glance ...
But they were actually all ex-pros who have played in the capital!
They had abandoned their ambition ...
But their technique was still something an amateur could not measure up to!
What's up with those messy discards!?
Tenpai!
Pinfu and up to sanshoku dora 1 with 9p!
It'll come out in no time with this gang ...
But first I'll dama a bit!
It came!
Fug :D Nod dis on :D
Ebin :D
Fug :D
Yuo gan dage bacg de dile if yuor drung :DDD Here habe anodher :D
Ebin :D Dank yuo :D
Dzumo :D
Fugging dsumo nomi :D
Fug ebin :D
Fugging surbrise :DDDD
Gant disgard 9b :DDD
Same :D
Ebin :D Yuo god fugging oudblayed :DDD
Here in Binland eberyuone blay lige dis :DD
Dring gläs :D
They're strong!
Hey, Toyotomi!
He ain't here!
A farewell letter in a place like this?!
That bastard, leaving behind a fucking letter ...
He wants to run away from us!
Tch, what a pathetic guy!
Toyotomi ...
So? What does it say?
Hey! Hayami!
Where are you going?!
Toyotomi!
Dear Akina ...
Soon, I'll travel to the north to gamble ...
No matter where I go, I shan't forget you ...
t. Toyotomi
Hayami!
Shintarou-kun ...
So you won't even call me Shintarou-san anymore ...
I ...
You're going to leave me, aren't you.
So-sorry ... After all, I ...
Don't say it!
At last I truly see!
You only got close to me to invigorate that faggot Toyotomi!
You ... you bartered me away!
You ...
You barbered me away!?
I'm sorry, but ...
I'll go now.
Attention. The 14:40 express Yukitsubaki 32 to Kitaguni will depart from platform 14.
Ron :D Tagame :DD
Zugan!
Toyotomi ...
Until I get there ...
Ron :D Dun nan dora dora. Mangan :D
Hang in there, Toyotomi!
Until I get there ...
Please, please don't get shadowrealmed!
Godspeed, Akina!
Toyotomi's shadowrealming is near!
South 1, North seat, turn 10, 22100 points
Tsumo 4p dora 3s
sanshogu :DDDD
Toyotomi, hang in there!
Hold out until I get there!
GAMBLING TRIP ZUGAN PART 2
Disgard de fugging dile :D
Fug wy yuo dond's disgards nuow :D
Tanpin sanshoku ...
But he's already tenpai ...
That being said, dora is 4p.
I shan't cut the dora soba 36p against dealer riichi ippatsu ...
It can't be helped.
"Enduring the unendurable and suffering what is insufferable!"
(TN: from the Imperial Rescript on Surrender)
Even if I have to go for tanyao nomi, I have to cut 5p!
Ron!
Riidi ibbadzu menhon iddsuu :DD
Zugan!
Fugging ojabbane :D
Fugg :D yuo deald in again :DDD
I wanna go home!
Bedder lug negst dime :D
Fug dond sboil him :D
Wait a moment! I'll be right back!
It was really Baba!
If you think about it, Baba didn't know about anything ...
What was it ...?
It took a while for Toyotomi to think that it might just have been a big-lipped ghost.
Well, let's go back to Tokyo.
Yuo gand go bacg :D
Fug yuo drying do run awy :D
Dond leave in de middle :D
Ebin :D Sdill dwo ruonds lefd :DDD
Fug :D
Zugan!
This is the town!
I can hear his voice from this town!
This way!
He must be close.
That's a lucklet flower!.
Here too!
There too!
Here it is.
Toyotomi ...
Akina!
How did you know I was here?
It was ...
It was love.
AKINA!
Toyotomi!
Sir, please play quietly ...
This is a gentlemen's club.
Mommy, those uncles've been bullying me!
Don't worry, sweetie, it'll be fine.
C'mon, blow your nose!
For the rest of the game ...
Is it okay if I play instead?
Pergele :D Learn somme maner's viddu ruodsalainen :D
Ebin :D
Fug :D
Yuo is 20k in shaduorelam's :DDD
What? Did you really?!
Bdw ids all lasd :DD Benis in bagina :D
What are you doing!?
Fug sdob :D
Abologise Jonne :DD
Fug whose negst afder dis fadass :DD
Ebin :D
At any rate, I have to renchan.
Fug :D Yuo gand renchan if we wins :DDD
Yuo wins jaguman nuow? :DDD Ebin :D
1p kan!
Fug suugandsu :DDDDD
6s kan!
Fugging gaaaaaan :DDDD Wdf yuo doings :DD
Gan dis :DDD
Kan.
Fug :D
Wow!
This sucks! Another kan!
Which one should I cut?
This one!
Fug whad do i gud :DDD
She gebd fugging 2s too de end :D
Fug 1s is dangeruos :D
She wend fugging doidoi :D So gand be middle dile :DDD
Whad ar de odds :D
Wow!
It worked!
Ron!
Look! It's a suji trap with 2s and 8s!
No worries jusd gondinue :DD
Dis bud a sgradch :DDDD
Jusd end her delear ruond :D
Bon :DD
Utsuki went for tanyao.
Toubara went for haku nomi.
Dabörii :DDDD
Gento called turn 1 riichi.
Nuow whad :DD
Leds go :D
Deamworg :D
Tanoshii!
They all didn't deal in.
Fug she was in denbai!? :D
Fug :DDDDDD
4m ...
I shan't discard it!
4m kan!
Even with pinfu tanyao sanshoku dora dora ...
What a waste ...
Yay! I tsumoed!
Tanyao tsumo rinshan, with 3p kandora, dora 3!
What is this, it ended up as a dealer haneman anyway!
Ganning my winning dile and dzumoing de lasd 5m :DD Ebin :DD
I did it! 8-honba!
Now anything you win is a yakuman!
Riichi!
Sorry!
Riichi ippatsu menchin!
Uhh ... ura 3.
This sucks!
It was a yakuman anyway and I get menchin ura 3!
Rigged!
Thus, Toubara died.
I have to conserve my flow!
A 1 han hand is fine too!
Blease dond ron :DD
This sucks!
Ron!
Tanyao sanshoku iipeikou!
Holy rigged!
Thus, Gento died.
Fugg bass bls :DD
Now this is a real waste!
Junchan dora 3!
AAA RIGGED!
Thus, Utsuki died.
A cig after gambling is always so awfully bitter ...
Fug :DD
They're behaving like a bunch of kids!
Heh. Hopeless guys.
I'm sorry, Toyotomi.
I'm over it. Don't worry.
We meet again, old man.
Didst thou find what thou wert looking for, traveler?
Yeah!
It's as if deep inside of me, something's changed!
Let's go back!
To Tokyo!
Riding off unoriginally into the sunset
the train carrying the two made its way back to Tokyo.
A poem:
O haku nomi, are you not sad? Wandering without calling kamicha's hatsu or shimocha's chun.
Thank you for listening.
TN: The poem is a parody of Wakayama Bokusui's tanka
"O white bird! Are you not sad, wandering through the sky's blue and the sea's green, unstained?"