Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
Tch!
Yasu!
Got a smoke?
Here ya go!
Don't forget to give it back!
Sure ...
Another fine day with a fine-tasting ciggie!
Wut ya say, Shintarou?
Yer really talkin' big today, huh?
To be honest, I'm feeling unusually cheerful too.
Wut? Me too!
Really?
Uhh ...
I cut that tile, you know ...
Ron! Chinitsu!
Ron! Double nan sanankou!
Ron! Pinfu sanshoku dora dora!
Zugan!
LUCKLETS ARE FOREVER PART 1
I'm hungry ...
I've only drunk water for three days ...
Hello, with Toyotomi.
Hideyuki?
Mom!
Are you all right?
I'm doing fine! Yeah!
I sent you a parcel of vegetables and mandarins, you know.
Wow, really?
Just take care of your health and do your best!
Thanks, mom!
There it is.
Now!
It's a Suginami indian ambush!
Thus, the relief supplies failed to reach Toyotomi.
Hey!
Akina ...
Toyotomi?
Thanks, Akina!
It's the least I can do.
You know, Toyotomi ...
What is it, Akina?
I ...
I'm going to study in the USA.
The professor said I should definitely go.
And my parents agreed with it.
N-no way!
After I graduate ...
I'll probably stay there for some time.
I see ...
What should I say?
Congratulations ...
I guess ...
I'm really grateful for everything until now, Toyotomi.
Please come with me.
It was really fun coming to Tokyo and being able to meet you.
Come to America with me, Toyotomi!
There aren't mahjong parlors over there.
But there's no chance.
But I'll never forget how to play mahjong!
One day, we'll surely play mahjong together again!
Right?
My plane leaves at 5 PM the day after tomorrow.
United Airlines to San Francisco.
The day after tomorrow?
I'm sorry I couldn't bring it up with you sooner.
Uhh ...
Can you do me a favor?
Can you see me off at the airport?
This is ... the last selfish thing I can say to you ...
Akina ...
While I'm in America, you'll change, and I'll change too.
It's not like it would be possible to say ...
"Wait for me!"
I've made my decision!
What in the bloody hell are ya doin'?
Boss! Gettin' all dressed up in a jet, what's goin' on?
I'm going to America!
What?!
I'm goin' with ya! To America!
Idiot! I'm not going there for fun, but to stay there!
Anyway ...
There's not even enough money for you to travel.
Boss!
Don't hang shit on me like that!
Toyotomi ...
Sorry.
We've heard the rumors.
You're going to America?!
America is ...
A whole lot farther than Chiba.
How sad.
I see.
I thought about telling you guys ...
Fine.
I leave Japan tomorrow evening.
So I'm through with you guys!
You're not going alone, are you.
I see ... with Hayami?
Our sitting duck's going across the sea ...
All the way to America?
Yasu ... That's a hell of a pun.
Heh, gotta stand out when I got to!
We'll meet tomorrow at noon.
A final hanchan at your place.
Bring it on.
I see ...
A final match ...
You should already have ...
Enough skill to fight anyone on even terms ...
Yes.
Then you must have faith in yourself.
If you believe in yourself, you can win.
Toyotomi, do you like the spring?
You have a fortright heart.
You see, in mahjong ...
A fortright heart wins in the end.
Do you understand, Toyotomi?
All your luckletism until this moment ...
Was but a prelude swelling to this epilogue!
Devote yourself!
Kou-chan, I made you coffee!
Kou-chan?
Hey, Kou-chan, I'm talking to you!
America ...
Is that on the Soubu line? Or the Jouban line?
Mongai!
I really want to win this match!
Rather, you should consider ...
If you can satisfy Akina as a man when you're in America.
If you're strong man, you can make her happy. You can't let yourself be weak.
You don't lose at mahjong because you're a lucklet.
It's because you're a weak man.
Those three are indeed a big obstacle for you.
But if you don't overcome that obstacle, you'll never become a real man.
To lose is to die.
Can you fight with your life on the line like that? That is the question.
Should I go meet Baba-pro too?
Hey, I called dealer riichi.
Get on with it and discard something.
The hell am I gonna do? I can't cut any tile!
Guess not.
Hello, with Hayami!
Toyotomi ...
Tomorrow, I'll play mahjong with them for the last time.
And, if I can beat them ...
If you win ...
I'll go to America with you.
But, if I lose ...
You should think of me that I don't deserve to go with you.
I understand, Toyotomi.
That match, win it, please!
Do your best!
Please, please win!
Hey!
I've been waiting for you!
Welcome!
Let's start!
We'll decide seats by picking winds, as always.
East?
I'm fine with sitting here.
I'm South, so over here.
Oho, this is the seat I won a kokushi from Toyotomi in last time!
And I've won a daisangen off him from this seat!
And I've won a suuankou here, if I remember right!
I've dealt into every seat!
But now that's all in the past!
Go ahead, I'm ready!
Yeah!
Dass right!
Boss!
The three gentlemen!
I, Kenjin, alias Ken the Pouncin' Cunt, say thus ...
Carn, mate! And give 'em bloody hell!
Well then.
Let's begin.
And, the dice were cast!
East 4, West seat, 9th turn, 3rd place with 21400 points
Tsumo 8p dora 6p
Who cares what the fucking discard is! Mahjong is a game, not a science, and to win, you just got to believe in yourself! Hard work and guts! Turn off your computer! Go outside! Touch grass! Get a mahjong gf! Live your life!
I have no dora (8m) ...
So I'll go for the hidden 234 sanshoku ...
Riichi.
Oho! He even called a riichi!
Is Akechi in tenpai too?
Look! It's this pattern again!
3m and 4m are genbutsu against Shintarou.
If I play it weak and cut 3m, I deal into Akechi's mangan!
If I play it strong and cut 4s or 6s, I'll deal into Shintarou's 3900!
Therefore ...
This one!
Chii!
Yasu called because he's the dealer ...
A 7s wait from a 468s shape?
It came out!
Ron! Haku dora 3, 8000!
Noooo, my dealer turn!
Dammit, where was my fucking wait!
I got it! I saw it all!
I know your mahjong like the back of my own hand!
LUCKLETS ARE FOREVER PART 2
EAST 2
Got it!
The dora is 8m ...
Why wontcha call riichi, boss?
Yer bloody tenpai for 14s, arentcha?!
Oi!
The 14s won't come out ...
Someone's got to be holding an ankou of it ...
Riichi!
Riichi, I called riichi.
What am I doing?
This isn't a hand to stay dama with!
Riichi!
Pass ...
Let's fight!
I can't tsumo!
C'mon now!
Deal in, Toyotomi!
Deal in like always!
That's your destiny!
Riichi ippatsu tsumo pinfu dora 1!
Could this 1s ...
Be the last tile left in the wall?!
It is!
Fuck! How do you even tsumo that?!
Toyotomi ...
United Airlines flight 401 to San Francisco will begin boarding.
Ya bewd! Ya clobbered Shintarou in a riichi duel!
That's right!
He always used to out-tsumo me!
Chii!
Pon!
I don't need this one ...
Oi, just try 'n' ron it!
Ron! Ton sanshoku dora dora! Best out!
Wut the fuck?!
Ya beat Yasu at calling!
He was just a nyagger after all.
I was always more skilled than him.
Here, I guess the best move is 8m ...
Go for 567 sanshoku ...
All right!
Easy win!
Ron!
That a tile like that could even come out!
Nan chun honitsu chanta, haneman!
This wasn't supposed to happen!
This plot is all wrong!
Toyotomi!
Cast away your delusions!
Free yourself!
Free yourself and rise against the challenge!
Do you see at last, Toyotomi?
Ron!
18000!
Toyotomi ...
A man's strength reveals itself in his point stick ...
Ron! Riichi tanyao pinfu dora dora!
Ron!
I've only got 3000 points left ...
I've got 2000 ...
I only have 1200 ...
All right, all last!
I'm the final dealer!
Crikey!
Akina's plane was bound to leave at 5!
Boss is on fire!
Boss is burning bright red!
It's over! Nothing I say will convince him!
Here it is!
Honroutou toitoi nan sanshoku doukou!
Dealer's haneman tenpai!
I remember it all ...
All those days you utterly fucked me over ...
Now is the time ...
I shadowrealm all three of you in one fell stroke!
With ... With this 6000 all!
Wait ... Akina is ...!
Toyotomi ...
Dear customer, please go ahead.
Sorry ...
Ron! Suuankou tanki!
Ron! Daisangen!
Ron! Chinitsu pinfu tanyao ryanpeikou dora dora!
I did it! I got first place!
Just second place?!
Dammit! A hand like this and I only got third!
Zu ... zu ...
Gaaaaaan.
Flight 401 has taken off from New Tokyo Airport at the scheduled time.
Koucha ka koohii?
Koucha onegai shimasu.
Oh mai gah! Anpanman ka!
Iya, rakkuretto da!
Sugoi rakkuretto da!
Toyotomi! You came after all!
We can play together again!
Tsukanpo.
Toyotomi, I love you!
Toyotomi!
That fucker. He still owes us debt and he just bailed.
Yeah ... And now he's in America.
And we're in Chiba.
Another young 'un went off on a journey ...
Hey, gramps! We just sighted a big one! Hurry!
What?
Boss!
Boss! What the bloody hell am I gonna do with my life now?!
Thus, the young lovers embarked on a journey ...
Leaving behind three friends, a disciple, and countless emotions and memories.
"We'll meet again, Toyotomi! One day, for sure!"
GAME OVER
Lovingly translated for (You) by /mjg/ anon
And to all lucklets ...
Congratulations!