Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
Uooohhh!
Pools in midwinter are really the best!
It's a feast for the eyes!
Hey! Look there!
Uooohhh! Zekkoh!
Hehe!
Booba!
Sorry to have kept you waiting​!
POOLSIDE ZUGOOMERS
Feels good man!
Akina's akinas!
Uoohhhh!
Hey guys!
Awooga!
Wheee!
Yahow!
What is this?!
Sea cucumbers?!
Two huge red sea cucumbers stuck together!?
Retard, this isn't the ocean!
Don't get close to it! Run away!
Tfu!
Who's a red sea cucumber?!
How rude! Can't even get left alone and swim!
I'm gonna go back to my room and sleep!
That guy, what was the deal with his way of swimming?
It must have been Undersea Humanoid Ragon!
(TN: big-lipped fishman from the Ultraman series)
Hey! It's Toyotomi!
Wutcha doin' there?!
You all went without me ...
It's your fault you were lazin' about!
I'm so happy you came here too, Toyotomi!
Anyway, I'd like to have something cold to drink!
Yeah, Toyotomi! Don't just stand around and buy us something!
I'll go get something!
It's fine! You just sit down with us, Akina!
Here!
Four colas, please!
One, two, three, four ...
Wutcha doin'?! Get on with it!
There's only enough for four ...
Yeah, that's what I told ya, ya dolt!
What about mine ...?
Stop fuckin' with me! Pay for your own!
My own ...?
But ... I don't have any money?!
Whoa, he started to cry just from a cola. Kek, what a bitch!
Well then ya shouldn't have come here with us anyway!
I'll treat you!
Akina, if you spoil him he'll get used to it!
Here, buy yourself something nice!
Akina!
What a pathetic guy ...
"DELICIOUS YAKITORI"
Five colas, old man!
Douzo, lad.
Arigatoh!
You're ...
My teacher Ozawa Takeshobo!
Ozawa Takeshobo!
Famed as the user of the unbeatable rage harvesting technique ...
he is an invulnerable mahjonger who has returned from death many times!
Master ... you were alive after all!
What should you mean by that?
Haha, it's been a long time, you old prankster!
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
I am certainly no "Ozawa" you speak of!
Well, then who are you?! Tell me!
You got your cola, so get the bloody hell out!
I politely ask you to not come in the vicinity of this stand again.
Pon!
C'mon!
Roll~
What is it?
I'm bored.
Now now, I can't let you pull mischief!
Be a good boy and sit over there!
Let me play next?
Wut? I'm busy right now! No time to talk to you!
Wow! Such a good hand!
Your "help" is uncalled for.
Whoa! Cutting that one?!
I'd cut this one instead!
And then cutting this would guarantee a yaku ...
Look!
If you did like I told you, you'd be in 14m tenpai!
Riichi!
Whaaat?! Riichi?! That's totally the wrong move!
Is it?
Ippatsu tsumo! Riichi instant tsumo tanyao sanshoku!
Got it! Ura ura!
It's baiman!
No way ...
You were saying?
N-never mind ...
Fuck off!
Riichi!
Oh shit! I have no safe tiles!
All right, point read!
Akina's wait is definitely 36m!
A 36m wait, you say?
36m!
All right!
Cut 3m!
Huh?!
Aww ... pass.
Ah, good grief!
I had no safe tiles at all, but luckily Toyotomi's reads are guaranteed to be wrong!
It's as good as genbutsu!
Hey! Stop ruining the game, ToyotomI!
I ... didn't want to ...
Stop ruining it! It's your bedtime already!
Kuyashii ...
What's this ...
This is ...!
I found this!
A voucher for a free night's lodging and dinner at this hotel?!
We should give it back to them ...
Yeah ...
Well, Toyotomi, it's mahjong time!
I'll sit out, you guys have fun!
But we should ...
C'mon, let's go! Start already!
Heh, idiot. I'll beat him and the dinner voucher's mine!
That faggot Toyotomi brought something nice!
After you all go back to your rooms, it'll be just me and Akina!
This soon.
Whoa, this is another great haipai!
Pon!
Yeah! I can hear the sound of victory!
I drew it! Ryuuiisou tenpai!
WRYYY
With this wait, 7s is just 5200!
I'll call 3s and wait on 3s tanki, it'll come out easily with the 4s pon!
Chii!
Let's gooo!
He called? Ron eet.
Tanyao sanshoku iipeikou dora dora! 18000!
Zugan!
Wut? He got shadowrealmed before I got a chance to ron him?
Heh. The dinner voucher will be mine.
It's a matter of time.
Toyotomi ...
It's not here ...
Perhaps ...
The luxury lodging and dinner voucher Toyotomi found!
Was this mysterious character who seemed to be its owner ...
The supposedly late Ozawa Takeshobo?
Furthermore, what conclusion is waiting for Toyotomi and Akina?
The turbulent second act will begin in about 80 seconds.
Expect the point of view of all concerned!
East 1, North seat, 9th turn, 25000 points
Dora 4p, tsumo 8p
Sanshoku is ... le GOOD!
So, where's my comeback hand?
Comeback?!
How are ya gonna come back from –60k?
"Comeback" is not a word to be used lightly.
Well, everyone should still be allowed to have hopes and dreams!
Yeah, he deserves a human rights tsumo!
Yep, whether you're a frog, bug, or poor as a church rat, you deserve to live!
That's right! We're all frens!
Stop fucking with me!
RETURN OF THE OLD MAN
All right! Check 'em!
Let's go!
Cut 2s for 1p3s shanpon! Cut 3s for 14s ryanmen!
This one and ...
Riichi!
If I ippatsu tsumo and get ura 3, it's baiman!
And then, with just one hand ...
I'll be at –44k!
What did he mean by this ...
C'mon, tsumo!
What.
Zugan!
If I cut 3s I would have ippatsu tsumo'd!
Out-squid!
Nice, I got to tenpai ...
I finish first if I win!
It came out ...
Thank you very much ...
What, you?!
Riichi!
No other words after "riichi"?
What, riichi nomi?!
Retard! I have to look at the ura first!
Got it! Ura 1!
Ura! Ura! Told you so!
Wow, so impressive!
So that's 2600 ...
Wrong!
3200! 3200! I get extra points!
Look at the hand, adeptchad! If I get screwed out of my points every hand, that's no business!
It's 50 fu! 50!
Fuck off!
With 2600 or 3200, your end score is still -107!
Smoko doko ...
Ron! Mangan.
What the hell, Toyotomi?!
Th-there was something weird outside the window ...
There isn't anything here or there.
But there definitely was!
You were daydreaming, weren't ya.
So weird ...
Dammit, such an annoying false alarm kind of guy ...
Cut it out!
Chii!
Who the hell are you?!
That's our line!
Who the fuck are you?!
Wait ... I've seen him before somewhere ...
Got it! It's Ozawa Takeshobo!
Correct! Much obliged.
Master!
Master! I'm so happy to see you again ...
My disciple ...?
That ugly old man from the stand was you after all!
I see you youngsters were playing mah-jongg?
Yes! Would you like to play too, Master? Please show your true power to them!
Hmm, well ...
C'mon, gramps!
Well, if you insist ...
Ah, it's a good feeling to touch the tiles again ...
What's that? Humu humu? I see, I see ...
You're telling me to cut this one?
All right!
He's talking to himself ...
I wonder what he's doing.
Wrong!
Someone like me can hear the voice of the tiles.
The voice of the tiles?!
Indeed. The tiles are alive and have a heart!
A true adept can rise above common sense and flow like water, discaring what the tiles tell him!
So true!
Hmm, I'll try to listen to the tiles too.
Do you berievu in za Gahdo?
While you're trying to be funny, I'm calling riichi.
Hmm, these youngsters are always calling riichi too early ...
Hmm. Which one ... I see.
Your wait is 36p!
Did I hit the bullseye?
How did you know my wait?!
H-holy shit!
The discards have a voice of their own ... and they told me 36p is your wait!
Ippatsu! Riichi ippatsu tanyao iipeikou!
Young man ... you will die a good death ...
Ron! Pinfu ittsuu, 5200! [sic]
Ron! Honitsu ton, mangan!
Ron! Riichi chanta sanshoku dora dora!
Horrible!
Don't you have any pity for an old man like me!
I've never seen young people like this!
Sorry ...
Don't worry about it!
Heh, like this Master is guaranteed to come in last!
It's time for my ...
Riichi to confirm 3rd place!
You underestimated me, Toyotomi ...
I was secretly waiting for you to make this mistake all along!
Apoplexy riichi!
Wh-what's that?
Oh, you want to know? You want to know ... its meaning?!
All right? Apoplexy suddenly attacks you one day and then ...
you're certain to fall over dead.
This one's high calorie!
Apoplexy!
And I told you to pay attention to your calorie intake ...
Oh, I'm tenpai again ...
Riichi.
Wait! That wait is ... look, old man!
Oh, I see ... it's fine!
Ippatsu tsumo Alzheimer tanki!
Furiten tanki?!
How do you tsumo that?!
Dumb boomer ... I'll show him the power of our generation!
Subarachnoid hemorrhage riichi.
Social security chase!
Super express retirement home return!
Riichi ippatsu honitsu shousangen, baiman!
Victory for the young!
Bedridden old man.
Stop foolin' around!
Master!
It seems that death has come calling for me ...
I just wanted to eat a hotel dinner before ...
What?! We have a ...!
No! That's for me and Akina!
This is ...!
My luxury lodging and dinner voucher for five people!
You were going to steal it, weren't you!
Ah, the food's tasty and the show's great too!
It's good! Yeah, good!
Arigatoh for treating us, old man!
Well, as long as people don't do bad deeds, we're all friends.
Here, eat some more!
Toyotomi ...
And now, tonight's special guest, the abominable snowman ...
Mister Lucklet!
"I'm innocent!"
The outcry of Toyotomi's heart was drowned out by the flames of the burning limbo and the cheers of the crowd.
Toyotomi, let me offer these lines to you:
Fireworks might be / compared to a storm
but the only thing I say goodbye to / is life.