Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Akina!
Hey, Akina!
So, Akina ...
Oh. It's you, Toyotomi.
She looks like she's in a bad mood.
It's not like I bumped into you on purpose, Akina!
So—
Toyotomi.
I heard you had to repeat a year?
WELCOME TO THE MAHJUNGLE
Wow, I had to repeat?
We're adults now.
We're a different race from students like you who can slack off all the time.
But we used to be ...
Hey, Toyotomi! Congrats on your extra year!
You're hopeless ... Just going to the mahjong parlor day in, day out ...
No wonder you couldn't get enough credits!
Those suits ...
We've washed our hands of mahjong a long time ago.
From now on, we're first-year working adults!
Ya were a little slow to notice, huh.
No way!
I've gotten completely fed up with you. Farewell, Toyotomi!
Bye!
Akina!
From now we're in the same year! Let's be good friends!
Kouhai! From now we're even! Even!
Oi boss, somethin' wrong with me face?
Uhh, what did I do last night?
Ya don't remember anythin', mate?
Ya got pissed as a parrot in Shibuya to drown ya worries!
Drown my worries? Me? Why?
'Cause ya have to repeat a year!
I actually can't graduate on time?!
Right-io! Ya failed to advance from junior to senior year.
Don't even mention graduating ...
That's why you couldn't—
Before that!
Boss!
Say it again!
Stop takin' the piss! I'm goin' to yakka!
Welcome!
Hey, coffee please!
Here you go, sir!
Hand me a hot towel!
Yes, sir!
I heard Toyotomi had to repeat a year ...
I thought he'd be depressed, but he looks so lively!
Yeah, though he was spitting the dummy this morning.
I wonder if he'll be right.
Hey, fill in for me, please!
Fill in!
East 4, exactly at starting points, I see.
All right, I'm the dealer.
I've got to play toward a quick win, but what to discard ...
First I'll get rid of 2s and 8s!
Oi, kid, get on with it!
Y-yes sir ...
Start with this and see what I draw!
Oh, you drew the backfire straight away.
If I draw 3s it's fine.
The flow is toward souzu. I'll cut the pinzu penchan!
Don't worry! It's still only the early game.
That's right, nothing to despair about!
I can still make 234 sanshoku!
I'll cut the dora early!
>inb4 I draw another dora
Zugan.
If I cut it, I draw it ... It's really the law of cut-and-draw!
Oh, I'll pon that.
I just drew the pair.
N-no way ...
Why is he such a lucklet?
Doushite?
Take the 58s furiten!
On turn 5 I've got furiten on both 58s and 14p!
And I've missed a 234s sequence!
And I've let that guy call his dora pair! This is bad!
I've got to do something before that customer gets back!
What's this?!
Can you please stay in for a little more, sir?
Now that you mention, I've still got some left ...
Isn't that right? So take your time while you're in there!
Who is it?
It's your turn to discard.
All right!
10 tiles ...
And 2 more tiles ...
Totals 12.
I've got too few tiles ...
I've got to struggle through this round somehow without getting found out ...
What's wrong, jobber-kun? You look pale.
I-it's fine.
I've got a bit of a toothache since yesterday ...
The hell? Did I have the top draws?
Mister, these things can happen with an autotable ...
Sometimes the top and bottom draws shift ...
Anyway, this round I just have to be thorough and fold!
Sujibros!
Just let the round end with nothing happening ...
Ron! It's a really bad wait though!
Toitoi ton dora 3! Haneman!
Zugan!
That was refreshing!
Wait!
What!? What's going on?!
I'm sorry sir, please stay out of the way!
Dora.
Pon!
All right ...
If I win this, I'm even! It's only turn 5, as good as won!
He's thinking.
He should just tsumogiri that 3m straight away.
Well, maybe ...
Boss is an adeptchad so he'll kan it.
No way.
Don't even think about it!
Just watch!
In this case a pro would ...
Cut this one!
He's sharp!
If he cuts 3m, it's a 4-sided wait on 1247m ...
But with 9m, it's a 5-sided wait on 12458m!
Boss, I kneel!
So, do you rate me now?
I've always rated ya, boss!
C'mon!
The discerning viewers should already know which tile he has drawn.
Extreme zugan!
Ron! Riichi tanyao pinfu sanshoku, 8000!
Zu ...
Thanks for filling in for me, I'm back!
Zugan!
You must be feeling unwell, here's a hot towel!
Thanks ...
Extra big cup of coffee and tea!
And a free Yokult drink!
And I'll light your cigarette!
After that, a massage!
Pick one for mother ...
(from the Buddhist hymn Jizō Wasan)
Pick two for father ...
And a flower bouquet!
I'm sorry, I don't deserve all this ...
Not at all, these are my true feelings ...
So please enjoy your day!
Amazing! Double riichi!
The infernal mahjong tyrant, Toyotomi!
Whoever asks him to fill in is already dead.
Hey, can you fill in for me?
Yes, I'll be right there!
Toyotomi should a repeat a year in mahjong too ...
South 3, East seat, 9th turn, 29200 points
Dora 5s, tsumo 5m
Dealer → speed > sandshocker
Wut? I'm on my last ball!
No! Not there!
Wut?!
Another 5000 yen down the drain! Fuck!
Let's get engaged!
Rie?!
Akechi!
Fuck ...
Who the hell are you?
What the hell's going on?
What's going on ...? Well, you could say my love's cooled off ...
Get lost!
I wasn't done explaining ...
All right! C'mon! Faster, you fuck!
5 and 6! 5 and 6!
GOOD STUDENTS SHOULD NOT ENGAGE IN LEGAL GAMBLING
Damn it, I lost!
All of part-time money for this month gone to shit!
Ey, I'm walkin' 'ere, you fuck!
What? Fuck off!
Akechi?
Shintarou!
Wut's goin' on, fuckers?!
Yasu?!
The hell you two bumpin' into me here?!
I'm out of luck. A wave of brokeness's spilled over my life.
Yeah! Pachinko's no fucking way to make money!
And my girls both dumped me ...
Then let's go do our role!
MAHJONG RULES 101
Did I do a good job filling in?
Need to me to sub?
What's goin' on, boss?
Never seen ya be such a happy little Vegemite!
Something nice must've happened to him.
No, not in particular ...
C'mon, tell us!
I got it, boss! A date with Akina!
How did you know?
And afterwards just the two of you in Akina's room ...
No way ...
When the EDM breaks off...
The two of you gaze at each other ...
Toyotomi ...
Akina!
No! You fool! Stop it ...
Toyotomi, there's some customers calling from that table!
They say they went to play with you!
O-okay.
Hey, Toyotomi.
How've ya been?
Long time no see!
Uhh, my shift is almost over so I'll go home and let you guys have fun with someone else ...
Damn it! Your friends came over just to see you!
What's with this attitude?!
Have some respect for our past friendship!
No ...
C'mon, I'll be the first dealer!
Hey, first dealer!
No, me!
Got it! I'm starting dealer!
Wut?! I ain't lost yet, ya know!
Could you guys tone it down a little bit?
Okay.
What?
It's rude towards the other customers.
Wut's that, Toyotomi?! Since when do you boss it over people like that?! Huh?!
Calm down ...
Let's play quietly.
He can flex all he wants, it's time to play!
I'll vent all my piled up seething ...
All right! Ippatsu!
Riichi tile suji trap!
The only one who'd deal in is Toyotomi, so predictable!
Sir, that's a chombo. You don't have a yaku.
Retard! Look, I called riichi!
Riichi is only applied when you say "riichi", put out a 1000 point stick and turn the tile 90 degrees.
Not declaring vocally and not putting a riichi stick makes this not a valid riichi.
The fuck ya bitchin' about? It's because ya said we shouldn't make a noise in the first place!
No, he's got a point.
I also agree with Toyotomi.
Gib chombo!
You fuckers!
I get it! Ya're both out of luck so you're gonna fuck me over, huh?
Here!
Riichi, motherfuckers!
Here! Now you've got no right to bitch!
Chase riichi.
What's this guy's deal?
He didn't put a riichi stick like he said you should!
Heh, what a retard.
Oh no ...
I can't cut this ...
The fuck ya doin'? Ya're in riichi!
Please, sir ...
I just told you!
If I don't put a stick, it doesn't count as riichi.
The fuck?!
And I haven't put one, have I? Therefore, I'm not in riichi.
In other words, I can discard any tile.
Motherfucker ...
Oh, nice draw!
Chase riichi!
This time it's the real deal!
Damn it! There's no fucking way!
It's over!
Ron!
Goddammit! This is such bullshit!
Sir, please don't put your knee above the table.
Fuck off!
Discard your tiles softly.
Stop fuckin' bitchin'!
Uhh, what do ...
Call!
Sir ... once you've touched the wall, you can't call.
Wutcha talkin' about? I didn't touch it!
Forensics!
It's clearly Yasu's fingerprint, Dr Watson!
How's that? Do you still deny your mahjong crime?
B-but I must've touched it last round!
You've incriminated yourself, Yasubee!
On an autotable, there are two sets of tiles with different colored backs!
Therefore, there's no way you could've touched this set when it's only East 2!
Oh no ...!
I see ... You really don't want me to pon that chun ...
It's the rules.
I get it! I'll just tsumo it instead!
Tsumogiri!
Pon!
Hey! I just remembered it's East 3!
My fingerprint could've been there from East 1!
Slow ... way too slow.
Dammit!
It came out! 2600!
Chii!
Don't need it!
Ron! Chanta honitsu nan! Mangan!
He's good! With this form, he might even get first for the first time in this parlor!
What's that?
N-no way ...
This round's gonna go to draw ...
All right, riichi!
What? No way he called riichi!
There's only 4 tiles left in the regular wall! That means he's only got 1 draw left!
No! This isn't an ordinary riichi!
It's a 16-sided wait riichi!
Wut? 16-sided wait?
You alright, mama-san?
Take a good look at my discards ...
What did he mean ...
What the hell you makin' a fuss ab—
One discard away from nagashi mangan!
And a 258m sanmenchan to boot!
Together with the 13 kinds of terminal and honors, he's a got an unbeatable 16-sided wait!
Someone call, 1p!
No good, I can't call it! Call the nan!
I already drew! Call the 9p plox!
All right!
Whaaaat!?
Tsumo! Nagashi mangan!
Mama-san, does this parlor even play with nagashi mangan?
Oh, no, not at all! I forgot!
Here! As you can see, at Ichibankan, we do not consider nagashi mangan to be a yaku!
Sorry ... We just changed that rule last week.
No way!
Having to play with an employee who doesn't know the parlor's rules ...
It's rude to the customers, isn't it?
I think we should get a chombo payment for this.
Well, we're all generous here so we'll give ya a pass.
Zugan.
Ron! 7700!
One is for your luck which is always far away.
Ron! 12000!
Two's for being born on an unlucky day.
Ron! 18000!
Three is for your dreams although you don't really try.
Four is for the time it took to get to tenpai.
Five is for the riichi you chase while in denial.
Six is for your draw, the rigged ippatsu tile.
Ron! Ron!
Ron! Mama-san, do you play with triple ron?
Of course!
Zugan!
It's the cold season. Take care not to catch a cold!
Now then, on a winter evening of dancing blizzards ...
What did Toyotomi dream while sleeping alone?
Next time: "South Pole Zugan" and "Nouveau Riche Zugan"
Don't miss it! Don't want to you to sleep on it!