Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
I'm back!
Work was really tough today!
You're still sleeping!?
Hooly dooley, I slept in till the arvo!
Why din't ya knock me up, mate?
Who cares, retard.
Bugger!
Stop fucking sleeping so much!
Oi, I'm feelin' the buzz, mate!
NOTHING BEATS THE BUZZ
Are there even guys who sleep 16 hours a day!?
Well, let's go for some gamblin' then.
No way, I'm broke!
I only have 200 yen left!
Good onya chad! I only got 107 yen.
If ya win I'll give ya 2 yen!
Fuck off!
Well then, shall we bet our entire net worth on a single roll of the dice?
Agreed.
Bloody hell! A one!
I've as good as won!
Let's go! Cee-lo!
All right, it's a triple of ones!
Zugan!
Here you go.
DON'T TRY THIS AT HOME~!
Right-o, that's one down!
Whoa, are we really going to a mahjong parlor completely broke?
Too right, mate!
With this mood we'll deffo win!
And it's not true that I ain't got a brass razoo: I've got 307 yen!
That's what it means to be broke!
I ...
I've felt the buzz, mate!
I just want to feel the buzz!
Ouch!
Static electricity ...
Idiot.
Cheerio!
Welcome! Oh my!
If it isn't Toyotomi and Mr. disciple!
Hi!
Shall we play, mama?
A spot just opened at the tengo (1000 pts = 50 yen) table!
Mama-san! Ya've come a bloody gutser there.
Do you really wanna let me play at tengo?
Huh?
I shan't ...
I shan't feel the buzz like that!
Pin! A true blue bloke's gotta play pin (1000 pts = 100 yen)!
I see ...
Mama! One open spot at the pin table!
C'mon, let's start!
Boss!
None of 'em look like mad cunts.
Really ...?
Ponya!
Double east dora 1!
Fair enough!
Riichi!
Crikey! Wait a bit with that shaa!
Yeah nah.
I shan't cut that 7p.
Go on, mate.
Hey, you!
That's a foul pon!
Don't rubbish me mate, it's nothing.
Fuck! Dora 9p!
Crikey! If I'd ponned the shaa I'd've won off the dora tanki!
Now this is the real buzz, mate!
Oi, what's this?
Ron! Riichi haitei haku, 5200!
Why did you have to ron me, you cunt?
It's a live tile.
You could've cut the fuckin' shaa ...
Shan't! I ain't came here to win, mate.
I came to feel the buzz!
NEXT ROUND
Take a dekko mate! A hand with guaranteed tanpin sanshoku!
Ya bloody bewt!
Time for a cheeky dama ...
No, wait! If I riichi that and tsumo it'll be a haneman!
If I tsumo ippatsu and get an ura it'll be a baiman!
This is ...
This is making me feel the buzz just by imagining it!
Get on with it and discard!
WRYYYYYYCHI! I'll win this time!
Crikey! Such tight folding!
Mate! Ya've never felt the buzz at pussers bones before?!
Huh?
Nice, I tsumo'd! 300-500!
Bloody hell, mate!
Heh, nothing personnel, kid. This is enough buzz for me.
As if that's the dinkum buzz!
HANCHAN END
Well, in any event I'm first.
NOOOO, NOT LIKE THIS!
I need to ... feel the buzz more!
Feel the BZZZZZZZZ!
Mama-san! I need to borrow money.
(TN: Some parlors allow this.)
Borrow money already?!
Surely you weren't playing broke??
Yeah nah ...
Ya don't get it at all, mama-san ...
Playing without a brass razoo is the surest way to feel the buzz!
What the fuck are you on about?!
Fair suck of the sauce bottle, mama-san ...
"No"
And if I lose, I'll let me boss work here for free for a month, howzat sound?
Then it's fine :^)
W-wait, not like this!
If you lose, I'll let Toyotomi work here really hard with no breaks!
No ...
Truly me and me boss are two tickers beating as one!
Hey! We're making a ryanpin (1000 pts = 200 yen) table!
Won't somebody come play?
When did they ...
She'll be right, I'm right there!
Stop!
Do you even know who your opponents are?
No worries, mate.
I don't feel like losin' today.
You said that last ti-
Hey! Gonna play or not?
Okey-dokey!
Will he be okay?
Now ryanpin, that's a real bewt ...
Riichi!
This one!
Pass.
Crikey! Just one push and I'm already gonna BZZZZZZ!
Heh. Coming without a brass razoo and playing ryanpin rate ...
It's fighting with your back to the water like Han Xin at Jingxing!
Throwing your life and limb on the line!
Letting your flesh be cut to break the enemy's bone! That's right.
That's just my way of life.
Holy based! I'm feeling the buzz just from describing my way of life!
Get on with it and discard.
Retard ...
Let's go!
89m ...
Those fairly safe tiles are what an amateur would cut ...
But mahjong is and always has been ...
About battling straight on!
Powerful.
Hah! The rigged ippatsu tile never fails!
Yooooo!
Adeptchad pls!
3m can make sanshoku! You can draw 5p for dora!
25s for iipeikou! You have 3 kinds of improvements!
Heh. I'll show you MY kind of mahjong.
Ron! 18000! 8000! Tsumo! 2000!
Whoa! A huge lead!
Hahaha! She'll be right, mate!
Pon! Pon! Kan!
Aha! The dealer's going all in!
Whaat? Well you should be folding, you!
I'm gonna say it: I shan't lose at nyagging!
Chii! Pon! Chii!
Retard! What are ya gonna do as first place with such a short hand!
The fear and pressure of defending with such a small hand ...
is making me feel the buzz from the bottom of my ...
It's making my livelihood feel the buzz too!
The dora chun!
Stop!
A tile like that is 90% certain to deal in!
A normal bloke couldn't cut this tile ...
But I ...
I want to ...
Don't do it!
Cut the tile that makes me feel the buzz!
Pon.
BZZZZ
Howzat, boss?
I must've made even the audience feel the buzz.
Yeah ... made me feel it to my heart's content ...
C'mon, tsumo!
Hatsu!
Ah, finally a tile to make you fold ...
Let's go!
Stop! If you cut that it's not mahjong anymore!
Stop it, boss! It's a rare chance to feel such a buzz!
Boom!
Pass.
C'mon!
What is this.
Ron!
Shousangen honitsu dora 7, kazoe yakuman~!
All right! Electric massage service for everyone left!
Damn! Feels nice!
(TN: Don't look up "denki anma")
Yeah, it does!
Mama-san, arigatoh!
There'll be free service for the next month!
>doing it for free
Zugan!
Buzzing and buzzing pass half a year
and pass the other half sleeping.
(TN: Parody of the folk song "Dekanshobushi")
Ah!
A man's life! The spirit of exciting mahjong!
(TN: This line is like a typical Minami Haruo lyric)
But, the discerning viewer should not certainly not try it himself.
WWYD? South 3, West seat, 6th turn, 16600 points
Tsumo 8m, dora 8m
crowkeks btfo
DECEMBER 24TH
SANTA'S WAIT'S COME TO TOWN
I'm hungry ...
Boss!
I'm shot of this life without a brazz razoo.
I'm lookin' for someone with big bickies
so I wish ya a ripper Chrissie!
t. Kenjin
Fuck! What a faggot!
Wait! Today is Christmas Eve!
I haven't called Akina in a long time ...
Let's call her!
Hello, with Hayami!
I have a very important rendezvous today, so I'm not home.
If you have an important message, please leave a message after the beep.
An important rendezvous ...?
Merry Christmas!
So, what about some Merry Christmas mahjong?
C'mon, get up, chop chop!
C'mon, let's go!
Heave-ho!
Zugan.
What's wrong, Toyotomi? You look even more mindbroken than usual.
Did something happen?
We're worried, bro!
Aren't we being nice!
Look!
Suck on these and cheer up!
(TN: The famous "Sakuma-shiki" drops, in a retro tin with right-to-left writing)
Whoa! Drops! They're drops!
Open up!
What flavor is it this time?
Strawberry!
He looks happy.
Yeah.
We're really being good pals, huh.
Yep.
Which means, it's no problem to make him a little bit less happy.
Huh? Well, that's one way to put it!
I don't want to play mahjong all night long ...
Stop whining! It's your turn!
Don't need this one!
Toyotomi ...
Your hand is all drops!
Not all of it ...
Don't bullshit! 9p riichi!
Whoa, it's full of drops!
Shut up and discard!
This one!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu chinitsu!
Zugaaan!
Hey, everyone!
It's Mr. Santa!
Ho.
Huh?
It's Santa?
Oh, I've seen him in a magazine.
Apparently, this guy has never won a hand in his 30 years of playing mahjong.
Look, Toyotomi, it's Mr. Santa!
Really?
Yeah, really.
So why do you keep playing mahjong?
It's fun.
Huh?
I find mahjong extremely tanoshii.
That's why every Christmas Eve, he becomes Santa and brings presents to all the lucklets in Japan!
Seeing me, the unluckiest person in the world ...
will certainly give all those youngsters a boost to their self-confidence!
In other words: my present to you all, is myself!
Aight, gramps, let's do it!
What a funny Santa.
But the bar to clear is high!
Don't ask me ...
Santa! Is it true ya've never won a hand?
I swear to God it's true!
That's not really something to be so proud of ...
As expected of Santa!
A complete garbage hand!
My haipai are good tonight ...
They're usually 5-shanten, but this one's somehow 4-shanten!
He's here, he's here!
A powerful lucklet!
Not him ...
Not him either ...
It's him.
What a ... what a lucklet!
The spirit of luckletism is weighing heavily on his shoulders!
7p riichi!
Oh no! Such a garbage hand and yet no safe tiles!
Ron, baby! It's Christmas time!
Ouch!
Me too, me too!
Jinguru Berru!
Clang!
Drops!
Oh no, I brought Mr. Santa specially for Toyotomi ...
What is he doing?
Let's see ... Whoa, what a nice hand!
Oh no no no no no ...
What happened?
I'm ... in ... tenpai ...
The first time ...
in seven years!
Yes.
It was on Christmas Eve seven years ago.
I made it ...
I got to tenpai!
The first time in twelve years!
Tanoshii!
Mahjong is always so tanoshii!
Riichi!
Ron! Sorry, old man!
Mentanpin sanshoku dora dora, dealer's haneman, 18000! Ho ho ho ho ho ...
And now, again ...
Such a nostalgic feeling ...
Riichi.
The dora ...
My opponent has never won a hand, it's time to ...
Wait ... if I deal into Santa here ...
I'll be the guy who gave him his first ever win!
What's wrong, Toyotomi?
Superb nya!
Oh no no no no!
Ron! Chanta only.
REEEEE
Please look at the others' discards ...
B-but you were waiting on the dora 6m, right?
No ...
I was on 7p penchan!
Whoa! Amazing!
Two consecutive riichis for me!
Win.
The urge to win is flaming up within me!
Riichi.
Damn it!
This time I shan't fold!
Let's go! Riichi!
Riichi nomi.
Why are you doing all these special effects with just riichi nomi!
Ron.
Roooon! Hah! Ron! Riichi nomi!
Zugaaaaaan!
Mr. Santa! How does it feel to have won your first ever hand!
Well, uhh, I guess like "So this is what winning is like, huh", ho ho ho ho!
Zugan.
Ah, yes, I almost forgot.
I'll give you a present for dealing into me.
Here.
Whoa! They're drops!
Not like this.
There's something deeply wrong with him.
"Drops! Drops!" Toyotomi's voice echoes across the snowy town.
Whilst snow falls on Taro's roof ...
(TN: From Miyoshi Tatsuji's poem "Snow")
tonight too you sleep alone.
At any rate, Merry Christmas.