Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Ugh, it's sooo hot today~
Mama-san, a bottle of Ramune pwease!
One Ramune!
Mmm, this is really the best when it's hot!
It's still central heating season ... what a weird guy!
UNDEFEATED! THE LEGENDARY MAHJONG DEMON
Pei pon!
Hey, bro.
Yeah?
You're disturbing the field. You shouldn't cut honors, especially guest winds, on the first turn.
What do you think this is, mate, bush week? Ya were goin' for kokushi, weren't ya!
Hmm, which one to cut ...
Hey, girl.
Yeah?
You should discard in 3 seconds of drawing.
Longer than that, it's not thinking, but indecision.
B-but, I really don't know?!
He's so rude! Who is this guy?
Riichi!
Pass! Nice riichi!
I'm iishanten for ittsuu! Either tile's fine, just draw it!
I drew it!
Now I can cut the safe shaa and riichi waiting on Kenjin's genbutsu, 7p!
W-what's that?! It looked like his tiles were swaying!
Shaa?
Ron! Sanankou chun, 9600!
Zugan!
All right, pinfu tenpai!
And now I've drawn into confirmed sanshoku tenpai!
I'll rely on Kenjin and Akina's cover fire and ...
Let's go! Riichi!
Ton? 18000.
Zugan!
That was the legendary heat haze technique!
Heat haze technique?
The heat haze was perfected in the 1930s by Fujieda Baiman and is a type of sleight of hand.
(TN: parody of Fujieda Baian, doctor/assassin from Ikenami Shoutarou's novels)
Transforming a large quantity of CO2 accumulated in the body into heat ...
emitting it and causing the surroundings to appear distorted like a heat haze ...
and switching tiles unseen from the other players.
Truly, a legendary secret technique!
Source: Introduction to Mahjong History Research, book 2, chapter 11
Who are you, that you can use that technique with such ease?!
You're the legendary underworld pro, Sakurada Mongai!
(TN: refers to the Sakuradamongai incident, the assassination of Ii Naosuke in 1860)
Huh?! The one who has been feared for ages, known as the legendary Mahjong Demon?!
It seems you know a little.
Well, I'll be showing up at tomorrow's tournament as well.
You can already write "Mongai-sama" on the envelope with the prize money.
Now, do pray excuse me.
If that man shows up, all the adeptchad customers' fun will be ruined!
Mama-san, what tourney?
I'm actually holding one tomorrow!
The Ichibankan Cup Contest Mahjong Tourney!
The prize for the winner is, would you believe it, one million yen!
One million yen?!
Whoa, so many people!
Y-yeah ...
Everyone, please sit at the table indicated by your bib number!
There will be two qualifying rounds. Only the top 4 advances to the finals!
That Sakurada Mongai guy from yesterday is here too ...
I hope I won't get matched with him ...
Hooroo! Let's meet again in the finals!
Do your best!
Bye-bye!
Okay, Toyotomi, do your best!
O-okay.
Uhh, where's my table ...
Hey, Toyotomi, over here!
Master!
My kamicha is Master, toimen's some no-name student ...
I could win this—
Oh, excuse me, is this the right table?
Sakurada Mongai!
Oh my, we meet again!
Good luck and have fun!
Zugan.
This haipai is tenpai for 9-sided wait chuuren!
This is sus! Getting such a good haipai in East 1 ...
What's wrong? The dealer must discard for the game to start.
I get it, it's a trap! Damn it, Mongai's already set me up!
If I cut the 4s ...
Double riichi!
Renhou!
Now that's a real substitute for a proper greeting.
I hope you'll see it that way.
Or something like that is what he'll say when he rons me!
So, should I cut 5m and bet on a 4s tanki?
Double riichi!
So you cut it after all.
That's my wait!
He could definitely read I'd do that!
That means I should go back into iishanten and cut 1m or 9m ...
Aiming to draw into pinfu ittsuu tenpai around the 4s!
Weak. Ron! Suuankou.
Oh no! It's no good! My opponent is an underworld pro undefeated for 20 years!
It's completely possible he read right through me and has a 1m or 9m tanki!
What the hell should I discard?!
WWYD FOR ADVANCED PLAYERS
I see! In this case, this is the only play!
How's that, now I've taken you by surprise with my strategy!
Don't underestimate me, Mr. Sakurada!
I'm not someone who'll fall for your childish traps!
I've seen Hell countless times!
Let's go! Riichi!
A perfect finish! Kekekekeke ...
If it passes, I'm gonna chase!
Heh, chasing the dealer with the dora indicator. You're in for a world of hurt, kiddo.
Oh no, Toyotomibros?!
Ippatsu! With ura dora, it's 6400!
Zugan!
You should have just cut the 4s.
You underestimate him, Master.
Drawing this haipai from the wall Sakurada built ...
What do you think—
Hey, kiddo! Are you >implying I stacked the wall?
N-no, not in particular ...
Don't fucking spew bullshit and take a look at this!
His hand is complete garbage?!
What's the surprise?
Even I couldn't stack the wall on this table!
Oh fuck! This table was an autotable all along!
EAST 3 TURN 5
Tanyao only, waiting on 4m kanchan.
Mentanpin sanshoku iipeikou, haneman tenpai.
Ron! 1300!
Hey, kiddo! What the fuck's that hand?
What do you mean?
And you call yourself a mahjong player?
Look, this is your next draw.
Even with tsumo it's just 500/1000.
So I think there's no need to skip ron.
That's not the point! Your next draw is this!
The ton?
Well, the next draw!
The next one ... No! The next one!
Look!
You'd be tenpai for sanshoku!
But this is already the dead wall ...
What the hell does that matter?!
In mahjong, when you can win a yakuman, win a yakuman!
When you can win a mangan, you have to win precisely a mangan!
If you don't make this hand into sanshoku and win on turn 5 ...
Lady Luck won't smile on you!
On the contrary, I will be lucky for dealing in!
I can't get caught up in this occult nonsense!
I'll just keep winning small hands and ...
Riichi!
Kiddo. How old are you?
I'm 21 ...
Then correction might still be possible.
If you cut 4s here, you should quit mahjong and go back to your hometown.
What?!
Let's see ...
So you cut it from this hand ...
What the hell are you doing?! That's a chombo!
Don't worry! The 4s is my winning tile. My bad!
Zugan!
Suuankou?!
Toyotomi, that's the dora!
Ron! Chanta sanshoku dora dora!
Zugan!
The underworld pro who has been undefeated for 20 years ...
Sakurada Mongai is truly to be feared!
East 2, West seat, 6th turn, 25000 points
Tsumo 4p, dora 5s
Obvious
WHOSE WILL BE THE GLORY...?
Ya bewd! Tsumo!
Chinitsu! 3000/6000!
A tad bodgy, but fair enough!
Easy first with 60k after the first game!
One more and the final's a piss in the woods!
She'll be right, now let's take a dekko at Akina's game!
Crikey! What's all this crowd!
What's the haps here, mate?
Well, it's still only East 4 on this table.
That girl's been chaining renchans the whole time!
As if!
Tsumo! Kokushi musou!
Uhh ... 48000 with 12 honba ...
Makes 51600 total ...
So that's 17200 all!
Good on ya, Akina!
Like this, ya'll make the finals even with ya peepers shut!
Oh, what about Toyotomi?
Minus 200k?
He's got the wooden spoon!
Zugan!
Toyotomi!
What happened?
Sakurada Mongai!
Sakurada Mongai?!
Oh no ... so he came after all.
If ya can't beat him, winnin's gonna be bloody hard yakka!
It's no use! Just give up and go home already!
Wha'd ya say?!
With this flow, I'll get a big first next game too.
No one will be able to stop me.
For 20 years, there was no one who could stop me.
Then we're gonna break that record!
I know you're trying to look cool, kid, but be careful you don't get hurt.
We'll now start the second round!
Toyotomi! Now isn't the time to wallow in your loss!
Don't give up hope yet!
Zugan!
The fight isn't over yet!
You can just make up your losses in the second round!
But still, someone like me who struggled to get a part time job at the mahjong parlor is totally no match for him!
There's no way I can beat an underworld pro with 20 years of experience!
You can't give up!
You've got it your all and try until the very end!
It's okay! Just leave me and you go on to the finals!
Toyotomi, you idiot!
Even if your opponent is an underworld pro or the Mahjong Demon, he's still just a human!
Still just a human ...?
Mr. Sakurada is just a little bit older than you!
To offset that difference in experience, you've got ...
Uhh .. you've got uhh ...
Anyway, you've got to do your best and you'll manage somehow, okay!?
You couldn't even think of one thing I'm good at, could you!?
Stop complaining and just do it!
Good luck and have fun.
What's that, you again?
Zugan! Playing with Mongai twice in a row?!
Even if your opponent is an underworld pro or the Mahjong Demon, he's still just a human!
That's right!
An underworld pro or whatever is just a human after all! He can't have chance or luck on his side!
Ron! Sanshoku dora 1!
Tsumo! 2000/4000!
Ron! Honitsu sanankou dora 3!
Tsumo! Riichi tsumo tanyao pinfu dora dora!
Super zugan!
Oh no! Toyotomi!
He wasn't human after all ...
Toyotomi, hang in there!
Kenjin!
Master!
There was this mad cunt of a pro at my table!
Heaven has forsaken me!
All three of them ...
Long time no see, Akina.
You're the Tokyo U graduate mahjong pro, Mr. Ide!
I shan't let you forget about me either.
Magazine pro Mr. Kaneko?!
(TN: Kaneko Masateru, 4x Saikoui)
What's up with these cunts?
How the hell are we supposed to win this tourney if pros are gonna snipe us?!
There's no hope for this world ... *poa*
(TN: Poa is the Aum Shinrikyo term for death)
The lifestyle of a mahjong pro's tough too!
I'll say!
Sakurada Mongai?
The final four contestants have been decided!
These four!
Who will set off with the one million yen prize?
Finally, a table to show off my Tokyo U graduate skill!
TOKYO U GRADUATE IDE-PRO
Yeah, the qualifier was full of adeptchads.
MAGAZINE PRO KANEKO
Heh. The likes of you can't hold a candle to fifth-rate underworld pros.
UNDERWORLD EMPEROR SAKURADA MONGAI
There's no way you'll be a match for a first-rate one like me.
Go back and try your luck against some mahjong parlor jobbers.
What?!
I shan't let you slander us!
I'll fight!
For Toyotomi and the rest who fought bravely to the utmost!
Will Akina be all right?
No matter how astounding Akina's luck may be, she's surrounded by three pros!
Akina!
Akina fought well.
In all last, she was at 15000 points.
And then ...
At last, it's South 4!
In first is Sakurada Mongai, with a 4000 point lead!
Pon!
I've got a strong hand. I shan't let him upset me with his double nan!
Kan!
Excellent ...
Mongai's already tenpai on turn 3!
With the 8m takame, it's haku chun toitoi sanankou, haneman!
Like this, it's just tanyao.
It's only turn 4! I'll return to iishanten and go for a better shape!
Crikey, Kaneko! He didn't take tenpai and cut the 6p!
Oh, pretty Akina is hesitating!
Come on, cut 4m or 6m!
If I can call, I'll have shaa tanki for shousuushii, yakuman!
Oh no, now it's dangerous!
Chii!
Now Ide-pro is tenpai for shousuushii on turn 4, waiting on shaa!
If he called the 4m, he'd have dealt into me with 7m ...
What a lucky fucker ...
Well then, kan!
Oh, I drew the kandora ...
The flow is on my side. I'll clinch this win!
Wow! Haku chun honroutou toitoi sanankou dora dora!
He upgraded his haneman to a baiman!
Got it!
Riichi!
Crikey, this is rough!
Kaneko-pro, on turn 5 he's got at least a haneman, with the 5p takame it's mentanpin sanshoku dora 3!
Dealer's baiman riichi!
Oh no, what should I do?
Okay, this one!
Please pass!
On the same turn, Akina calls a cute oikake!
It was the 7m after all ...
C'mon!
And meanwhile, Ide-pro joins the fray!
I'll fucking show you!
Kan!
Kaneko-pro got two more dora!
Now it's dealer's baiman even on 2p ron!
This is the Mahjong Demon's mahjong.
He turned his haku chun honroutou toitoi sanankou dora dora baiman ...
Into a shousangen honroutou toitoi sanankou sankantsu sanbaiman!
Deal in, shousuushii!
Deal in, dealer's baiman!
Deal in, sanbaiman!
Akina!
Oh no, these guys are giving me such scary looks ...
Tsumo!
Uhh, riichi tsumo chiitoi dora 8!
She's got pairs ...
Of all ...
Our waits?!
A comeback into first place! Miss Hayami Akina is the winner!
Akina!
I did it, yay!
Thus, the legendary Mahjong Demon Sakurada Mongai left.
Who put an end to his gambling luck after he boasted of being undefeated for 20 years?
You see, I'm someone who'd never ron a lady.
Ah ... Man lives according to aesthetics ...
Toyotomi ...
What is it, Akina?
Farewell!
Akina ...
Next time, the last episode of Super Zugan:
"Lucklets Are Forever" part I and II!
Don't miss it! Don't want to you to sleep on it!