Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
It is said that a drowning man will clutch even at straws.
A human in trouble will entreat the gods, and certainly will always put his trust on something.
Depending on the person, it can be love, religion, or many other things.
But there is one thing ...
that must never be trusted.
The devil.
Let us watch the fate of one who sold his soul to the devil.
PLAYING DEVIL'S ADVOCATE
I finally got my hands on it ...
The Manga Guide to the Dark Arts!
With this book, I shall summon the devil ...
And wreak my vengeance on Shintarou and the others who've been bullying me for so long!
The time has come.
Now I shall seal by blood my contract with the devil!
Eroi moe saimoe eroi moe saimoe eko eko azarak eko eko azameraku donguri korokoro donburiko!
(TN: Eko Eko Azarak was a popular horror manga.)
Come forth, O Prince of Darkness!
Could it be ... the devil?!
Toyotomi!
Good evening!
Speak of the devil!
Whatcha bitchin' about? It's your turn!
Ron! Same wait!
Zugan!
Hey! Rie!
Make some tea would ya!
Okay!
Tch! I shouldn't have trusted the book's black magic ...
What, you're still reading that kind of stuff?
Heh, you're the kind of guy who'd fall for the "selling embarrassing photos of myself" thing!
That's you though.
Damn it! I've got bad luck today too!
If the devil's really here he could maybe at least help me a bit!
What's wrong! Toyotomi!
I-i-it's the devil!
What?
'D ya bump ya head or somethin?
Get a grip, Toyotomi!
Turn it off!
Are you okay?
It burns ...
Ya can't even light a fire properly?
No! I just turned the switch like always ...
Werks for me.
What?!
Well, it's Toyotomi's house anyway, so no problem if it burns down!
Tryin' to mooch off me or what?!
Well, it was no big deal, so let's continue.
Huh ... this was my hand?
All right ...
Riichi!
I have a 3-4-5 sanshoku!
Pass!
Ron!
Riichi ippatsu ryanpeikou dora 2!
Oh no no no!
Haha! Ya dealt into Toyotomi's haneman!
Whaat?! Why the hell did I cut 3p?
Based retard!
It's obviously a 5p discard!
G'day! How ya gahn everyone!
What did you buy there?
I flogged this at Keio Uni!
But what are you gonna use it for?
Boss! Ya din't know?
Nowadays we live in a society where if ya ain't got a computer, you don't mean a rat's ass!
Surely you're just gonna play H games on it?
What?
I play regular vidya too!
So really, it's just for gaming, right?
My hands are somehow all good today ...
Oi, boss! That's a bewt of a hand!
Already bored of your laptop?
Boss! Pon it!
Shut up!
Pon!
When the 8s comes out, pon it!
I know, retard!
Oh no no no! Laptoptoddlers btfo.
I only used it for 10 minutes!
Deal with it.
Be a man and deal with it.
Ron! Chinitsu tanyao toitoi!
Bloody hell! An' I just bought it!
Shut the fuck up!
I'm even worse off, so stop fuckin' crying!
Ho ho ho ... You're hustling all right.
Master!
Oh, what happened?
The laptop I just bought ...
All that has shape shall be destroyed, all who have life shall die.
Accept it.
Master!
I'll make some tea, so please pinch in for me.
Of course!
Oh ho! My word, this is saikoh!
Riichi!
What's that, old man? Riichi already?
Impressive.
Oh no! Are you okay?
He's dead.
What was his hand?
Chuuren poutou ... tenpai!
What was his draw?
The cheaper out.
What a lucklet!
It's a baiman though.
Wh-what are you doing?
If you die, you lose! Losers get their clothes stripped off!
And winners get to wear double!
What the fuck is wrong with you, retard?
Now the gap with Toyotomi's become even wider ...
It's strange ...
Haneman, baiman, sanbaiman ...
With every hand I won, Rie burnt her hand, Kenjin broke his laptop, and Master died!
It's like I'm sucking up everyone's luck to win!
AAAAA
What the hell is this haipai!?
This is scary!
It's only turn 2 ...
But I'm not gonna draw the dora 9m ...
Oh no! I tsumo'd!
But it's only turn 3!
This hand can be better than baiman!
Got it!
Chinroutou suuankou!
The devil! The devil was here all along!
Hello.
Hello, this is Hayami!
Akina!?
Toyotomi ...
I'm gonna be staying at the hospital ...
Hospital!?
They said something's off with my kidneys ...
so they'll be doing a complete examination, so I'm just a little worried.
Which hospital?
Get well soon!
Got it!
Wut? That luckshitter Hayami could get sick?
Should we go visit her right now?
Nah, we can go after the hanchan's over.
Got it!
But what if I win this hand and Akina'll ...
Akina!
Hey, get on with it!
Devil! So this time, you'd steal even Akina's life?!
Horrible!
My contract with you is over!
Ron! Ron!
Pinfu ittsuu dora 1!
Menhon chiitoi dora dora!
Zugan!
It turned out to be fine.
Sorry for making you guys worry.
I'm glad! Then you can eat some of this, right?
Look, I bought you this interesting book!
These are my feelings for you.
Sorry ... I lost all my money ...
Silly Toyotomi!
I'm happy enough just that you came to see me!
Akina!
There is a territory that humans should never set foot into.
Katayori no ryouiki.
It might even be existing there right next to you.
What about us?
Well excuse ME!
Zuganpo.
East 3, East seat, 13th turn, 19900 points
Dora chun, tsumo 6s
2p to confirm tanyao!
Or kan to increase value!
What's that? A present for your boyfriend?!
Yeah! I wanted to give it to him for New Year, but I'm just too slow.
Whaaat?! You should have told me!
You didn't have to go shopping with me!
It's fine! I'm happy to see you again after a long time.
Akina!
You look so pale! Are you okay?!
Yeah, I'm fine ...
Hey! Akina!
THE DREADED JAPANESE COLD
Akina!
Wow, you're here quick!
Toyotomi ...
Are you okay?
Well well, seems that the good boy next door's arrived!
I'll just put all the stuff here!
Hey, don't get any weird ideas!
How high's your fever?
Yeah, quite high ...
Feels good ...
Need medicine? Are you hungry?
It's fine! I can take care of that by myself, I just need to rest.
No way! You need to eat before you can take your medicine!
I'll make you something! Although I can't cook that well ...
So, what happened that you caught a cold, Akina? Spent all night playing again?
That's so unlike you, Toyotomi!
Toyotomi's special stamina-don!
(TL: rice with meat, vegetables, raw egg and soy sauce)
Wow, thank you!
Say "ah"!
Ah!
Ish it good?
Tell me if you want anything else!
Don't hold back, Akina ...
I ...
What is it?
I want to eat a melon!
Naze? Chikusho!
Is that no good?
Oh, wait!
I got a melon!
Mom just mailed it to me from the countryside!
Melon! Melon!
It's gone?!
The melon's gone!
You're late, Toyotomi!
We were bored so we had some of this!
Faggots! That melon was ...
That melon was ...
A Yuubari melon?
No! Well, it was actually a Yuubari melon, but this one's different!
So which is it?
I said ...
No good! This guy didn't come with brains included!
Let's settle it with gambling!
God of mahjong, just let me win this once!
If I win, I'll make them buy another melon and bring it to Akina!
Heh, it's a strange thing to see Toyotomi implore the gods.
However, your prayers won't work on us!
Ron!
What?!
3900! Fold the creases of your fingers together for good fortune! Akahanmyara parashiitaa!
(TN: this is a pun on shiwa wo awase and shiawase)
(TN: pseudo-Sanskrit)
Tsumo! 1300/2600!
Ron! 6400!
Tsumo! Tanyao pinfu sanshoku iipeikou assortment!
(TN: pun on tsume wo awase "nails together" and tsumeawase "assortment")
First place in all last!
Wut?! Toyotomi's first?!
I-impossible!
Heh. That's what happens when I play seriously!
Kan-ji-zai-bo-satsu ...
(TN: start of the Heart Sutra)
But he doesn't have that much points! I'll overtake him!
Riichi!
Oh no ...
If Shintarou tsumos 4000 all, he'll overtake me!
And if I can't give her the melon, then Akina will ...
Akina! Hang in there!
Toyotomi ...
I wanted to ... eat mel ...
Akina!
Shut up. It's your turn.
Look, I'm calling oikake riichi.
Stop spacing out and get on with it!
Hmm, I won't risk it. Let Yasu take care of it.
That's game-making!
Oh no, the ura suji!
C'mon, deal in!
Yasu is waiting for the outcome.
Oh no, the dora neighbor!
This time's the charm!
Yasu is waiting for the outcome.
The dora itself!
C'mon, bro!
Yasu is waiting for the outcome.
Tsumo!
4000 all!
Comeback into first place!
Fold the joints of your fingers together for bad fortune!
(TN: pun on fushi wo awase and fushiawase)
What the fuck is your problem?!
Fuck off! I had shanpon!
But 1s is already dead ...
Why didn't you cut 6p and go back to iishanten?!
In my mahjong, there's no going back.
I only go forward.
t. sakurai
I'm such a retard for ever trusting this guy!
I knew it! Everyone else is the enemy!
The only thing I can trust is my own skill!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu dora 1!
Tsumo! 2000/4000!
Riichi pinfu instant tsumo! 2600 all!
Let's go! Second hanchan and I'm first place in all last again!
Impossible!
It can't be helped. I'll need to bring out my special skill!
Ponya!
Chiinya!
The dora is 4p ... I'm 19000 points ahead of Yasu ...
I can deal in for 8000 and still be first!
So even if he has a concealed dora triplet and rons me with 2s tanki, I'm safe!
Kanya!
NOOOOOO
SUPERB! Tsumo nya!
Rinshan tanyao dora 6! Baiman! 4000/8000!
First place by 1000!
NOOOO BECAUSE HE CALLED THE ZUGAAAN
A poem!
Takame tsumo'd / he stands on cliff's edge / of the fjord
which hath scraped the peaks / of the tun-dora
(TN: tsumoru also refers to the piling up of snow)
Doesn't scan.
Hello, with Hayami ...
Help me, Akina!
What is he saying now ...
I have a fever so I'll just draw your haipai ...
Nooo, please play too!
I can't ... you do it ...
Menpin dora 3 iishanten?! With this even I'll be A-O-K!
Yeah, I'm not going to take this riichi nomi.
Huh?
Tsumogiri!
Nooo! What the hell's going on!?
9m!
Chii!
Nice call!
Pinfu ryanpeikou tsumo!
Maybe I should draw the haipai and Akina the tsumos ...
Huh?
Uhh, your chanta sanshoku?
Riichi!
Holy cringe! If the 25m come out it's just sanankou!
Hmmmm ...
Do not want.
Ron! Riichi ippatsu suuankou tanki!
Based!
Wow! I feel better after winning!
Yay!
Here here, you should get some rest if you have a cold ...
Here, put on this scarf!
Akina, this is ...
Get nice and warm so you get well soon!
Thank you!
Yasu!
Unlucky in the game, lucky in love!
The breeze blowing through the alleys was still cold ...
but their spring looked like it was just about to come.
*coof* And what about me!?