Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba prefecture.
Oda Shintarou, an ippatsu chad ignorant of theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasubee, a nyagger with zero understanding of mahjong theory. From Chiba prefecture.
Akechi Kouichi, an experienced player who plays an extremely logical mahjong. From Chiba prefecture.
Hayami Akina. Supposedly Toyotomi's girlfriend and the possessor of astounding good luck. From Chiba prefecture.
Ron! Mentanpin sanshoku, dealer mangan!
Zugan.
Ron! Menchin pinfu dora 1. Baiman!
Pass!
Ron! Yakuman!
Zugan!
Pon! Call to invigorate the field!
Triple ron!
Zugaaan!
THE INVINCIBLE RAGE OVERLOAD TECHNIQUE
Hmm, will it hold the 20th box?
I bet my lunch money it will!
Then I bet it won't!
It held!
Now treat us for lunch!
Oh no no no what are you doing?!
Fuck, I got it wrong ...
That being said, I'm 236k points in the green.
For me it's 178k.
I'm at exactly 200k!
He resembles me ...
That youngster is a spitting image of me in my young days!
It is he! I shall transmit my rage overload technique to him only!
Bye!
Cheer up, Toyotomi!
You're last!
7TH /MJG/ TOURNEY
Ron. Junchan sanshoku iipeikou. Dealer haneman.
You owe me another 8000.
REEEEEE
Mr. Ozawa isn't in good form today, huh?
Yeah, with a hand like this even I could do it!
REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
Ron. Menhon sanankou nan hatsu dora 1. Baiman.
REEEEEE
Oh no no no, he dealt in again!
Uh Ozawabros!? What is he doing!? Oh no no no no no no no!
SUPERB!
What the hell!?
He might finally be turning it around!
Honroutou honitsu toitoi ton hatsu dora 3, what the actual!?
What a surprise! Mr. Ozawa who had been so unlucky has won off ron with a spectacular technique!
That's the level C ultra tech called the "pon palace"!
It causes great psychological damage to opponents!
ITTSUU DORA DORA
SHOUSANGEN HONITSU
RIICHI CHIITOI
DAISANGEN
KOKUSHI MUSOU
P I N F U
Amazing! What the hell happened to Mr. Ozawa!?
No, it can't be! Is this the ...
Congratulations with your 5th Saikyoui title, Mr. Ozawa!
Your counterattack in all last was terrific, can you explain how you did it?
Rage overload.
Huh?
I used the rage overload technique.
The rage overload technique!?
Was that the legendary rage overload technique!?
What did he mean with "rage overload"?
When you play mahjong and get luckshitted on, anyone would REEEEEEE.
I guess.
As you keep dealing in, the REE becomes REEEEE and then REEEEEEEEEEE.
But when that state crossses a certain level ...
SUPERB!
You no longer care about the opponents' hands.
And when you enter this SUPERB! state of mind, the player's heart becomes like a perfectly clear spring gushing forth pure water, and incredible luckshitting occurs!
This is a graph which shows this transformation.
This is an ultimate secret certain kill technique transmitted only to the best disciples that can make even crying children deal in!
Truly the rage overload technique is to be feared!
Why did you bring me to these deep mountains?!
Be silent and listen! Don't you want to get stronger at mahjong?
Don't you want to keep winning, defeat them all and be worshipped as the strongest mahjong player in Japan?
Who the hell are you even?!
I see ... the time has come to reveal who I am.
5 TIME SAIKYOUI CHAMPION
OZAWA TAKESHOBO
Wow, it's written there!
This guy's the great Ozawa Takeshobo!
I might be able to win ...
If I follow him, I might be able to win.
Tsu ... mo ...
I underestimated you!
Don't even think you can defeat me with training wheels!
Come at with a real point stick next time!
Ron! Pinfu nomi.
You fool! Who told you to win?
I told you to deal in for flow!
Okay ...
Ron. Suuankou.
Ron. Kokushi musou.
REE
Yes! Get tilted!
Ron. Daisuushii.
REEEEEEEE
Get tilted even more.
The more tilted you get, the more the power of the rage energy will increase!
Let the tilt flow through your body, then let it explode! That's what mahjong is about!
Ron. Chuuren poutou.
REEEEEEEEEEEEEE
Yes! Like a tiger! You must become a tiger!
Double ron!
SUPERB!
At last!
My successor!
Master!
Well done, Toyotomi! At last you have mastered the rage overload technique!
You have transformed into a superb tiger!
Noooo!
Now, you will become Japan's strongest mahjong player!
Master!
The time has come for all of Japan's mahjong players to kneel before you!
NOOOOO
And I wanted to eat some yōkan dessert from Kanedaya before I died ...
Chestnut manjū from Nakagawa Main Store!
Get on with it!
At a place like this, I finally found you, Toyotomi ...
Toyotomi ...
Toyotomi, wait!
Toyotomi!
What happened?
Whose grave is that? Please tell me!
I am a tiger.
I have become a tiger.
What do you mean?
After enduring the harsh and painful lessons of Ozawa, Toyotomi finally mastered the rage overload technique.
Enemies no longer exist before him.
Win! Win! Rise up! Soon, Toyotomi will break through to total victory!
South 2, West seat, turn 9, 25500 points
tsumo 7m dora 3p
Guarantee either sanshoku or dora na no ja!
Toyotomi ...
What happened in those mountains?
Why won't you say anything to me?
I see ...
It's something you can't tell me.
Akina ...
It's fine.
You're no longer the Toyotomi I used to know.
TOYOTOMI'S REVENGE
NEWS TERMINAL
Good evening. It's time for News Terminal.
The first news of the day, from Omiya.
Ozawa Takeshobo (age unknown), known as Japan's strongest mahjong player
has passed away around a week ago
as has been revealed this morning.
The so-called invincible rage overload technique has thus been forever sealed away in mystery
having lost its only practitioner.
However, what even I didn't know was that there still was a user of the legendary rage overload technique left.
Mr. Wata!
Indeed, it's very regrettable, eh?
Although, it's something I used to hear rumors about from my grandfather when I was young, you see eh.
Well, in any case, the mahjong world has lost a valuable personality, eh?
We must really do our best, eh? From now on, eh?
Really, eh? Reaaaally!
We humbly do pray for his happiness in the next world.
Then, the next item from Omiya.
Today around noon, at the mahjong parlor "Miss Choice" in Meidaimae, Setagaya ward
someone led the shop's customers, about 20 persons, by the nose,
buried them deep in the shadowrealm,
and inflicted mental damage ranging from a week to a month to recover.
The authorities, taking a grave view of the situation, have imposed a state of high alert on the entire area and are pursuing the whereabouts of the culprit.
Hakabayashi reporting from the scene.
Yes.
This is the mahjong parlor avenue at Meidaimae where the incident occurred.
There are still places like this left in Japan!
What are the leads on the incident's perpetrator?
Yes. Currently, we cannot be cert-
Oh! Something seems to have happened over there!
Mr. Hakabayashi?
Yes. This is Hakabayashi.
It appears that an incident has occurred here just now!
Then, let us try to do an interview.
What was it that happened here?
I got rekt by the rage overload ...
Mr. Ume! Did you hear it? Rage overload!
The rage overload has reappeared!
But Ozawa Takeshobo was supposed to have died!
Yeah, but they just said someone got rekt by the rage overload, right?
Well, whose doing is this then?
Hey! Long time no see.
Toyotomi!?
Where the hell have ya been for a whole month?
Sorry for making you guys-
Our only joy in life was playing mahjong with you!
We even submitted a missing person report to Tokyo Metro Police!
A guy like you ...
Zugan.
Ron! Tanyao sanshoku, 5200!
Hm.
REE
Ron! Chun toitoi, 5800!
REEEEEE
Ron! Tanyao pinfu iipeikou dora dora, mangan.
REEEEEEEEEEEEEE
Why are you seething?
Let's just have fun, bro.
It's a long time since we've played together like this :^)
Fuck off!
Ron! 12000!
REEEEEEEEEE
Ron! 24000!
REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
SUPERB!
Wut!? Wut happened?
Toyotomi, any chance you know the rage overload technique?
Eh! Haneman?
TOYOTOMI'S HAIPAI NEXT ROUND
PON
TSUMO
HONROUTOU HONITSU TOITOI TON HATSU
ITTSUU DORA DORA
SHOUSANGEN HONITSU
RIICHI CHIITOI
AAAA! His rage overload technique is flawless!
Calm down!
We're trapped in his rage overload hell, and soon we'll get rekt so hard we won't be able to play mahjong any more!
Can it be that Toyotomi was that mahjong parlor destroyer?
Heh! Wutcha on about?! I can do that too!
It came out, huh ...
Pinfu.
Well, I guess it's chinitsu too.
Get outplayed, thanks.
You fucking damaing ...
Stop! If you start seething, it's just what the rage overload wants!
You have to keep playing at your usual pace!
Shut up! I don't give a fuck about his rage overload or whatever overload, for me just rage is enough!
Tsumo! Haneman!
REEEEEEEEE
Fuck! It's getting to my head too!
How's that! Ippatsu tsumo, dealer's mangan!
REEEEEE
Faggots! Letting everybody but me win!?
How's that! Tsumo! Dealer's haneman!
Ron! Ron! That's my winning tile, fucker!
Best out tsumo! Now fuckin' pay up those fuckin' point sticks!
Get fucked! Baiman!
Shadowrealmed!
Yakuman! Hand 'em fuckin' over!
Fuck! Dealer's baiman, fucking piece of shit!
Well fuck, got some fight left, you fucking shitter?
Shan't!
So, in the end, did the new you win?
Akina ...
I don't care if I win or lose ...
It's enough if I can play a mahjong that I can understand.
So ... you lost.
Akina!
Toyotomi!
I ... I ...
It's okay. You don't have to say anything.
You're the same old Toyotomi like always!
Thus rage overload, the killer technique that was transmitted only to the best disciples and could make crying children deal in,
was about to be buried away in history, becoming but a legend, true to its name.
Oh no! Perhaps I have taught my precious rage overload technique to the completely wrong person! Perhaps!
Ozawa's greatest blunder of his life!
At this rate I'll-
Seethe and cope.