Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
TN: this scene is a parody of Yotsuya Kaidan
6 man ...
7 man ...
8 man ...
9 man ...
1 man missing ...
1 man missing!
KAIDAN OF THE ZUGAN LANTERN
TN: Kaidan of the Peony Lantern (Botan Dourou) is a famous ghost story
Wut?
What's the fuss, Toyotomi?
I don't like this rain.
Indeed, it's so damp and gloomy ... it's giving me the chills.
I remember ... on a rainy day like this ...
Forgotten love?
No ...
But it was a rainy night like tonight, exactly one year ago ...
I encountered sleep paralysis ...
That day I came home tired from part-timing, so I went straight to sleep.
At about 2:00 AM ...
I noticed a sound like someone hitting a wall coming from somewhere ...
And that I couldn't move my body.
It's sleep paralysis ...
Then suddenly, I felt something painfully heavy on my feet.
Oh no! Something's climbing onto me, I thought.
But I couldn't move.
And it kept moving up my body step by step ...
Even someone like me'd get scared ...
"Please go away, I beg you!"
I thought, and closed my eyes ...
A while later, my body suddenly felt lighter ...
I thought it had left, and opened my eyes ...
And then ...
Next to my bed ...
A person in a white kimono was standing ...
Oh, I'll pon that!
"This is bad!" I thought, and closed my eyes again ...
And waited for dawn.
When I got to my senses, it was already morning.
It was all a dream, right?
No. I was fully conscious the entire time.
Riichi.
Oi! What's wrong?
Get on with it!
Hey, Toyotomi!
Sleep paralysis ...
I don't have any safe tiles!
All right, got it.
Okay? Close your eyes for a moment.
L-like this?
Good!
Now pick any tile and try to cut it!
C'mon!
That's the spirit!
Good! Good, good.
Now slowly open your eyes ...
Slowly ...
Winrar! Best out! Riichi ippatsu tanyao sanshoku!
Scary! Scarier than a ghost!
So, do you know this story?
It's a story about a certain long-haired actress.
Let's call her A-ko.
This A-ko went to stay in a hotel.
In fact, there had been a suicide 2 years earlier in her room ...
But of course A-ko didn't know that.
During the night, she couldn't sleep and went to the bathroom.
Her head hurt strangely and she felt sick.
When she looked in the bathroom mirror ...
Her hair was all standing on end!
I know a really similar story ...
I called riichi with this tile ...
It's actually a 7p suji trap wait ...
But Toyotomi has no way to know this.
Toyotomi cuts 7p to mawashi ...
In fact he deals into ippatsu!
And, if you look at Toyotomi's face ...
Somehow all his hair is standing on end!
In my senpai's hometown, they say there's an old battlefield.
Nooo, please stop!
Right? There's a place with a sacred rock in the middle of the road.
They tried to destroy that rock because it was in the way ...
But the construction workers started getting injured and strange things started happening ...
The road had to split and wind around the rock.
At night, my senpai went for a drive with two of his friends.
Some distance before the rock, a girl was waving.
They thought it was weird, but they let her hitchhike because she was cute.
The car got to the place with the rock.
When the two in front looked in the back mirror ...
The girl had no eyes, nose or mouth!
The two jumped out of the car and fled ...
But the one in the back got left behind ...
After they run away and calmed down, they got worried about him and came back ...
There, the girl was nowhere to be seen ...
And the one they left behind was done for ...
Pretend I'm scared ...
If the white one comes out it's daisangen!
White ...
Stop!
Toyotomi! What's wrong?
You okay?
Wutcha doin'?
It's your turn to draw.
No good ... I'm so focused on the haku their faces looked like the haku as well!
You want me to check up on Toyotomi, you say?
Yeah. He's been acting a bit weird.
TOYOTOMI
I can hear mahjong tiles ... What's that?
These are ...!
N-no way ...
No good! Like this his vigor will be sucked up until he dies!
Please do something!
It's morning.
Oh, Master!
I'm a little ...
Listen, Toyotomi!
The bunch you were playing mahjong with ...
Were not of this world!
They will be back tonight ...
But we shan't let them in!
Put up these talismans in your room and you can last till dawn!
Uhh, but aren't those yakuman mementos from parlors ...
Got it?! You mustn't let them in!
We can't take any chances! I'll write holy sutras on your body too!
All right ...
TN: Parody of the ghost story Hōichi the Earless
Open up, Toyotomi ...
Toyotomi ...
It's me, Toyotomi, open up!
The talisman's coming off ...
Toyotomi ... open up ...
Stop it!
Toyotomi ...
Toyotomi!
Akina ...
It's morning!
Toyotomi! It's me, Akina!
You did your best! It's okay now!
Akina! Akina!
You fell for it, Toyotomi!
Ron. Tanyao dora 4.
It's over ...
Ron. Honitsu dora dora. Mangan.
Zugan!
Ron. Riichi ippatsu toitoi.
Not like this ...
Oh my, this is bad ...
Ron!
Double ron!
I call ron too! Triple ron!
Dead inside zugan ...
I have disgraced your ears ...
(TN: A polite way of saying "thank you for listening")
An unseasonable ghost story!
(TN: Ghost stories are associated with summer, but this episode aired in January)
One evening of the Zugan Lantern ...
With this ...
East 4, West seat, 9th turn, 21400 points, 3rd place
Tsumo 8p, dora 6p
>cutting dora for sanshoku
ngmi
Oh no, it's no good! The compass isn't working!
No way!
Did ya get lost?
Boss!
Looks like it's gonna start pissin' down.
I WANT TO WIN
Is anyone here?
Minna koko?
Sorry for coming in!
What a gloomy house!
Is there really nobody here?
Let's take a dekko!
Whoa!
Boss! Boss! C'mere for a sec!
What happened, Kenjin?
It's a mahjong match in progress!
Here! It's a turn 5 riichi!
And a bloody spiffy riichi at that!
This seat is tenpai too!
Wut?! This one's hand is not that good.
But this one is!
Hmm ... Looks it's this seat's turn to discard.
Nothing to think about here, just tsumogiri!
Riichi!
Ron!
Tanyao only!
Heh, just like always, Toyotomi.
I wanted to win this hand ...
Welcome ...
Who are you?
I am the mistress of this house ...
We're sorry for coming in uninvited!
We got lost while hiking in the mountains!
You must be tired ...
Why don't you have a seat ...
And play some nice mahjong ...
Mahjong?
What do?
I don't like it! Playing mahjong with some mysterious person ...
Yeah, but it's such an opportunity ...
Yeah, let's go, let's go!
Will you play or not ...?
Let's play ... mahjong ...
EAST 1
Oh, what's wrong?
You're the dealer, so you gotta discard before we can start!
Riichi ...
What, double riichi?!
In East 1?
Wut?!
All right! Let's go! Try ronnin' these!
He's pushing like always ...
Boss, you shouldn't copy that lad.
Yasu cut 4p and it passed ...
I'll cut 7p suji!
Bloody hell! Ya don't get it at all!
Boss! Against a double riichi ya shan't cut a 3 or 7!
Gotta discard a terminal to be safe!
Ah, wakatte iru!
1m!
Pass ...
Look! Oikake riichi!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu dora 1! 5200!
So, what was your hand?
Yeah, show us!
"No."
Hey, we're just gonna take a look!
Aha! It was 7p penchan after all!
Told ya so, boss!
As expected of my disciple!
Aa! I hate thunder!
Crikey, I'm gonna spew!
I'll be right back, gotta chunder.
Now then, let's continue ...
Bugger this!
I'll be stuffed! I suddenly don't need to chunder!? What the hell?
Oi, what's that?
I'm stuck! Bloody cunt!
No worries, mate!
Crikey! As if!
Somebody! Help! Someone open!
Anyone!
Crikey!
Riichi.
What, another riichi?!
I'll be damned!
This one, I guess ...
What was that ...
To me it looked like one of the cupboard's doors flew open.
"Don't discard chun", I guess?
That means ...
Wut?!
Yasu, put out the fire, quick!
You damn ...!  C'mon!
Let's go on ...
What is this ... I guess this means ...
I'm not retarded! There's no way I'd cut this one!
Okay, I get it, I'll cut it!
Ron!
Oh, sorry, head bump! Ittsuu dora dora!
Oww! I'm feeling sick too!
Toilet break!
Kenjin! Kenjin!
He's taking long ...
Don't cut 7s ...
Hey, welcome back, Akina!
Are you feeling okay?
Wut? What did ya do there? And why are ya faces all flushed?!
It's your turn ...
What happened in this mansion?
You ask strange questions.
Nothing happened.
Riichi.
Huh ... That riichi ...
I feel like I've seen it somewhere ...
Hey, lady!
Ya haven't won a hand this entire game.
I can't win ...
Ever since I've started playing mahjong ...
I haven't won even a single hand ...
Not even once?!
But three years ago ...
On a rainy night like this one, I called riichi on turn 5 ...
But my shimocha dealt 7s into my kamicha's tanyao nomi ...
I wanted to win that hand ...
What happened to your opponents from then?
I can't remember ...
I made it!
Let's go!
Wait! Toyotomi!
Pon!
That's my win-
No! I clearly called pon so I won't let you ron!
Whoa! Chuuren poutou iishanten! Superb!
Ron!
Riichi kokushi musou.
Zugan!
Wut?!
Run!
It was the ghost of someone who left this world without winning once.
What a sad story ...
What was that chun?! C'mon ...
Thus, the pitiful woman's ghost ascended to heaven ...
And they all lived happily ever after ...
Or so one might have thought ...
That surely wasn't the last such person ...
Excuse me, but I heard that I can attain buddhahood by playing with you ...
(TN: die peacefully)
Me too ...
Scary!