Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Hey, what's the score?
East round's over, and yer on 48000 points, boss.
Heh, that's not a lot.
Well, time for South!
HEAD-ON ZUGAN
Tonight's Toyotomi's really something!
What, that's just the East round!
Riichi!
If I draw 6p or 7p, it's tanyao sanshoku tenpai ...
(dora 2m)
Dealer riichi ...
2s is dangerous ...
"Rich men shouldn't pick fights!" Mawashi!
I drew it ...
Boss!
If ya hadn't cut the 4s, ya could've won ya best out!
If the 4m and 2s had passed, that is.
All right! Riichi tsumo!
Oi! The dealer's wait was 58m!
Either one would've passed!
t. hindsight celestial
It was cheap anyway, it was the right call.
All right, with this I'll push everything!
And it's only turn 6!
Ron! Chun dora dora! 9600!
Boss!
Riichi!
My hand's trash ...
All right! Tsumo! 3000/6000!
Zugan!
Ron! 7700.
Tsumo. 500/1000!
Ron! 6400!
Tsumo! 8000!
You spin me right round zugan!
Mama-san, cold water please.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Good night!
Havin' to go for 2 minute noodles's pretty shonky, I reckon.
Why couldn't I take first place ...
I always get good draws in East ...
Today too! I had 48000 points going into South!
I got it, boss.
The beef's the dealer riichi in South 1!
Riichi!
Ya cut your only genbutsu, 4s, and bludged!
That's the obvious play as first place.
Fair enough, but after that ...
All right! Riichi tsumo!
Ron! 9600!
Tsumo! 3000/6000!
Ron! 7700.
Tsumo! 500/1000!
Ron! 6400!
Tsumo! 8000!
Okay, you can stop.
I shan't! That 4s is the reason for all ya losses, boss!
Right-o, boss?
If yar doin' hard yakka in pussers and the bones say "Carn!" and ya don't play head-on, that's piss-poor! Got it?
Head-on?
Too right! Like at Sekigahara!
When the victory of the Eastern Army was already assured!
FIFTH YEAR OF KEICHO ERA (1600)
BATTLE OF SEKIGAHARA
Two thousand Satsuma soldiers from the Western Army remained on the battlefield!
It seems our Western Army is defeated!
If we're to retreat, then we'll show them the spirit of Satsuma!
Hurrah!
Against the tens of thousands of advancing Eastern soldiers ...
They went on a never seen before in military history—forward retreat!
In other words, they retreated in the direction of the enemy!
They sped across right before the eyes of the Eastern commander, Tokugawa Ieyasu ...
And in the end were able to escape!
Splendid! They went straight through!
(TN: True story. The Satsuma forces were led by Shimazu Yoshihiro)
Another story!
Imagine yer a fine arts student who's destined to fail!
Okay ...
If yer gonna fail anyway, which model are ya gonna paint?
Huh?
A frontal nude, or from the back?
From the front!
Too right!
A man's gotta look head-on!
And so with mahjong!
If yer gonna get last anyway, it's better to get it head on than by folding!
Even if ya get destroyed completely and go 100k into the shadowrealm ...
It's just a last place after all!
That's right!
Understood, boss?
I got it all right ...
But there's one thing ...
"If you're gonna get last anyway ..."
That's what you said, right?
Huh? W-well I was just telling the truth ...
I see ... I understand what you meant now ...
Make a circle with your hands.
Whatcha gonna do, boss?!
Our friendship is over!
Now get lost!
B-boss!
Hey!
You came!
That's no good, you gotta be nice to him!
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Look, time to reconcile!
Boss!
He was crying, you know.
Boss! Forgive me!
I get it.
From now on, you'll get to take a good look at my head-on playstyle!
Righto.
No worries, mate. Head on!
Wait for it! To play head-on, in other words to greed!
Riichi.
Oh no, I was too slow with discarding 8m!
And with 5p and 3s!
What?!
N-no worries, mate! Just talkin' to myself, carry on, mate!
Oho! Greeding successful!
If I cut 4m, I have tanpin sanshoku tenpai!
Do you think 4m will pass?
Time like these, ya gotta think she'll be right!
It's London to a brick he's waiting on the 25p ya got an anko of!
All right, let's go!
Ron! Riichi pinfu.
Zugan!
Crikey!
Riichi.
Fodl.
Hmm, I can chii 2p and get keishiki tenpai with upgrade to sanshoku ...
But ...
Will the 8s pass?
Chii!
Push for muh tenpai!
Get rekt! Riichi chanta sanshoku, mangan!
Crikey!
Zugan!
Toyotomi's pitchin' fast tonight!
Boss, ya still got 1000 points left.
Even if you get shadowrealmed, if ya play head on you'll get good hands for sure!
Really!
Wow, it's true! What a great hand!
Told ya!
Pon!
Chii!
Tsumo! Nan honitsu chanta!
Ya bewt!
Honitsu iipeikou!
Riichi chiitoi!
Pinfu dora dora!
Tanyao dora 3!
Junchan ryanpeikou!
Boss! The head-on's shit-hot!
Yer first in all last!
All right, now it's simple!
Take first by winning a hand!
Kenoath, mate!
Pon!
Time for a power move!
Kan!
Yer head-on's rip snorter, boss!
Thought so!
All right, drew a 3p anko!
Haku pon!
Kan this too!
Whoa, amazing draws!
Kan! Kan! Kan!
All right, tenpai for toitoi sankantsu haku dora 3!
She'll be right!
Pass plox!
KAAAAAN!
Boss!
Suukantsu?!
Heh.
Nothin' personnel, Toyotomi.
Ton, kan!
Huh?
Now it's a draw.
There's no abortive draw when there's a suukantsu!
Bullshit! There's no rinshan to draw anymore!
Hey, Shintarou ... I kind of agree with Toyotomi though ...
(he's in suuankou tenpai)
I also think it doesn't go to draw in this case.
(also in suuankou tenpai)
Toyotomi won't be the one to win this round.
I'll win a suuankou before him!
All right, got it! Then I'll just draw this dora indicator!
No way!
Whoa, 1m tsumo!
Whoa, my winning tile was there?!
Tsumo, sanankou dora 8! Comeback into first!
Zugan!
So, that's what happened last night?
My head-on playstyle backfired ...
But, Toyotomi, if one player has made four kans, a fifth kan can't be made, didn't you know that rule?
Wait, for real?!
Zugan!
Duke said "Don't stand behind me!"
(TN: from the manga Golgo 13)
Miho-chan said "Who's behind me now?"
(TN: from the nursery rhyme Kagome Kagome)
The Grumman F4F pilot said "Don't fly a Zero behind me."
Toyotomi thought "Let's paint a model from behind some time!"
East 3, North seat, 10th turn, 23000 points
Tsumo 6s, dora 3m
KAAAAAAAAAN
Wassup!
How do you do, mama-san?
Ah, welcome. I'm glad you came too, Akina.
What happened, mama-san?
What happened to them, mama-san? They look like their soul left their body!
Well the truth is, just now ...
They were beaten down by me!
What?!
LUCKLET RIICHI GETS POINT READ?!
Ah, I'm bored!
What's Toyotomi doing?
Mama-san, when will he be back?
Toyotomi's working the evening shift today.
He said he had to go to a university lecture.
Mama-san ... the semester's over, so there's no way he's gone to a lecture.
Oh, is that so?
Can I join?
Sure, there's a free spot right here!
I see. All right, nice to meet you.
Wut? We might have a big fish here.
For sure.
That man ... I've seen him somewhere ...
Ah, I remember!
I'm the dealer.
Pon!
Riichi!
Dora: 4p
Whoa! That's a ballsy discard.
Don't worry. Cutting safe tiles isn't ballsy.
What's a safe tile?! I drew that to get into tenpai.
Dammit! Now yer cutting risky tiles too!
I read your wait. It's 69m, and I have an anko of it.
6m just passed! Pay attention, scrub!
Wutcha sayin'? You're gonna deal into my 18k anyway, Shintarou.
C'mon, draw it.
Wait: 3p58s
C'mon, deal in, you fat scrub.
Wait: 3p
The dora ...
I'll turn it to baiman! Dora tanki!
The fat guy's 2p was one turn too early ...
Wait: 25p
Ahh, would have been ippatsu!
All right, tsumo dora 1!
Furiten?!
And just a tsumo dora 1?
What a scrubby win!
That's what happens when I read and hold on to all your waits!
Riichi!
Oh, 7m suji trap again? I won't fall for it!
Pon!
You like toitoi, huh? You have a shanpon of ton and chun!
Bro, even if you dama that pinfu ittsuu, I won't cut your 4m takame!
He's reading ... our waits ... perfectly ...
The point read big guy?
That's right. He's nicknamed the "point read big guy".
The bane of every mahjong parlor!
His reading instinct's extremely skillful, and he never deals in!
Like this, he'll crash this parlor with no survivors!
I got it, mama-san.
The man Toyotomi will put him in his place!
Let's do our best!
Don't worry, mama-san, I'm enough of a match for him by myself.
Let's do something, Akina!
I'll do my best!
Let's do our best!
Toyotomi, you can keep cooking the octopus!
No, I'll join too!
Oho, mama-san and the lady colluding with each other ...
Rude! I'm playing too!
Riichi!
Made it! I have a dora pair! I can even get haneman!
Sujibros!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu iipeikou ura 1!
Zugan!
I should have been less greedy and cut 1p genbutsu!
A parlor employee dumb enough to deal into such an obvious suji trap?!
Anyway, sorry mama-san! Head bump!
What's so funny?
Mister! I see you're trying to cancel her win, but this parlor allows double ron!
I see ... Then that means you dealt into mangan and 5200.
Zuga–
Why do you have to dig your own grave?
Excuse me for a minute.
Maybe he's ...
Aha! Spotted!
You were doing drugs to improve your instinct?!
He saw me ...
We can't allow such dangerous people in our parlor so please leave and I'll be taking this as well and calling the police, thank you and goodbye and please don't come again!
What the fuck are you saying?
It's just ordinary glucose!
Wow, it's actually sweet.
Of course!
It's just a type of sugar.
I'm improving my instinct with nutrients only!
Ah, that's it ...
Oh, so that's why you're so fat!
The fire rises!
Riichi!
Even a big guy like you couldn't read my wait here!
Ah, a 69m wait? That's a nice wait.
Or so it would have been if you weren't playing against me!
No way!
Tsumo!
Nice tsumo, I knew that 6m was your wait.
If I riichi, he'll read my wait. I'll dama!
I can read dama too! 2s kanchan, isn't it?
How did you know?! Tsumo, haneman!
There's no way he can read this wait ...
I can read shanpon too! 5m and 8s!
Ah! I got exposed like an idiot!
Tsumo! I'm embarrassed, but it's dealer baiman!
This is bad ... I have to get this girl off dealer.
Chii!
Pon!
Tsumo! 300/500 with 1 honba, that's 400/600!
I'm shadowrealmed!
No good! I'm 20k in the red and in third place!
I need to go on the attack!
She's got an early 58p wait ...
Dora: 5s
What's this? 5p kan!
And then, 8p kan!
Riichi!
With that hand, she can't but cut 67p!
What?!
Impossible!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu tanyao chiitoi!
Dora dora dora dora!
Dora dora dora dora dora dora dora dora dora ...
Anyway, looks like you got shadowrealmed in East 1 too!
Fuck off! I'd hear that from anyone but you!
Another hanchan!
Early riichi!
7p penchan, isn't it?
Oh no, you're spot on! Ippatsu tsumo, dealer's mangan!
I know!
Your read was right! Tsumo, haneman!
Spot on! Tsumo, 2000/4000!
Spot on! Tsumo, 3000/6000!
Kokushi, waiting on 9s!
Kyaa! I'm no match for your reads!
Tsumo, yakuman!
Shadowrealmed.
Heh, big guy ... was losing part of your plan?
What?!
Lot of loyalty for a shadowrealmed lucklet!
We're both shadowrealmed ... But I'm starting dealer! And you're West seat!
In other words ... you're last by placement!
Well done, Toyotomi! He didn't fly so good!
If I read their waits it doesn't matter ... I won't even look at them!
What matters is to attack!
All right, my takame came out!
Honitsu ittsuu iipeikou, haneman!
For you!
Mate, that's too painful even for you.
Yeah, at least try to read his wait!
Look, you drew a suji!
All right, big guy on table three! Shadowrealmed again!
Well, floating and sinking go together in life!
But you're the one that made him sink! You!
Float and sink, sink and float ...
In any case this world is best spent going with the waves.
Even if you try to go with the waves ...
Tomorrow's harbor weighs on your mind.