Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
Finally!
The day when maidens bashfully confess their true love to their sweetheart!
The yearly ultra big event!
Valentine's Day!
MY LUCKLET VALENTINE
I hope I'll get heaps of chockie this year!
Hey!
So, how many did you get last year?
Last year's last year!
So, zero.
Stop takin' the piss out of me!
So how many chockies did you get, mate?
Ron!
Chiitoi. And yes, I did get chocolate from 7 girls.
I only got some from my gf Megumi.
Ron! Sanankou dora 1, hatsu hell wait!
I got chocolate from Tomomi, Junko, Rie, Masako ...
About 13 girls!
No way!
Ron! Kokushi! 13-sided wait!
Toyotomi! How many did you get?
Zero.
Right-oh! As expected of me boss!
That feel when you know that feel!
Happy Valentine's Day!
Hey, Akina!
Here, Toyotomi, my homemade chocolate!
Thanks!
Boss ...
And storebought chocolate for the rest!
Oh, thanks.
Arigatoh!
I can feel Hayami's love!
Heh, lollies're for sheilas 'n' ankle biters ...
So did ya bring one for me too?
Sorry, I bought one too few!
You're a background character anyway!
As if!
Just ya watch!
I'll get a mahjong gf and chockie today, kenoath!
She'll be apples.
I'll show them my true blue root rat playboy skills!
Oi, sheila! How 'bout some tea 'n' bickies?!
No!
Oi, sheila! How 'bout—
Am I a joke to you?!
Oi, shei—
Shut up!
Crikey!
These Tokyo sheilas don't know what a true blue bloke I am!
SFX: hurrying
I'll make you my mahjong gf!
Shan't let ya escape! I was my middle school's sprint champion!
And I was known as the best runner of Kamakura High School!
She's from Kamakura?!
Good onya, sheila.
Y-you too ...
I think we'll make a ripper couple.
Yeah ...
This is my boss's house.
No worries, you can come in.
There ya are.
And we thought ya wouldn't be comin' back ...
Who is that?
My mate.
Nice to meet you! I'm Asami.
Help yourselves!
Oh, what a nice girl!
She's too good for ya!
Can I brew some tea?
Don't worry, I'll do it.
You can sit down with Kenjin, Asami.
I shan't let me boss's gf do such a thing!
Hey! Make mine real thick and steamy!
Thick and steamy? You barely know her, you sick fuck!
Well, I'll brew it.
It's fine, you can sit down, Kenjin.
No, I'll do—
No, I'll—
I'll do it!
No, I'll do it!
Asami ...
Kenjin ...
I don't care who does it, but get on with it!
Right-io!
Can you swap two players out so I can join?
Sure!
I like it more when there's two fish rather than one.
Fish?
You mean me?
You're a funny guy!
He made the tea kettle whistle!
The hell ...
Ii kumiawase!
As expected of a couple ...
Now that I have a mahjong gf, there's no one here who can beat me!
Sorry, I need you to not be here for a sec.
Now, there's really no one in this room who can beat me!
You're joking, right?
We'll beat you at your own game!
Now watch my playstyle.
8m or 1p, which should I cut?
Obvious dama, and go for the dama junchan sanshoku dora 1 haneman on 7m.
Nice! The skill of a man who got 7 chocolates last year!
I'll make ya feel it all right ...
Riichi!
Zugan! If I knew it was gonna come out, I should have called riichi!
I'll ponya that dora!
I'll riichi then!
2s!
9s!
3s!
If it won't come out ... I'll tsumo it!
Ron!
Riichi tanyao pinfu ura 1!
Toitoi dora 3! Superb!
Zugan! Double ron!
So. That's all skill.
Sure, I don't know how to play mahjong!
What's that?
Zugan!
Wow, so cute! What are these flowers?
Heh, m'lady ... Those are ...
Lucklet flowers ....
My heart makes them bloom whenever something sad happens ...
They're so pretty! Can I pick them?
Go ahead, they'll bloom  plenty more so it's fine!
As if I'll let you!
Chiinya!
Ponya!
The 8m ...
Oh no ...
Oi, mate! Discard quick!
The ticking of time ain't just for you!
What?! Then try ronning this tile, fucker!
Yer back's gonna be a real flower bed, mate.
Ron! Chinitsu.
Zugan!
Wow, so pretty!
I'll put some on Ken too!
Stop it!
But why, when they're so pretty?
Riichi!
I drew the last 3m!
14m are the dora suji, and a great wait!
Should I cut 4p and go for an iishanten accepting 36p58s14m?
Or cut 8s and accept 1245m2356p?
No! 4p and 8s are both risky!
I'll fold and ...
Discard genbutsu for acceptance of 58s25m25p!
Crikey! I drew the dora!
But no worries mate, I'll cut 5m!
Crikey! I should have made 8s my head and dropped 67s!
Oi!
Then I'd have won off of that 2p!
The hell ya on about?
It's over ...
Whoa ...
This is ...
Ron! Riichi hatsu ura ura!
Crikey! I've been infected by boss's luckletism!
Ron! Baiman!
Ron! Dealer's haneman!
I can do better! Tsumo! Suuankou!
Double super zugan!
We'll, we're off to go get our own chocolates.
It was tasty!
Have fun with your gf!
Zugan!
All right, I'll be heading home too!
It was fun!
W-wait, Asami ...
Huh?
Are ya ... are ya gonna leave me behind all buggered like this?
Asami ...
You didn't love me?
No, I love you. So ...
So ...
Let's just be good friends!
Those words are ...
Bye!
Zugan.
The finishing blow.
Let's just be friends.
Thus, Kenjin died.
South 2, West seat, 8th turn, 19800 points
Tsumo 5p, dora 7m
You vill NOT riichi ze dora tanki!!!
AKINA TRIANGLE
I see. Chun pon!
Heh, now I'm tenpai for chun chanta sanshoku dora 1!
Ron! Dealer's mangan!
I've got good flow today!
Oi, boss!
Ya got heaps good flow today!
But he shouldn't get too carried away ...
Welcome!
What's going on, mama-san?
That's Sanjouin Kimimaro!
Wow! The crown prince of Sanjouin Group—the kingpin of the Japanese economy!
Welcome!
Is there a free seat?
Crown prince coming to his private parlor—talk about being fed from a silver spoon.
Toyotomi!
You're a funny guy.
Well then, Can I join your table?
You all right, mama-san?!
EAST 1
STARTING DEALER: SANJOUIN
I'll show this greenhorn the roughness of the world's waves!
Well then, East 1 ...
Let's start with a dealer's mangan.
Mr. Sanjouin is famous for winning with the score he announces beforehand!
What?! Babe Ruth's got skill too!
C'mon!
Pon!
Tch, double ton? I've got a good hand too!
Cut dora before it's too late!
Dora pon!
Boss, ya shouldn't let him call all that!
Don't whine about things that can't be helped!
All right, riichi!
Let's go! Riichi shaa honitsu iipeikou! If I ippatsu tsumo the hatsu, it's baiman!
I shan't let anyone stop my ippatsu!
Oh no no no!
Ron! Double east dora 3, that's 12000.
Zuga—
Oh, that's right, did I lose already?!
Let's win 5800 from toimen now, shall we?
Boss!
Ron! Dealer's 60 fu sanankou, 5800 plus 1 honba.
Zugan!
Senpai!
Cheers!
It's such a long time since we've talked like this!
Indeed.
I was on exchange in London, so it's been about two years.
You've become a real lady in the meantime.
No way, senpai!
There's something I'd like to give to you.
T-this is ...
A memento of our reunion.
Something so fancy ...
I can't accept it.
Whaaat?!
N-no way, you already love someone else?
Yes.
There's something I'd like to give to you, Akina. Here!
No way, three months of your salary?
(TN: the traditional price for an engagement ring)
What's this ...
Aww, that's so unlike you, Akina! It's basalt!
I shan't give up!
Ahh, it's cold!
Kotatsu's the best when it's cold!
Come in!
You get it!
What do you think this is, bush week? You're the boss, and this is your place, so you should be dealin' with guests!
What the ...
C'mon, what's going on?
Akina!
You're ...!
Well, well, we meet again. I'd never have thought you were Toyotomi.
Are you really in love with Hayami?!
Wh-wha ...
I love her!
What?!
I've graduated from Oxford, work at Sanjouin Group, and at age 24 already make over 80 million yen per year!
On top of that, I'm 188 cm tall and have a good face!
However, Hayami still wants to choose you over me.
She does ...?
Boss! This ain't the time to be takin' the piss!
But I still don't consider you to be Hayami's boyfriend!
What?!
That's right. I'll fight you at mahjong once again!
If you can beat me, I'll be a gentleman and step aside!
What do you say?
Wait, Akina! Life is always a gamble!
Whatever's the thing—if you win, flowers! If you lose and fall, the mud!
No ...
The only field where I have a chance against other people is mahjong!
Riichi!
Ron! Riichi ippatsu chiitoi ura ura!
And I'm so bad at mahjong!
Toyotomi ... It's just started ... Do your best!
Kan!
Tanyao dora 3 straight away!
2m is dora, 4p is the dora indicator ...
This shanpon won't come out.
If I cut 4p, the 369p is furiten.
All right ...
Shan't take furiten!
Boss, I'll help ya.
If he can't call anything in pinzu, he's buggered.
Try callin' it, mate, the 8p you just cut!
Chii!
Crikey, what's that call?!
Riichi!
Tsumo! Mangan.
Horrible!
My luck is even worse than normal!
Shan't let ya whinge an' give up!
All right, surely this riichi will win!
You just don't get it, do you?
C'mon! Please! The dora!
She's trying to deal in!
Hayami was really on boss's side after all!
This is Hayami's answer!
Why won't you ron her if she loves you this much?!
Shut up!
Ron! Honitsu haku.
Thank you, Hayami. I can feel your love!
Cunt! I'll bugger ya up!
Carn!
Pon!
Tsumo 3s! Crikey ...
Tsumogiri!
Boss! Why did ya call an' flog my tsumo?
Oi, that's a ripper draw! Good on me!
She'll be right mate, closed chinitsu 259s wait!
9s!
Crikey! I shan't ron ya, boss!
Aight, I'll tsumogiri and riichi!
This passed last turn!
Boss! A bloody pair drop!
Goddamn it, mate! Riichi ippatsu chinitsu, baiman!
(TN: skipping ron in riichi used to be illegal)
Zugan!
Hayami, what's there even to like about this guy?
All people get unlucky sometimes.
He's in a bad spot now too.
But senpai, can you make such beautiful and colorful flowers bloom when you're unlucky?
This woman has lost her composure.
Ron! Best out riichi pinfu ittsuu!
You've been the ace #4 hitter since forever, senpai, and you're amazing.
(TN: the best player is 4th in batting order)
But people who've always been subs on the bench and still never gave up are even more admirable!
They're beautiful ...
I see ...
I never knew flowers growing forgotten by the wayside could be so valiant and beautiful ...
Sanjouin-senpai ...
I have lost.
You've showed me something so beautiful ...
But I still shan't give up!
If I can make such flowers bloom, then for sure ...
For sure I'll be able to ...
Let's just give up ...?
Ah! Did they know the feelings that dwelt in their hearts, or not?
The lucklet flowers said nothing and bloomed in silence.
Working at a mahjong parlor is hard work!
You have to fill in for customers and teach them manners!
I wonder if Toyotomi can do that?
Next time on Super Zugan:
"Welcome to the Mahjungle" and "Mahjong Rules 101"
Don't miss it! Don't want to you to sleep on it!