Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
NEW YEAR'S ZUGAN
He drew it!
But he needs to discard 1p or 5p against 3 riichis ...
Which one will ya cut, boss?
YASU
AKECHI
AKINA
Pass.
I want to ... see the sea.
B-boss!?
What the bloody hell happened to ya?
Tsumo!
Suuankou tanki.
As dealer, that's 96000.
Strong!
He's a whole different man!
Completely different from last year's Toyotomi!
How did it ...
NEW YEAR'S EVE 1992
For juice, is grapefruit fine?
Daijoubu!
Shan't buy any New Year's soba noodles!
I love Tonbee noodles!
(TN: Sanuki udon, a popular Shikoku dish)
Well, I guess I'm a stickler for tradition.
It's gone!
It's common for cup noodles to run out before New Year!
Please ...
500 yen per cup.
Zugan.
Well, Toyotomi ...
You don't have to eat those trashy cup noodles!
Akina!
Will you maybe cook me homemade soba yourself?!
Yeah!
They got a new wrapper!
If you get hungry, eat a lot of these!
Zugan!
Shintarou's gone to his hometown, I wonder how he's doing ...
Playing mahjong no doubt!
Yeah, that guy's got no brains for anything else!
Not a single good thing's happened to me all year!
Wait a second, you.
Uhh, m-me?
That's right.
You have the look of a lucklet.
I'll tell your fortune for next year using my guitar!
In '92 you were unlucky!
However next year it will go well!
Whoa luckshit luckshit yeah yeah!
What did he mean by this ...
What a load of bullshit!
Yeah, funny guy!
Hey! You guys still eating?
C'mon, let's play after we're done, hm!
You want to play already?
Obviously! Let's go, pick your seat!
EAST 1 TURN 8
Riichi!
Crikey! Doragiri riichi!
Fodl.
Hooly dooley!
What a bewt!
4p is safe, so cut 7p and wait on the dora which just passed!
It's a superb wait!
Cringe!
That's piss-weak, mate, I'm spewin'!
Hmm, maybe ...
Genbutsu!
If 7p passed you'd have won 6400!
Don't whisper so close to my ear, retard!
Pretty spiffy!
Now cut 3m and with 9p it's riichi chun iipeikou for 5200! She'll be right, mate!
Time to push!
Piss-poor!
If ya'd kept the chun ya'd have hit the 6p with riichi ippatsu chun!
Cutting chun for iipeikou nomi dama ...
Pig's arse!
The dora!
Crikey! He's even breakin' his tenpai!
I overestimated ya, boss.
From today my new boss is Hayami!
No backseating.
What d'ya mean by that!? Ya promised me you'd let me teach you!
I can do it myself, you know!
Oh no no no, boss!
That's dicey, mate, bloody dicey!
Riichi!
Tenpai!
Ron!
Riichi ippatsu chanta sanshoku!
Haneman, mate!
Zugan!
By the way, Akechi, what was ya hand, mate?
I had a mentanpin 258m wait with sanshoku ...
Many such cases!
Both 7p and 3m would have passed!
Shut up!
Pon! Pon! Sore pon!
Riichi.
5p ... the dora!
Fold with suji!
Ron!
The cheaper out ...
Riichi ippatsu tanyao!
I'm at -3200 in the shadowrealm ...
This 5-shanten haipai will be this year's last ...
This year's last riichi!
Ron!
Akemashite omedetou!
Riichi ippatsu ittsuu!
Zugan!
Riichi!
Toyotomi, I hope you'll do the needful this year too!
What's wrong, Toyotomi?
Ura suji ...
Pass ...
All those dangerous tiles ...
Riichi.
Ron.
Riichi tanyao pinfu iipeikou.
Holy rigged ...
It's not last year's Toyotomi!
Wut? Shan't believe you.
Riichi!
C'mon, Toyotomi, deal in!
Riichi, huh ...
Ura suji!
Gah! Pass.
I have genbutsu ...
But I cut 4m on purpose!
But why?
Yeah, why?
That's because ...
Because I'm confident!
Matagi suji!
Pass.
Suji!
3 times out!
Pass!
Genbutsu riichi!
So confident! Those discards with this hand!
Boss's reincarnated into a chad!
The fortune telling was right!
Wut?
Ron!
Riichi ippatsu tanyao!
But boss!
Ya might flog Akechi and Tokugawa ...
But until ya flog Miss Hayami ya aren't the dinky-di!
TURN 10
DORA 6s
Closed honitsu iishanten!
She made it!
Cut 5s for 8s kanchan ...
Or 9s for 6s kanchan ...
But 6s is the dora ...
No one will discard it ...
Push the haku!
Pon!
Crikey!
The hatsu and chun ...
Haven't been cut at all!
There's no doubt this is daisangen!
I shan't discard this ...
I'll fold with ...
Ron!
Haku dora 1!
Nooo, you can't cut dora from that hand!
Ya ning-nong!
A new dawn!
The sun rises on 1993, Toyotomi's Year 1!
Ron! Sanankou chanta honitsu hatsu chun ton!
Boss! As expected of me boss!
Ya're the only one in the green!
What?!
Yasu, -1!
Akechi, -1!
Akina, -1!
Toyotomi, +3!
Well, cheers to you for today's game.
Amazing, Toyotomi!
Sole winner ...
It's so trifling when you look back on it ...
Hey, Toyotomi, since you're the sole winner, why don't ya treat us!
It's New Year after all!
I'll have the calf steak, Koakuma spicy style!
I'll have a large "fabula" with extra egg!
I'll have the Sanzeno full course menu!
Fine if I wrap my laughin' gear round the same as Hayami?
And some pickles for me, please.
Certainly, sir.
Thus ended the turbulent year 1992 ...
and heading towards the dramatic climax, Toyotomi's year 1993 began!
Three months remain until Super Zugan's final episode!
And to you dear viewers, Happy New Year!
East 4, South seat, 12th turn, 27800 points.
Tsumo 2p dora 7s
1p riichi
TN: one of the 5p should be a 4p, see last frame
Riichi!
Wut? Riichi on turn 4 already?!
Pass!
Tenpai!
What should I do ...
Cut 2p and call riichi with up to pinfu iipeikou dora 1 ...
2p should pass ...
No ... it's only turn 4 ...
It's also possible to cut 1p genbutsu and go for tanyao!
Whatcha thinking about? Just cut something!
Toyotomi!
I can draw 34s for sanshoku ...
But can I afford to slow my hand down that much?
Toyotomi!
Zugan!
ONCE UPON A ZUGAN
Guys! Stop it, guys!
Wut?
Who's you?
Have a go at the turtle too!
Y-you shouldn't bully animals ...
Please stop ...
I shan't let you abuse a helpless animal!
What!?
What a cocky guy!
Get him!
Zugan ...
Heh, no match for us.
All talk and no bite.
Let's go!
Tangs! Tangs for kelping me!
Let me roe you to the Dragon Palace.
Why don't you perch yourself on my back.
The Dragon Palace?
Is that where "the sea breams and flounders dance"?
(TN: from the schoolbook song "Urashima Taro")
Indeed.
And a bonito princess too, I hope!
Dace right, chum!
Tanoshii!
Sorry for the wait.
That's the Dragon Palace!
Tsumo! Chiitoi dorado dorado!
Oh roe!
Sharks to be you!
There were a great many minnows and whales in that mahjong parlor.
Princess Otohime, I brought a customer!
Welcome!
I'm Otohime, working as manager of this establishment!
Want!
If you win at mahjong, okay?
I've seen these guys somewhere before ...
Wutcha yappin' on about? C'mon, chop chop, let's go!
Shan't lose against minnows and whales ...
Riichi ippatsu dora dora bang bang!
I shan't give up on Otohime after just a mangan ...
Ron! Honitsu ippatsu haku dora dora! Baiman!
Not yet!
Ron! Riichi tanyao dora dora, as dealer that's 12000!
YOU CAN PLAY ALONE AS WELL
Here, your jewel box!
Zugan!
And thus, Urashima Taro's hair turned all white ...
What's that?
Oh my, such a big ii-pin!
From that ii-pin, a baby boy cute as a button was born.
And they gave him the inevitable name Zugantaro.
15 YEARS LATER
Dear goodness, he keeps eating through all our rice!
Thanks to him, we're in the red this month again!
Why don't we get rid of him somewhere?
Yeah!
Uhh ... I'm going to exterminate the demons and bring back a lot of treasure.
Bloody oath, boss! We're countin' on ya!
And bring something back for us!
Look! Special point stick millet dumplings!
Thus Zugantaro left on his quest to exterminate the demons.
Where are ya goin' in that hero getup?
Must be carrying some tasty stuff.
Hand it over, Zugantaro.
These are the precious millet dumplings my grandma gave me!
I shan't give them to you lot!
Well how about this ...
We play mahjong, and if we win, we get the dumplings.
And if I win?
We will be your retainers and follow you to Demon Island.
There's no way I can lose against these animals ...
Let's go!
Tanyao pinfu sanshoku, dealer's mangan!
Zugan!
Damn it, I shan't lose against animals!
Scree! That's my wait!
Chinitsu pinfu dora 1, baiman!
This should pass ...
Ik ook!
Suuankou monkey!
Zugan!
Well, let's eat those dumplings!
Yeah, let's eat!
Won't you let me have just a bite ...
What, you're still alive?
Here, have a bite.
100 points.
Zugan!
And thus they say that Zugantaro never got to Demon Island.
Little Red Lucklet! Little Red Lucklet!
Yes, mom?
I have an errand for you.
Okay!
Bring these tiles to your sick grandmother.
But these are mahjong tiles, Akina!
Don't talk back.
And then, I'm your mom.
And you might know this already, but ...
We're the Three Wolves!
Excuse me!
It's the newspaper!
Is the sick grandmother here?
Hello!
Oh my, three cute boys!
I've got some spare time, why don't you come in?
Riichi.
Wut?
That's obviously a 47s wait!
Your reading skills are no big deal ...
Really?
In that case, 4s kan!
Riichi!
Ron! Riichi tanyao ippatsu!
C'mon!
Whoa!
I have a kan of 4s, so 8 ura. Sanbaiman.
Zugan!
Well, looks like we're in charge of this house now.
Someone's here! Hide!
I came to see you, grandma!
I'm so glad to see you!
How are you feeling?
Whoa!
Grandma, why are your hands so big?
It's to grab a lot of riichi sticks!
Grandma, why are your eyes so big?
To look at your discards really well!
And why is your mouth so big?
It's ...
To say ron!
Toyotomi! Hey! Wake up, Toyotomi!
How do you even fall asleep playing mahjong?
Do you even want to play seriously?
Cut it out or bad things will happen.
A dream?
I see! I can't let myself be misled by Akechi's discards!
These guys are all beasts!
I'll avoid ippatsu and go for tanyao, cutting 1p!
Genbutsu!
Ron!
Akechi's genbutsu is a big hit for me! Junchan sanshoku pinfu dora dora!
Zugan ...
Tsk ...
Unlucky ...
And thus, Little Red Lucklet was all eaten up by the wolves.
And they all lived happily ever after​.