Article 186 of the Penal Code
A person who habitually gambles or bets shall be punished by hard labor for not more than 3 years.
SOUTH POLE ZUGAN
This is Souzu! Heisei Base, please respond!
(TN: Parody of the icebreaker Sōya's 1958 evacuation of Shōwa Base)
What?! In that case, the Souzu can't advance any more.
It's over. Wait for the weather to improve and dispatch a helicopter.
End of transmission.
You've all heard the message.
We won't be able to get out of here?
Yeah. Until the helicopter arrives, we'll have to wait.
There is one problem.
What is it?
There are five of us in this first Antarctic wintering party.
However, the helicopter only seats four.
And if the helicopter can make two round trips in this bad weather ...
Subete wa God knows.
In other words ...
One of us has to be left behind ...
I should be able to beat this guy ...
Well, in any case I should be able ...
All right? I'll say it again!
The game's South Pole rules, south round only! One dealer turn for each of you and it's done.
I'm the captain, so I'll be the first to get in the chopper. That's the rule.
SOUTH 1
All right. I'm the starting dealer.
Chii!
Ryanmen chii on turn 5? Does he have an anko of the dora chun?
8s!
Ron! Tanyao, 1000!
Spending the Antarctic winter's alone gonna be cold!
Fuck! Screwing over my dealer turn with his fucking 1000!
SOUTH 2
Pon!
I shan't cut this hatsu against toitoi ...
This one!
Sorry!
South only, 1000!
Have fun looking at the aurora by yourself!
Fucker ...
SOUTH 3
Heh, I've paid him back!
Ron! Pinfu only, 1000!
Sanmenchan dama? Holy based!
ALL LAST
Bruh ... what's this haipai ...
I'll pon that!
If Yasu tsumos, I get away with 3rd place!
He's clearly still in iishanten!
I'll let him call the tiles he needs!
Call it!
Wut, it came out? Chun only, 1000!
Zugan!
Tied for last place ...
What?! The helicopter seats six?
Whoa, amazing! So you're saying there was even a free spot all along?!
Thank god, and you were making me all worried, you ...
IN THE MEANTIME...
That's right, I'd forgotten all about you!
(TN: The 1958 expedition left 15 dogs behind, of which 2 survived the winter and inspired a well-known film)
Toyotomi will finally come home the day after tomorrow!
That's right! I'll cook his favorite dish, duck soup!
Heh, ridiculous. With dogs as opponents, the outcome should be obvious.
You rascal! What kind of pon is that?! You!
Actually, the dog brothers Taro and Jiro were able to telepathically communicate the tiles they needed.
Ugh, letting him call the fucking dora ...
Fucking dogs ...
Taro is clearly going for a manzu chinitsu ...
But there's no way I'd lose to a dog!
BABA HIROKAZU AGE 24
BORN IN IKEBUKURO
All right! This is great, as long as I don't deal in, Baba will be last!
But I don't have any safe tiles!
In this ruleset, it's totally possible that he has a suji trap on 8p ...
The 4s matagi is the most dangerous ...
So I'll trust the kabe of 4m ...
There's no way he has a manzu wait!
Riichi ippatsu honitsu ittsuu, haneman?!
Now I'm tied with Baba!
But, I'm still only tied with him.
I'm still not guaranteed to be 4th.
Ura dora?! Baiman?!
Zugan!
Are you Toyotomi's family?
You're the members of the Antartic expedition, aren't you.
From now on ...
Why ...
Miss ...
This guy makes for a great lucklet feeder too.
Oh, is that so?
Ron! Riichi tanyao pinfu ippatsu iipeikou dora dora!
Zugan!
It's true! He gets bad draws and he deals in a lot, he's great to play against!
I know, right!
Yeah, let's play another hanchan!
Zugan!
A year later, Oda and the rest sailed to Antarctica again as the second wintering party.
Shin, do you think Toyotomi's still alive?
I don't know ...
But, if he still was ...
If he still was ...
What the hell happened here?
Frightening ...
OBSERVATION JOURNAL
I'M COLD / I'M STARVING / I'M TIRED
He's frozen into the Antarctic ice by now!
I suppose ...
I hear something!
Over here! Guys!
Shin! Look!
Wut the ...!
Toyotomi!
That fucker! He's playing mahjong for fish against fucking penguins!
That's how he survived!
Toyotomi!
He's running, the fucker!
Let's get him!
That fucking bastard, he still owes us!
Zugan!
To all those who sleep alone ...
Please take care of yourselves.
South 1, North seat, 8th turn, 23000 points
Tsumo 3m, dora 3m
>greeding dora
ngmi
I've caught a cold, damn it ...
Extremely popular mangaka Hatayama Masayuki's luxury villa?
(TN: The Super Zugan manga is drawn by Katayama Masayuki)
Ah, that was refreshing!
Wanna go for a swim too, Toyotomi?
I'd rather watch you swimming than swim myself, you know.
Anyway, I didn't know you had such talent, Toyotomi!
Turning your luckletism into the manga "Ultra Zugan", and just like that, you're a millionaire!
NOUVEAU RICHE ZUGAN
Boss!
There's guests to see you, boss.
Who?
They're three odd blokes who say they're boss's old friends ...
Saying:
"We were the inspiration for Ultra Zugan!"
"Give us our royalties!"
"Wut! Wut!"
And making a fuss about other such nonsensical things.
So they've come ...
Doesn't matter. Just send them away.
All right, mates, boss's busy. Why don't you come another time?
Fuck! He's gonna turn us away at the gate?!
That fucker, enjoying all his fortune by himself!
Gib it to me too! Gib me some of your fortune too, yeah!
Toyotomi, is it really okay to send them away like that?
By the way, I've got a present for you.
Wow, it's wonderful!
Thank you so much!
Boss.
I'm so happy, Toyotomi! I love you!
What?!
There are more guests, boss.
Again? Just send them away!
But, boss, they're girl fans of you, college students ... and pretty busty too.
Akina ... it turns out I've got some business.
See you later. Take it easy.
Hey, thanks for coming.
Oh, nice to meet you. My name is Satomi.
I'm a big fan of yours!
I'm the Toyotomi Hideyuki!
He shook my hand!
Since you're here, why don't I show you where I work?
Wow, I'd be delighted!
Sorry for intruding!
There's no desk to work on ...
That's because I ...
This is how I do my job!
Good girl ...
Stop raping me!
Bank balance 70 000 000 yen?!
Have your way with me ...
The old savings book trick always works!
Akina, it's not what it—
Shut the fuck up!
Akina! Wait!
Hello!
I'm Yukari!
I'm Eriko!
And you are ...?
Satomi's friends!
We were gonna to come together, but ...
No good, you're late!
Sorry!
Our train was a bit late!
You know, that guy's got 70 000 000 yen in savings ...
Wow, no way!
And it's well known he's bad at mahjong!
Uh, Maestro?
Would you have some time?
What for?
Wanna play some mahjong?
Mahjong?!
Sure, but ...
But ...?
My body can't take regular mahjong anymore ...
Are you okay with that?
Wh-what do you mean?
In my mahjong ...
The one who dealt in, even for just 1000 points, must take off a piece of clothing ...
Strip mahjong!
Kyah! Sounds like fun!
I'm first dealer!
Gotta do your best!
All right, let's go! Chop chop!
They're such naïve and good girls, and my haipai's good too!
3p.
Chii!
Don't need chun!
Hatsu!
Pon!
Don't even need any shousangen!
Ron! Hatsu only!
All right, now strip!
Oh no ...
Booba!
Hey, miss ...
You really cut that one, huh?
Ron! Chun only! Now strip!
Oh no no no, not again!
9s!
Ron!
No way!
Cheapest out, pinfu only missing tanyao and sanshoku, now strip!
C'mon, with that you'd skip the 9s ...
Ron, iipeikou only! Now strip!
Ron, ton only! Now strip!
Ron, riichi nomi, now strip!
Ron, chun only! Ron, nan only! Ron, riichi only! Ron, pinfu only! Ron, just ron!
Oh no, we've been tricked!
This guy is actually good?!
So weird!
Now, I've got you cornered!
SOUTH 1 EAST SEAT TURN 8
Got it!
Superb!
In this hand, you would normally cut 6m and go for 234 sanshoku using the 4m ...
But right now, I don't need a high score.
Dora: 4m
C'mon, I've got a 2369m wait, cut it already!
My wish is merely ron.
Just tanyao, waiting on 36p!
What a luckshitter!
Well, who'll be the first to show me her cute booba?
Yukari-chan?
Or Eriko-chan?
Or Satomi-chan after all?
Maestro ... it's your turn.
Zugan!
I tsumo'd ...
That's no fun at all!
I've got to cut my 6m head and change my wait!
It came out! Ron! Chun honitsu dora 1, mangan!
Zugan!
You rock, Satomi!
Genius!
Yay!
Zugan!
My luck's run out!
Uoh!
Kokushi musou tenpai!
>dama
Fuck, it won't come ...
I tsumo'd ...
Fuck, why are my draws so good tonight?
Should I just tsumo ...
No.
With just a little more effort ...
I can reap the sweet fruit of their charm ...
And for kokushi, furiten applies only to genbutsu.
(TN: Common rule in this era)
I'll seek a wonderful man's romance ...
Cut 1m!
Ron! Pinfu only!
Ron! Pinfu iipeikou!
Ron! Chanta chiitoitsu!
Zugan!
Now, because it's triple ron, take off your pants and underpants!
That's right!
No ...
Strip him!
Noooooo! Make it stop!
Next hanchan, let's bet this house!
Zuga—AAAAAAAA
Thus, Toyotomi died.
What's that, you guys?!
Hey, Toyotomi! Just woke up?
We were just deciding seats.
Get on with it, come on!
Phew ... it was just a dream ...
Tsumogiri ...
Ron! Pinfu dora 3! Riichi ippatsu pinfu iipeikou! Chanta chiitoitsu!
Zugan!
Toyotomi?
Aren't you Toyotomi?
Toyotomi!
A-Akina ...
Won't you buy a match, Akina?
In the end, you were defeated by those girls and lost even your mansion, didn't you?
Akina.
Kenjin?!
I shan't let ya be that dole bludger's missus.
Ya'll catch the poors from him too.
Kenjin ...
This is how you treat your boss ...
Buy yourself a pasty, mate.
Let's go. We'll be late to the party.
O-okay.
"Is the dream truth, or is truth but a dream?"
"Life is truly but a butterfly's dream."
(Zhuangzi)
"The proud do not endure [...] reveals the truth that the prosperous must decline."
(Tale of the Heike)
"In nothing but idleness, I have spent my days before this inkstone [...]"
(Tsurezuregusa)
"In spring, dawn [is best]."
(Pillow Book of Sei Shōnagon)
Zugan!
Have you seen him?
The mahjong demon undefeated for 20 years: Sakurada Mongai!
Why do three pros have to enter the local parlor's tourney again?!
Next time on Super Zugan:
"Undefeated! The Legendary Mahjong Demon" and "Whose Will Be the Glory...?"
Don't miss it! Don't want to you to sleep on it!